<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl'  href='../xslt/list.xsl'?>
<root xmlns:jobsinmalta="http://jobsinmalta.com/jobsinmalta-schema" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" jobsinmalta:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://jobsinmalta.com/jobsinmalta.xsd" encoding="utf-8">
<channel><title>Castille</title><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/rss</link><description>News</description><copyright>Copyright 2016 Castille All rights reserved.</copyright><item><title>Pensions Supervisor</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this role is to supervise the administration team of&amp;nbsp;a Pensions&amp;nbsp;Company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Ensuring efficient communication with prospective and existing customers, transferring schemes and service providers;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Setting up terms of business with service providers;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Communicating with other departments within the company;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Ensuring that cases are followed up efficiently;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Monitoring the progress of the processing of transfer requests from transferring schemes;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Monitoring scheme accounts on a daily basis;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Ensuring that payment requests and investment and disinvestment requests are processed efficiently;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Ensuring timely reporting to authorities;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Maintaining an updated training register for the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;QUALIFICATIONS AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in administering Qualifying Recognised Overseas Pension Schemes (QROPS), knowledge of the local regulatory framework, good customer service and communication skills and the ability to motivate and lead a team are essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Allison&amp;nbsp;at finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1241</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:36:04 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1241</guid></item><item><title>Sales &amp; Business Development Officers</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In support of planned business growth our client is&amp;nbsp;currently looking to hire two Sales &amp;amp; Business Development professionals (one senior; one junior) to join their&amp;nbsp;Malta office.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a challenging and varied role with&lt;b&gt; responsibilities including&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Identify, pursue and close sales opportunities with new leads and existing clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Conduct client meetings across the range of Company&amp;nbsp;products within the EMEA &amp;amp; US region&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Coordinate software demos highlighting the benefits and features of our cutting-edge compliance software tools&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Generate sales proposals and work closely with senior management in order to close deals&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Source new and alternative distribution channels&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Develop new business ideas&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Develop strong relationships with other industry groups and service providers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Experience / Skills:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A graduate degree in any field including accounting or legal or banking&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;For the senior hire, a proven track record of sales in financial services industry is necessary; experience of the asset management sector would be highly beneficial&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;For the junior hire, a track record in sales and / or sales support roles is required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated, results-oriented individual with an eye for detail&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Exceptional English communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong organisational and follow up skills a must (including use of a CRM to track sales efforts)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Great IT skills; experience with MS Dynamics CRM a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidates will benefit from an attractive remuneration package commensurate with qualifications and experience, together with the opportunity to become part of an energetic team in a well-structured and growing organisation operating in the asset management sector in Malta and across the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Allison&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1462</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:35:50 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1462</guid></item><item><title>Branch Officer (Insurance)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A prominent Maltese Insurance Company is seeking a Branch Officer to&amp;nbsp;manage&amp;nbsp;a portfolio of existing clients,&amp;nbsp;with the aim of maintaining existing business as well as creating and optimising new business opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This post&amp;nbsp;involves dealing in all classes of business including claims handling and the chosen candidate will gain wide-ranging experience in underwriting, sales and claims.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills and experience required:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Insurance experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Customer relationship managment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;IT proficiency including good knowledge of Microsoft Office applications&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent written and spoken Maltese and English&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A good advanced level of education and preferably insurance qualifications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You should be entrepreneurial and enjoy the challenge of a sales job. Should you be selected, full on the job training will be given.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Allison&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1473</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:35:36 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1473</guid></item><item><title>Consumer Banking Officer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;A prominent Maltese Bank&amp;nbsp;focused on providing market leading savings products and investment services, currently have a great&amp;nbsp;opportunity for a Consumer Banking Officer to join their established Team;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;JOB DESCRIPTION &lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Consumer Banking Officer will form part of a team responsible within the local branch network to promote, sell and maintain relationships with new and existing banking and investment customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duties and responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working within a team to promote and sell to new and existing customers the Bank&amp;rsquo;s savings, investment and foreign exchange products&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Opening and maintaining customers accounts whilst ensuring that existing relationships are kept to high standards by offering a superior customer service&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Attending to customers at the branch whilst making outbound calls, organising meetings and making outside visits to existing/ potential clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting the Branch Manager / Head of Branch Network to bring on board new customers and build up the client, deposit and investment base&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required knowledge, skills and experience&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;In possession of or studying to obtain a qualification related to Investments such as the Certificate for Financial Advisers (CeFA) or equivalent Diploma/Degree&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years experience working in a bank or financial institution with a desire to work in sales&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent in written and spoken English and Maltese&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a target and performance-oriented manner&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Posesses a customer-centric&amp;nbsp;attitude&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;approach&amp;nbsp;to&amp;nbsp;sales&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Possess good verbal and written communication skills with a proven ability to develop and build relationships both internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this role please forward your CV to Allison - amckenzie@castilleresources.com.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1489</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:35:21 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1489</guid></item><item><title>Pensions Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Pensions Administrator will report to the Pensions Supervisor and will handle the daily administration of pension schemes administered by the Company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;KEY RESPONSIBILITIES:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) Communicating with prospective and existing customers and service providers,;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Providing application packs to prospective customers and service providers;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Providing questionnaires to service providers;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) Setting up terms of business with service providers and investment houses as may be required;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;5) Opening files for new customers and service providers;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6) Updating the company&amp;rsquo;s IT register on a daily basis;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7) Communicating with transferring schemes and processing pension transfer paperwork;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;8) Monitoring the progress of the processing of pension transfer requests;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;9) Referring any deeds, payment requests, investment requests and any other matters with compliance and/or legal implications to the Compliance Officer;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;QUALIFICATIONS AND EXPERIENCE REQUIRED:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Experience in administering Qualifying Recognised Overseas Pension Schemes (QROPS) is preferable, but not essential.&amp;nbsp; Good customer service and communication skills and&amp;nbsp; attention to detail are essential.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Allison&amp;nbsp;at &lt;a href="mailto:finance@castilleresources.com"&gt;finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1240</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:31:47 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1240</guid></item><item><title>Junior Pensions Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A leading global provider of high-value business services to clients operating and investing globally is seeking to recruit a Pension Scheme Administrator. In this role you will&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;assist with the on-boarding, general administration and liaison with counter parties of the members&amp;rsquo;&amp;nbsp;Pension Retirement Scheme, held on trust.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
MAIN DUTIES OF THE POSITION:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Responsibility for a portfolio of Pension Scheme members&amp;rsquo; accounts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;To ensure regular updates to Scheme members&amp;rsquo; records and other databases as&amp;nbsp;required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Liaison with Investment Managers, clients and service providers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Collating of information from Investment Managers and service providers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Assisting with client onboarding, benefit payments, strike-offs and transfers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Opening/closure of Bank accounts, custody accounts and preparation of supporting due diligence&amp;nbsp;documentation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Providing both verbal and written reports to the senior pension scheme administrator&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PRINCIPAL QUALIFICATIONS /SKILL SET REQUIRED:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Good working knowledge of a busy administrative environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Capability with respect to Microsoft Office (i.e. Word, e-mail, Excel)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Proactive and willing to take ownership of problems with attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ability to manage a large number of projects and issues simultaneously and to tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;High degree of communication skills, verbal and written with the ability to&amp;nbsp;communicate externally&amp;nbsp;and internally at all levels&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Ability to work with multi-cultural teams&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Previous experience in similar roles within financial services industry would be a plus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Allison&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1492</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:31:31 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1492</guid></item><item><title>Senior Investment Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A well established Financial Services Company is looking to employ a Senior Investment Administrator.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Primary&amp;nbsp;Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the upkeep of the assets under&amp;nbsp;management report and ensuring that regulatorydeadlines are reached in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring of investments and meeting&amp;nbsp;representatives of different investment houses or&amp;nbsp;funds&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Compilation of data on the investments the&amp;nbsp;trustees usually deal with&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Support to the Admin Department: assisting in&amp;nbsp;filling application forms with investment houses,&amp;nbsp;answering to investment queries from&amp;nbsp;members/IFA, reviewing of dealing instructions and&amp;nbsp;explaining the investment type&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Support to the Compliance Department:&amp;nbsp;assisting the compliance officer in handling&amp;nbsp;complaints, risk assessment and other queries&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintaining adequate investments policies and&amp;nbsp;principles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1499</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:43:34 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1499</guid></item><item><title>HR Business Partner</title><description>&lt;p&gt;An international Financial Services Company is&amp;nbsp;looking for an experienced HR Business Partner for their&amp;nbsp;Maltese office. You will be part of a challenging environment in an International team atmosphere and spirit,&amp;nbsp;where innovative ideas are supported and highly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As HR Business Partner you&amp;nbsp;will be in charge of all HR related topics and will have an opportunity to directly influence the functioning of HR processes&amp;nbsp;and fine-tune the company&amp;#39;s&amp;nbsp;established processes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The main responsibilities are:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Managing HR processes from end to end with a high attention to detail and in a collaborative manner&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Coach and advise managers on HR processes and people management&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Overall responsibility for the recruitment &amp;amp; selection process&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Compensation and benefits administration, payroll processing&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Effective onboarding process - host new joiner training and assure that new employees integrate effectively into the organization&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Relocation assistance for new employees, if needed&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Foster relationships with cross-functional stakeholders to build a better employment experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Support with the organization of team events and in house trainings&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Min 3&amp;nbsp;years&amp;#39; working experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent English both written and spoken is must&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1491</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:43:22 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1491</guid></item><item><title>Wealth Relationship Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Wealth Relationship Manager will form part of the Consumer Banking team responsible to promote and sell savings, investments and foreign exchange products through effective relationship management with new and existing retail banking customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Duties and responsibilities&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working within a team to promote and sell the Bank&amp;rsquo;s wealth management, investment and foreign exchange products to new and existing customers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Developing leads and referrals from existing clients through regular client reviews whilst being proactive in the way new clients are onboarded&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Meeting targets by establishing new relationships and managing existing relationships to increase deposits, generate new assets under custody and revenue from the Bank&amp;rsquo;s investment and foreign exchange products&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Required knowledge, skills and experience&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Certificate for Financial Advisers (CeFA) or equivalent, to be registered with the MFSA to obtain the required license to provide financial advice&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least three years experience working in this field&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to work in a target and performance oriented manner&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Possess a customer centric attitude and approach to sales&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to develop and build relationships both internally and externally&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills in both English and Maltese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of&amp;nbsp;Mark at finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1488</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:43:11 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1488</guid></item><item><title>Risk Analyst (Insurance)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;One of the world&amp;rsquo;s leading insurance companies with over 50 locations around the globe is seeking a&amp;nbsp;Risk Analyst to&amp;nbsp;support proper risk management at its Malta Office&amp;nbsp;based on local regulatory requirements and the standards of the company. He/She shall report and provide support to the Chief Risk Officer and &lt;b&gt;responsibilities will include:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;maintaining and validating the internal risk model&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;performing the Own Risk and Solvency Assessment (ORSA)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;assessment of risk (underwriting, market, credit, liquidity, operational, strategic)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;reviewing of transactions including accumulation control and scenario analysis&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;maintaining the Internal Control System and risk policies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;maintaining Security &amp;amp; Continuity Risk Management, including IT-Security&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;identifying, monitoring and reporting of risks to various stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Profile:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;3 years&amp;rsquo; experience within the&amp;nbsp;industry&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;High level University degree or equivalent qualification preferably in mathematics, statistics, economics or insurance&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Distinctive analytical and conceptual skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Highly motivated, quick learner with the ambition to apply technical skills in a pragmatic way&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of Solvency II is considered an advantage&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Microsoft Office tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will be occupying a role providing excellent opportunity for growth and development with a first class international organisation. In-/External Training will be provided where required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1468</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:43:02 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1468</guid></item><item><title>Commercial Banking Relationship Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A&amp;nbsp;large International Bank is looking for an experienced&amp;nbsp;client Relationship Manager&amp;nbsp;for their corporate&amp;nbsp;business.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
The Relationship Manager will manage a portfolio of corporate&amp;nbsp;clients and &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
serve as a key player in building customer relationships with a focus on &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
client experience and risk management. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Main responsibilities of the role&lt;/b&gt;: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the management of a portfolio of customers,&amp;nbsp;including growing the portfolio by deepening and developing existing&amp;nbsp;relationships and prospecting for new customers. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Building internal and external relationships to deliver high quality&amp;nbsp;customer experience by providing appropriate solutions and services.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Following a robust risk management culture and adhering to&amp;nbsp;regulatory requirements. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Significant credit risk management. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;Qualifications &amp;amp; experience: &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in a client relationship management role preferably in Financial Services &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and influencing skills at all levels, both&amp;nbsp;internally and externally. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Well organised and able to work under pressure on own initiative to&amp;nbsp;manage competing priorities. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of different markets, industries and businesses&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge and understanding of financial and business concepts&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Professional qualifications relative to the role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Eager to develop and embark on a career path&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1465</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:42:53 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1465</guid></item><item><title>Personal Assistant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summary of Role &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To provide senior level administrative support in a very dynamic executive setting. To play an active role in improving the efficiency of the MD&amp;rsquo;s Office and senior management within the company. .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Knowledge and Skills&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Flawless execution of administrative activities, with high attention to detail and organization&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong team work skills and strong ability to offer suggestions and improvements to process and work effectively with all personalities&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to be flexible in response to changing needs and priorities of the business&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Thorough knowledge of office management practices and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle public relations items&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proven ability to manage projects, work under pressure and consistently achieve deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to handle confidential and sensitive information&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Educated to a Diploma level or Higher&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience of working as a Personal&amp;nbsp;Assistant&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Extensive Diary management experience, using MS Outlook&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent organisations skills and an ability to multitask and work within strict time constraints&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong working knowledge of MS Word, Excel, Outlook &amp;amp; PowerPoint&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Primary Responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Diary management making appropriate use of time and resources, and carrying out the role of &amp;#39;gatekeeper&amp;#39;, advising others of diary priorities.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Planning meetings, visits and events as appropriate, ensuring all details are confirmed and correct&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintaining the Housekeeping of the MD&amp;rsquo;s office and meetings&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Organising all travel and accommodation, making best use of the Managing Director&amp;rsquo;s time&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Organise papers and briefing notes for meetings.&amp;nbsp;Ensuring briefing and board papers are obtained and presented in an appropriate format and in sufficient time in advance of meetings to allow for reading/preparation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Draft as required, high quality and confidential letters, documents and emails within required deadline&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Print, scan and fax confidential documentation as and when required ensuring that the information remains strictly confidential&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Anticipate requirements, clarifying as appropriate and sending back items which are not up to par&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Drafting PowerPoint presentations and collecting information as required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Handle incoming and outgoing communications to take initiative in prioritising, channelling and processing telephone calls, messages and correspondence ensuring that draft replies are provided in a timely manner&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Take the necessary steps in the Managing Director&amp;rsquo;s absence to ensure calls and messages are responded to&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be able to react to constant changes in work load and arrange appointments and meetings at short notice and often at short notice re-arrange meetings and make alternative arrangements for travel and accommodation.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be able to travel within Malta and abroad with the Managing Director as and when required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1451</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:42:34 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1451</guid></item><item><title>Investment Assistant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To support the investment function and dealing desk, execution and monitoring of the trading function, maintaining investment portfolio information, and assist with the review of dealing instructions and portfolios.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Core Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Degree in Finance or related fields or relevant working experience.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in trading preferred.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Excel.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Access considered an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Knowledge and Skills&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledgeable in all major asset classes and investment transactions procedure.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to understand the risks connected to trading procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Familiar with all main office productivity software.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience of office environment.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Advanced communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Attention to details, and ability to work under pressure to meet daily deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to set own deadline and work unsupervised&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Primary responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Management of the entire dealing process from reception of dealing instructions to execution of orders.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring of dealing instructions&amp;rsquo; compliance with statutory and internal investment policies and parameters.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Co-ordination of aging debtors dealing instructions.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Management of Corporate Action notifications and voluntary actions by relying with relevant IFAs and Investment Houses.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaise with IFAs, Investment Houses and other external 3rd counterparties.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Participation in the monitoring and review of portfolios.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Review of IFAs performance.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Contributing in the preparation of key investment reports for the management and external stakeholders such as auditors and regulators.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1033</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:36:11 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1033</guid></item><item><title>Administrator (Pensions)</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Summary of Role &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To administer a portfolio of trusts and companies and pensions, handling the diverse needs of a number of private clients with focus on effective service, quality, productivity and efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Knowledge and&amp;nbsp;Skills&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Educated to A level, with passes in O&amp;rsquo;Level English and Mathematics&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Familiar with QROPS&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to identify risks associated with client transactions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Financial Services Background essential&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to set own deadlines and work accurately to tight deadlines for self and potential reportees&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Primary&amp;nbsp;Responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Establish initial administration procedure and maintain office administration in conjunction with the Manager.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaising with clients and their advisers in respect of service issues, via telephone and other electronic interface.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Execution of client transactions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintain client data within a primary management information system&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Undertake and manage full time recording and client billing process of self and others&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of correspondence with clients and their advisors&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring that statutory record are accurate and full audit trail maintained&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaise with intermediary, client and transferring trustees/investment managers whilst transfer proceeding.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Provide regular valuations to clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of payment instructions, and monitoring execution of instructions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of minutes, and ancillary document&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Production and submission of government returns&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;MFSA/HMRC reporting requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV to msims@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/743</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:36:04 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/743</guid></item><item><title>Pensions Admin Team Leader</title><description>&lt;p&gt;In an expanding business environment our client is seeking a&amp;nbsp;Pensions Administrator Team Leader who will mainly be &lt;b&gt;responsible for&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Leading a team of administrators and assistant administrators&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Communicating with the staff members across departments, IFA&amp;rsquo;s and client&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Complying to internal and external rules and regulations&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring the welfare of staff and conduct annual objectives and appraisals&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring up to date&amp;nbsp;adequate training in Pension Administration&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring the department maintains a high level of service to it&amp;rsquo;s clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting the Pensions Administration Manager and the Pensions Administration Director.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Core Competencies Required&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to work with Numbers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Computer literate (ideally holding an ECDL certificate)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to interact effectively with clients at all levels&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Educated with either a Diploma or Degree Level in Financial services&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;2 years Experience and knowledge on QROPS&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to identify risks associated with client transactions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Familiar with the main office productivity software&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to set own deadlines and work accurately to tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV to msims@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/709</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 15:35:54 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/709</guid></item><item><title>Junior Accountant - Marketing and Advertising</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Want to join a leading sales platform?&amp;nbsp;We are looking to hire a talented Junior Accountant to strengthen our team in Malta on a full-time basis. The office is based in St Julians.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Debtor/Creditor Control&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Issuing of Sales invoices&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Revenue Reconciliations &amp;amp; Bank Reconciliations&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting in the month-end closing &amp;amp; annual audit procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;b&gt;:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;AAT Diploma in accounting &amp;amp; preferably in initial stages of&amp;nbsp;ACCA&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;2 years&amp;rsquo; experience in a similar environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good analytical skills, with the ability to define and solve issues&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to prioritize and manage multiple tasks to effectively meet deadlines.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask and prioritize responsibilities.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be a team player.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1420</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 14:05:35 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1420</guid></item><item><title>Technical Programme Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The technical programme manager will manage end to end delivery of strategic programmes within the organisation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duties:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
- Develop, lead and manage the Technical delivery of the Programme, which will consist of a series of contributing projects.&lt;br /&gt;
- Ensure coordination between the PMs and Coordinators working on the projects.&lt;br /&gt;
- Project financials and budget management&lt;br /&gt;
- Progress reports for the Programme Director&lt;br /&gt;
- Stakeholder and work stream management to ensure successful end to end delivery&lt;br /&gt;
- Manage requests from the organisation and ensuring these are aligned with the programme&amp;rsquo;s strategy and priorities&lt;br /&gt;
- Time Management&lt;br /&gt;
- Promote effective cross-functional teamwork throughout the delivery lifecycle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills required:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Degree in Business Management, Electrical Engineering or IT&lt;br /&gt;
- Experience in IT Enterprise programmes with a proven track record in the successful delivery of Programmes and/or Projects&lt;br /&gt;
- Ability to engage with stakeholders, develop relationships and communicate results&lt;br /&gt;
- Proven influencing and negotiating skills&lt;br /&gt;
- Has strong communication and presentation skills&lt;br /&gt;
- Accredited Project/Programme Management qualification (such as PRINCE2)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why you should you join the organisation?:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Felxible working hours&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Attractive remuneration&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Great working environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Senior Level position&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidates, contact Clare on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1543</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 12:21:38 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1543</guid></item><item><title>Accounts Officer - Healthcare</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A local leading healthcare distributor operating in&amp;nbsp;the pharmaceutical, diagnostics, laboratory and hospital equipment as well as dental sector is looking to expand their existing finance team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are seeking to employ Accounts Officer who will be responsible for performing general accounting functions and maintaining accounting records as well administrative and &amp;nbsp;HR duties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate should have A level in Accounts and actively studying towards a professional accounting qualification ( ACCA, ACA or equivalent).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Preference will be given to those candidates who have a minimum of 1-2 years experience in a related post.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1434</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 12:02:11 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1434</guid></item><item><title>Accounts Assistant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;An international Financial Services provider is looking for &lt;b&gt;Accounts Assistant&lt;/b&gt; who will be reporting to Accounts Senior Manager within Accounting Services Department.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal candidate should have experience in a similar role and should be in a process of pursuing&amp;nbsp;ACCA qualification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Preparation of accounts from&amp;nbsp;postings to management accounts,&amp;nbsp;including&amp;nbsp;preparation of VAT returns&amp;nbsp;and year end close offs.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Preparing financial statements in line&amp;nbsp;with IFRS/GAPSE/GAPSME&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;Actively managing&amp;nbsp;client&amp;nbsp;relationship&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1538</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 11:56:55 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1538</guid></item><item><title>Affiliate Manager (German Market) - Gaming</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our client, an&amp;nbsp;established and expanding Gaming company, is seeking to recruit a German speaking Affiliate Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will be responsible for the recruitment, maintenance and development of affiliates within the German market and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With sales experience specifically within the Casino industry, the Affiliate Manager will be required to identify opportunities, develop reward concepts for key partners, and enhance the current programme. Applicants must be able to demonstrate excellent people skills, engagement and motivational abilities to drive growth forward.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Overseeing affiliate acquisitions and retention&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Managing relationships with affiliates, including the recruitment of new affiliate members&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Constant monitoring of affiliates, reward plans awarded, and placements given to the Company&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assessment of traffic and volumes brought by affiliates post-acquisition and handling affiliates struggling with performance accordingly&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure compliance amongst affiliates with regards to terms and conditions, while analysing activity with optimal reward plans in place&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monthly preparation of reports on recently recruited affiliates, promotions, and detailed statistics&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of affiliate newsletter&amp;nbsp;each month&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Meeting personal and departmental KPI&amp;rsquo;s as assigned by the Company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years&amp;rsquo; experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of the Casino industry&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent in German and English (additional languages would be advantageous)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Self-motivated and proactive character, driven to produce results&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent negotiation abilities, with analytical and implementation skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Creative and innovative in approach&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to build and develop strong relationships&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sociable and comfortable working in a fast pace small team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should this role be of interest and you would like to be considered, please contact Simon&amp;nbsp;on &lt;a href="mailto:tech@castilleresources.com"&gt;tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1415</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:43:08 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1415</guid></item><item><title>Junior ERP Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a Business &amp;amp; Computing Graduate? Do you have an A level in accounts? Ever thought of joining an ERP team to assist with the successful implementation and maintenance of Microsoft Dynamics NAV systems?&lt;br /&gt;
Our Client is looking for new graduate with a passion for computer systems. The role involves all aspects of implementation of Microsoft Dynamics NAV-ERP solutions from presale prototype work through the project life cycle to go live and ongoing support. It is great opportunity to develop customer service skills when dealing with clients as well as achieve Microsoft Dynamics NAV knowledge and achieve relevant certifications. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;C/AL Programming&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Configuring NAV reporting functions&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Provision of support and training to end users&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Assistance with development of NAV-based portal projects and assessment of functional requirements on NAV implementation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Requirements&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Development skills in C/AL (Pascal)&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Business &amp;amp; Computing Graduate with A levels in accounting&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Microsoft Certification in NAV development with experience in NAV customizations on Microsoft Dynamics NAV 2009-2016 in considered as an asset&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Simon&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1178</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:42:58 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1178</guid></item><item><title>Junior Web Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Business management company is looking for Junior Web Developer which is familiar with C#, .NET environment to join their existing team. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Programming, configuration, management and maintenance of complex ASP.NET applications;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Design and implementation of complex relational database schemes;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Interface development for web-based applications;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Analysis and design of web-based applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;C#&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;.NET&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;HTML&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;CSS3&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;MS SQL&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;1-2 years of experience in similar role&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Proficiency in LINQ, Bootstrap, jQuery, MVC, SASS,&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;.Net based CMS will be considered as an asset&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Simon&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1177</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:42:55 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1177</guid></item><item><title>Senior PHP Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Seeking a senior profile to join the our client&amp;#39;s development team in Malta and work on PHP and JavaScript solutions. Applicants need to conversant in both front end and back end development and are able to write unit tests and deliver a full solution.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Full stack developers are encouraged to apply and explore this vacancy which will give them the opportunity to strengthen their PHP&amp;nbsp;and JavaScript exposure and have the possibility of working in a young, international and dynamic team, who are passionate about technology and are keen to learn and grow further.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, e-mail Simon on tech@castilleresources.com. Applicants need to be in possession of an EU passport, given work permit time frames.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1299</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:42:42 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1299</guid></item><item><title>PHP Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Vacancy for a senior PHP&amp;nbsp;developer to work within the iGaming industry. S/he will be responsible for integrating 3rd party APIs, maintain an internal support documentation and troubleshoot technical issues that may arise from time to time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Minimum of 4 years work experience within PHP development and&amp;nbsp;a good understanding of MySQL, JavaScript and jQuery are required. Having a good knowledge of RESTful API design and implementation, together with experience working in Agile methodologies will be considered an asset.&amp;nbsp;Chosen candidate need to be able to work both individually as well as in a team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more info, e-mail Simon on space@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1251</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:42:36 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1251</guid></item><item><title>SENIOR INTERNAL AUDIT EXECUTIVE - BANKING</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A leading financial institution is seeking to employ an experienced internal auditor with experience audit and credit risk. The right candidate will be joining a highly skilled team of people and will be reporting directly to the Chief Internal Audit Officer of the company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Reasons why you should join this company:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Challenging but rewarding role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Career growth and personal development opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A market leading salary&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working with a highly skilled team under the supervision of the Chief Internal Audit Officer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duties and responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Building and maintaining professional good working relationships both internally and externally&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Participating in discussions with key business stakeholders leading to final issue acceptance and remediation&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Ensuring that proper planning procedures are undergone when carrying out the various audit reviews&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Identifying effective and efficient control tests, including the development of new audit tools and methodologies to facilitate the identification of risks&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Standardizing audit programmes to ensure that all significant risks are adequately considered&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Flow charting of processes to highlight key controls and process weaknesses&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Evaluating and monitoring business processes and controls and governance practices, through the conduct of Internal Audit reviews&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Providing feedback and recommendations for improvement whilst ensuring compliance with regulatory requirements and best practices&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Providing feedback with regard to the setting of resolution deadlines for particular audit findings&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Supporting other departments to assist the correct implementation of the recommended business processes.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Undertaking the necessary continued professional education&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Other duties as may be determined from time to time by the Chief Internal Audit Officer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required knowledge, skills and experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;A qualification in Audit or Accountancy (ACA/ACCA/IIA)&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Strong knowledge of credit risk and controls and a working knowledge of relevant areas of regulation&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Strong analytic skills and familiarity with current credit risk practices and credit risk mitigation techniques would also be valuable&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Strong interpersonal, verbal and written communication skills&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Knowledge of credit or lending banking products&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1541</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:13:45 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1541</guid></item><item><title>Software Solutions Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a senior developer with Project management skills?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role could be you&amp;rsquo;re the next step in your career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting directly to the CTO, you will be responsible for managing, planning, organising, directing and project managing operations of the Software Solutions function.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ideal Candidate will have:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;IT qualification or a related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A min three years&amp;rsquo; experience in managing a development team;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong PM skills (Ideally using PRINCE2 methodology)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience developing and managing IT projects;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The ability to work under pressure&lt;br /&gt;
	Organisational skills;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills &amp;ndash; both written &amp;amp; verbal;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong skills in negotiating, relationship building and problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The ability to work in a team and independently when needed&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good analytical skills and be a quick learner&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Exposure that would be considered an asset:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Financial Services Industry experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in mobile technologies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working in the Cards/payments business.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidates contact Clare on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1542</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 09:06:04 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1542</guid></item><item><title>Business Analyst</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A financial services organisation is seeking to recruit a Business Analyst who is capable of taking the initiative in the analysis of various business needs. S/he will be working in a team of Business Analysts and will be actively participating in the understanding and documentation of internal business requirements.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring business requirements fit within the boundaries of the systems;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reviewing functional documentation and coordinating feedback with business;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Define and highlight potential gaps between functionalities and desired changes;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Develop and review test cases for business and functional requirements;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Conducting basic end user training and first line support for new deployments;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Diploma/Degree in Business &amp;amp; Computing or related areas;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills in English and Maltese;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good analytical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge or keen interest in financial services will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call or e-mail Simon for more details regarding this vacancy&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1520</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:51:05 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1520</guid></item><item><title>Payments Officer - Bank</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a payments officer to join a a young team of professionals in a bank. &amp;nbsp;The ideal candidate would be have experience with handling&amp;nbsp;SWIFT payments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Processing of payments requests&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Forex transactions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Daily processing and reconciliation of inward payments&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring of customers&amp;#39; transactions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;KYC and due diligence procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Minimum 1 year experience in a similar environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent in spoken and written English&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Organised and adhere to deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Stefania at finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1514</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 08:48:50 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1514</guid></item><item><title>Accounts Executive</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A leading local Education&amp;nbsp;provider is seeking to employ Accounts Executive to grow his existing finance team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;assisting Finance Manager&amp;nbsp;in the performance of the Accounting function of the company&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of bank reconciliation statements&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting the Finance Manager in the preparation and compiling of the monthly Management Accounts and quarterly VAT Returns;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist Audit preparations;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Carry out any other Accounts work required for end of year;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Issuing monthly invoices and Re-charges and resolving the disputes arising with our Inter-Companies;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Supervising the Accounts Clerks;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist the Finance Manager with the preparation of Budgets and other ad hoc reports as required;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Company benefits:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;free health insurance to all&amp;nbsp;employees, with a possibility to&amp;nbsp;add family/relatives&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;free parking for employees&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;international atmosphere and good working environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The role of the Accounts Executive is one of high responsibility, directly concerned with the day-to day accounting duties of the department, and assisting the Finance Manager in financial reporting matters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1526</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 16:25:27 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1526</guid></item><item><title>Accountant - Gaming</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The Role&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently looking to employ a meticulous &amp;amp; career minded&amp;nbsp;accountant within a reputable gaming company.The role&amp;nbsp;will be a part of the Accounting team&amp;nbsp;and you will report to the Accounting Manager&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This role is focused on revenue calculations and accounts receivable however you will be involved in other tasks, and will be a person of support to other parts of the Accounting team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duties &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The role will include but not be limited to the following areas:&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Accounts Receivable, sending invoices, reply to client queries, book keeping of customer payment and credit control;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Review of commercial term clauses in sales agreements;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Communication with other departments&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;General book keeping, reconciliations, book closing;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Other various tasks within the accounting department, such as investigations, administrative work, filing etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;CPA, CA, ACA or ACCA qualified or part-qualified or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong accounting background and accounts preparation experience.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent teamwork, team-management, interpersonal, client relationship and communication (written and verbal) skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested kindly send me an email on finance@castilleresources.com or click on the &amp;#39;Apply now&amp;#39; button.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1486</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 16:20:32 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1486</guid></item><item><title>Accountant - Pharmaceutical</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;leading Pharmaceutical Company is&amp;nbsp;seeking to employ an Accountant&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;to join their finance function. The position has arisen&amp;nbsp;due to growth and positive restructuring and the person will be&amp;nbsp;responsible for the effective management of&amp;nbsp;financial reporting, control of systems and processes, and relationship management.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Prepare monthly management accounts for the business units they are responsible for&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist the Finance Manager with the preparation of monthly Group reporting&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist in the analysis of all expense and revenue lines in the P&amp;amp;L on a monthly basis&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintain the fixed asset system and reconcile it on a monthly basis with the general ledger&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Prepare monthly reconciliations of balance sheet accounts, including accruals and prepayments&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintain all general ledger accounting&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist in generating and analysing revenue and cost of sales reports from our IT system to support management accounts analysis and decision-making&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist with the audit preparation work to allow for timely completion of the annual financial statements and corporation tax returns&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist in the preparation of annual budget and periodic forecasts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Provide ad hoc analysis, as required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Travel to our retail outlets, as required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaise with the rest of the finance team and all internal and external customers, as required &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Education Required:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Recently qualified accountant (ACCA, ACA, Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or equivalent)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong academic background&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Experience Required:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Relevant experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good Excel Skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Commercial acumen and a good eye for detail,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to work alone and as part of a team and achieve results&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Specific Competencies:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Gathering information in a precise and systematic way, processing data efficiently and presenting back in a way that appeals to its reader and heightens understanding of that information.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Approaching multiple, varied tasks in a systematic manner that ensures that tasks are completed to time.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Transferring insights, knowledge and experiences to others (formally or informally) to ensure that learning is shared across the team.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Using targeted questioning to fully gain the perspectives of others and identify what drives them and concerns them. &amp;nbsp;Actively seeing things from the viewpoint of others and being open and honest at all times to build trust in all interactions.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Showing application that is driven by a combination of personal principles and values and the expectations of the business. Fulfilling commitments consistently and treating others fairly and with respect.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested kindly send me an email on finance@castilleresources.com or click on the &amp;#39;Apply now&amp;#39; button.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1540</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 16:20:15 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1540</guid></item><item><title>Senior Fund Accountant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking to employ a qualified accountant with funds experience to join&amp;nbsp;a reputable&amp;nbsp;international company. They provide a wide variety of solutions such as&amp;nbsp;funds &amp;amp;&amp;nbsp;pensions services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a new&amp;nbsp;position within the company&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;will offer good career progression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Compiling NAV calculations, administration of trades and fund reconciliations as well as performing cash, positions and market-value reconciliations&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of financial statements compliant with IFRS/GAAP and statutory returns in accordance with prescribed client deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitor clients&amp;rsquo; regulatory compliance and provide help with the year-end audit process&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist with the preparation of client documentation and reporting&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Processing of subscription and redemption activity for multiple funds abiding by anti-money laundering and compliance procedures;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Providing accounting and administrative services for client companies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaising with the funds&amp;rsquo; investors, bankers, independent auditors and other service providers to the Funds&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Supervision and training of Fund Administration staff and provide support when needed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;CPA, CA, ACA or ACCA qualified&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Minimum of two to five years&amp;rsquo; experience in an accounting/finance environment&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of financial instruments&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A strong work ethic with the proven ability to demonstrate initiative and meet tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal skills and the ability to work effectively within a team environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proficiency with the Microsoft Office suite of applications with Advanced MS Excel skills&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested contact Andre&amp;nbsp;by email on finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1354</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 15:01:07 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1354</guid></item><item><title>Risk Officer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A well established Maltese Financial Services company is seeking a Risk Officer. Reporting directly to the Managing Director, you will be responsible for all aspects of risk.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;be a mature person with a Financial Services background;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Insurance operational and technical knowledge considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;have a thorough knowledge of Regulatory requirements/deadlines in Financial Services reporting timeframes.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;have at least a minimum of 6 years in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary depending on level of experience after evaluation of candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1378</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 15:00:07 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1378</guid></item><item><title>Financial Crime Compliance Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a Financial Crime Compliance Manager to join a local Bank and assist in the development and implementation of policies, procedures and controls related to financial crime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting the Head of Compliance in AML, CTF, ABC and Sanctions regulations&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Overseeing the Customer Due Diligence processes in line with the Bank&amp;#39;s standards and regulatory obligations&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring of financial crime risks&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Acting as MLRO delegate&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Graduate in Banking, Compliance or related discipline&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluency&amp;nbsp;in Maltese and English together with good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent analytical and managerial skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Stefania at finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1440</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 14:51:25 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1440</guid></item><item><title>SENIOR FINANCIAL PLANNING MANAGER</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A leading international company with offices around the world is seeking to employ a &lt;b&gt;Senior financial planning manager&lt;/b&gt; to head the department in Malta. The right candidate would have experience working in a similar role with another international company or work within the advisory department of a reputable firm. A competitive salary including perks will be offered to the chosen candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Some of the main reasons why you should join this company :&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Market leading salary&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Attractive staff benefits&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Work closely with top management&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Managing a professional and driven team&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Stable and growing international company&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Main Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Translate business strategies into plans, budgets and financial and operational targets (P&amp;amp;L, KPIs, CapEx, B/S, Cash Flow and Working Capital)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Lead the Long Range Planning and the Annual Budgeting and Forecasting processes defining the calendar, models and best practices&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Define financial and operational targets for the business based on inputs received from relevant sources&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Submit and present the overall Budget scenarios to the Group&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Lead the monthly performance review process and present the results to management&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Co-ordinate and prepare analysis that provides insight on the overall business performance of the company&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Co-ordinate rolling forecasts based upon accurate trending of key indices with strong focus on anticipating and managing month-end results, and on management actions for the following months&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure alignment on statutory information, Group requirements and other stakeholder requirements&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Build and maintain market models&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Build and define Finance MI requirements&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of realistic &amp;amp; structured business cases to support investment &amp;amp; commercial decisions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be proactive, looking at problems, providing solutions &amp;amp; alternatives&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Execute profitability analysis of enterprise offers and ad-hoc profitability analysis&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Support development of calculation tools and verify alignment with forecast&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Provide informed and insightful analysis on actual performance and support in identifying management actions to remedy gapsvs. forecast&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proactively advise and support the business unit to ensure an effective operating control environment is in place&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;Core competencies, knowledge and experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Solid Accountant - formal qualifications in Accountancy, possessing a sound financial academic background and analytical skills,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preference will be given to candidates with a corporate finance background in a big four audit firm&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Self-starter, forward looking, meticulous and capable of working on own initiative, working at senior management level&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;IT literate with a good working knowledge of office based computer systems&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be able to demonstrate a strong drive for results, achieving and improving objectives&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Team management skills, ability to drive a positive vibe and ambience within own team and cross functionally&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to adapt quickly to a dynamic environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1539</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 14:34:07 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1539</guid></item><item><title>Banking &amp; Compliance Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking to recruit a young individual to join an established corporate service provider in Malta. &amp;nbsp;The selected candidate shall join the banking and compliance department and shall be responsible for the opening of bank accounts, processing of payments and carry out compliance checks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Minimum A level standard of education&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent organisation skills and work to tight deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English and Maltese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this opportunity apply online or send your CV for the attention of Stefania at finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1537</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 13:43:54 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1537</guid></item><item><title>Account Manager - Gaming</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Interested in starting a career within the Gaming industry? Seeking an Account Manager who will be responsible for building and maintaining a network of stakeholders within the Gaming industry and ensure a high quality client service and support at all times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further responsibilities include:&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assistance with compiling documentation;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Articles &amp;amp; gaming related material contribution, compilation and review;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Help co-ordinate tasks and workloads internally;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Follow up on&amp;nbsp;business opportunities;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Travel from time to time to conferences, client meetings and seminars&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants should be in possession of:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A tertiary level of education in an IT/ Business/ Communications/ Management area;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge or keen interest in the online gambling industry;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills in English. Additional languages&amp;nbsp;are an asset;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience with client handling and F2F meetings considered an asse;t&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;EU citizenship in view of EU work permit restrictions;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call or E-mail for more information.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1482</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 12:06:39 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1482</guid></item><item><title>Linux Infrastructure Engineer - Gaming</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Great opportunity for Linux engineers with passion to grow with gaming environment. The role involves management of the company IT infrastructure including data centres, network (SAN), design, administration and documentation of systems and servers. Successful candidate will form part of the incident response team on 24/7 basic with one week per month roster. The responsibilities will also include research, development and implementation of new technologies and active participation in the decision process. The company offers very attractive remuneration package and young and energetic environment with many company perks. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;4 years of experience in managing infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Being familiar with below technologies: Ubuntu Linux, Nginx, MySQL, PHP, Puppet, Chef, Salt, Jira, Confluence, Zabbix, Nagios, Pingdom, NewRelic&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience with Network Security: Firewalls, Access Control, NAT, VPN&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge of vSphere, HP servers and database management&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous gaming experience will be considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:tech@castilleresources.com"&gt;tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1533</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 12:01:08 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1533</guid></item><item><title>Java Developer - Payments</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A company providing Payment&amp;nbsp;Platform&amp;nbsp;solutions is hiring 2 Java developers to join their team. With an exciting portfolio of clients, the person joining them will be exposed to a vast range of technologies.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Duties:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Development using Java&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working on designs and developing the Payment Platform&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sharing ideas to improve the functionality of the system&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Implementation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working in a team&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;2/3years experience in Java development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience with Spring framework, Spring Web / MVC and Spring Data (SQL)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience using Junit as a testing tool&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience using MySQL for Database&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Frontend development skills - HTML, CSS, Javascript, Angular, JQuery&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidates contact Clare on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1531</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:50:37 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1531</guid></item><item><title>IT Manager/Team Lead - Gaming</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you ready to enter the world of Gaming industry? We have excellent opportunity for senior candidates who would like to take a challenge and become internal IT Manager/ Team Lead with large gaming operator and white label solution provider in Malta. We are looking for skilled and passionate individuals who would like to lead, coach and mentor a growing team of IT, oversee and provide technical support to the company. &amp;nbsp;Successful candidate will also be required to manage the company office IT infrastructure, including networks, servers, PC&amp;rsquo;s and operating systems. Apart from managerial duties the role will also involve hands on duties like: installation, upgrades, configuration, maintenance, troubleshooting and maintenance of IT systems. The Client offers competitive remuneration package and vibrant and dynamic work environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;4 years of experience in managing, operating and maintaining IT infrastructure&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Understanding of ITIL, network management and practices and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience managing and leading the IT team, ideally in gaming environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge in Windows Networking, Active Directory, Office365, Exchange, VOIP Telephony.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="mailto:tech@castilleresources.com"&gt;tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1532</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:47:42 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1532</guid></item><item><title>UX Designer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;UX Designer&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;A technology solutions company is looking for a UX Designer responsible for making the online platforms and games as the most user centric in the industry. This would include the branding experience, its content look and feel, navigation, features and functionality.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Define and plan the strategy for A/B Testing&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Translate research finding into design recommendations&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Coordinate and manage any external partners or service provider in relation to UI/UX&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Establish and promote design guidelines, best practices and standards&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Create conceptual prototypes, mock-ups, behavioural specifications and personas&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Direct the visual appearance of new features and enhancements on software &amp;nbsp; application&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Design elegant solutions to complex workflows&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Organise and facilitate handover activities to the development team&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Understanding and assisting with formulating the client&amp;rsquo;s requirements.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Ideal Candidate:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Time Management Skills is important for Multi-tasking between various different product requests&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Excellent verbal and written communication skills in English&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Leadership skills&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Minimum of 3 years of UX design experience&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Expertise in UX software such as InVision, UXPin, Balsamiq, Quartz Composer&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Extensive experience in using UX design best practices to design solutions, and a deep understanding of mobile-first and responsive design.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Knowledge of Agile development processes&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Prior experience in the iGaming industry is desirable&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Travel and work within an international context&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;For more information, get in touch with Veronique on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/font&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1493</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:40:13 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1493</guid></item><item><title>Test Automation Engineer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will work closely with QA Analysts and product decision makers to become part of a strong team with a great team spirit.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The main tasks include:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Define Automation strategy&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Design, enhance, build, test, and deploy test automation solutions and frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Perform automation and manual tests on existing platforms&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Understand new features and provide estimates for implementing the necessary automated tests&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Create detailed, comprehensive and well-structured test plans and test cases&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Form part of the Agile team and be involved throughout the development cycle&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reviewing product requirements and functional specifications documents to do an impact analysis, estimate QA effort, plan the required test plans&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting in the implementation of QA standards and continual QA improvement activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills &amp;amp; Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Relevant qualification in IT&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;ISTQB certification or experience in manual testing will be considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience designing and developing test automation solutions and frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge in programming and automation testing of web applications;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SQL;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience using code repositories;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience using build automation tools;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience using continuous integration tools;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience with high availability and high throughput systems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested, kindly contact Veronique on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1385</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:39:55 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1385</guid></item><item><title>MS Dynamics AX Consultant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our client, an international business and IT solutions company, is seeking a Microsoft Dynamics AX Consultant to join their expanding team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working closely with the Technical Architect and project team, the successful candidate will be required to design new functionalities and modules, manage hands-on configuration assignments and successfully lead the implementation of Dynamics AX solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;ERP Functional Consultant experience and knowledge of all modules&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Dynamics AX working knowledge within&amp;nbsp;Finance, Inventory and Trade&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sales presentation skills and excellent communications&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Analytical and accurate&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good level of spoken and written&amp;nbsp;English&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowledge of Manufacturing and Warehousing will be considered an asset, and a competitive salary package is being offered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position please apply online or send your CV for the attention of Veronique&amp;nbsp;to tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1381</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:39:47 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1381</guid></item><item><title>Project Management Coordinator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a candidate who will manage end to end delivery of strategic programmes and projects&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Accountabilities / Key Activities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Develop, lead and manage the delivery of Programmes/Projects. Develop, build and maintain strong relationships both internally and externally in order to achieve PMO objectives.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Manage the programme of functional work streams- Produce management reports through relevant tools to provide up to date information on projects requested/in progress.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Prepare progress reports for the sponsor, steering group and all other involved parties&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Stakeholder and work stream management to ensure successful end to end delivery of programmes/projects as per agreed scope, timelines and budget.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Manage requests originating from the organisation, whilst ensuring that these are aligned with the organisation&amp;rsquo;s strategy and priorities&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Prioritisation of activities requested by the business stakeholders to maximise the use of available resources&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Promote effective cross-functional teamwork throughout the delivery lifecycle Understands and can apply project methodology principles to their work to achieve a successful project outcome.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Seeks opportunities to develop own skills and knowledge in order to progress within the project management area.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills required:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Business Management, Electrical Engineering or IT&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Industry experience in IT Enterprise programmes with a proven track record in the successful delivery of Programmes and/or Projects&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Talent to engage with stakeholders, develop relationships and communicate results&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proven influencing and negotiating skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Has strong communication and presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to manage own workload and on own initiative&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitor and manage project costs under the assistance of then project leader&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Accredited Project/Programme Management qualification (such as PRINCE2)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Interested email Veronique on tech@castilleresources.com.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1368</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:39:42 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1368</guid></item><item><title>Java Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a Java developer?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking for your next step?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client is looking for a talented individual who is able to work on various exciting upcoming projects and work alongside a professional team of developers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Java Development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Understand software design patterns,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to come up with solutions to complex problems,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working in an agile environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Have experience in SW Testing.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Team work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Technical tools:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Spring framework&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;SQL&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Version control&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Unix utilities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidate contact Veronique&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1365</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:39:36 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1365</guid></item><item><title>Development Manager - Dynamics CRM</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This is a unique and exciting position where, after initially proving him/herself, the candidate will be given the opportunity to build, maintain and be responsible for the Dynamics CRM team. He/she will report directly to the company CTO.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal .NET Solution Developer will have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Degree in Computer Science or equivalent;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Intensive hands-on functional and technical experience working in Microsoft Dynamics CRM (online and on-prem);&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent knowledge of C#, .NET development,&amp;nbsp;SQL Server;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Familiarity with the Azure Platform, Parature, Dynamics Marketing;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial mentality&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Team building and management skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills in English&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Willingness to work in an international environment and with occasional&amp;nbsp;travel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will benefit from:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Flexible working conditions&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;An attractive remuneration package based on qualifications and work experience which will be variable depending on the goals achieved&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A variety of extras over and above the remuneration package which include Health Insurance, Life Insurance &amp;amp; Travel Insurance&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A unique opportunity to apply in practice and put his/her entrepreneurial skills to the test&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An attractive package is being offered to the selected candidate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please contact Veronique on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1062</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:39:29 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1062</guid></item><item><title>QA Analyst</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Large and well established software house in Malta is currently looking for Quality Assurance Analyst to join their QA Assurance Team. The role of QA Executive will mainly involve ensuring that the quality of service levels of the company platform are constantly maintained. Chosen Candidate will be making sure that all aspects of the software are properly tested and all the QA process of the company product development lifecycle is followed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reviewing product requirements and functional specifications documents to do an impact analysis, estimate QA effort, plan the required test plans.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintaining the defect log under control at all times&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Designing, maintaining and executing test plans and test cases.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Investigating and replicating reported defects.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Performing various kinds of testing: performance testing, functional testing, unit testing, user interface testing, integration testing, security testing, compatibility testing, regression testing etc.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting in the implementation of QA standards and continual QA improvement activities&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Skills:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sharp analytical skills in searching for and in identifying bugs&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Have an eye for detail&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A background of .NET. Ability to understand .NET code. Coding skills are not required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SQL scripting &amp;ndash; to be able to do database level testing&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A good understanding of software development life cycle&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills &amp;ndash; with ability to communicate at a technical level with developers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to work independently with minimal supervision&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Commitment to reach QA deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to always followup on things&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Veronique on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/960</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:38:16 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/960</guid></item><item><title>Backend Developer .net</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the CTO, the developer will work together with the existing development team to develop and maintain the systems including our live client sites. The Developer will also take part in the entire development life cycle as defined in Scrum methodology.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Functions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 4 years working experience, 3 of which in a .Net development environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure the right development of a work package&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Develop and integrate components into a larger product&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Respect coding best practices, including unit testing&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Respect delivery due date&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Document and comment the code&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Develop functional knowledge on casino, sports-bets, poker, payments, and other industry related products&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Break down and estimate development issues (features, improvements and defects)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Independently take issues from Sprint backlog&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Deploy releases to test and staging environments&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist operations team during deployment to production environment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Qualifications and Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience with agile methods (Scrum, XP)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience of business critical web development in a 24/7 business&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in online gaming industry - preferred&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience from successful team collaboration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills/Competencies Required&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of C#&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of SQL&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of Visual Studio Tools&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge in use of webservices&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in MVC&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SVN would be preferable&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, both written and oral&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to document work and business requirements&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good analytical skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Driven and results-oriented&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Initiative&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Self going&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Team Player with good social skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Easy to adapt and flexible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Desirable Skills&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in MySQL&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of IIS setup and configuration&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1310</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:31:51 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1310</guid></item><item><title>Senior Information Security Engineer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our client is looking for an individual to join there Information Security team.&lt;br /&gt;
The individual must be a highly talented and motivated information security engineer. This is a role reporting directly to the CTSO, within the organisation&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities: &lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
To drive and support the maintenance and improvement of security standards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Performing audits, penetration testing and vulnerability scanning activities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Liaise with Internal and External auditors to carry out audits and identify areas of improvement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Perform day to day security vetting on user access requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Implement and manage ways to regularly scan for, find and fix security problems/vulnerabilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Build internal tools that detect and respond to security issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Make intelligent decisions around prioritization of efforts based on risk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Perform security assessments of anything from a physical security system to a complex web application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Efficiently manage multiple simultaneous projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Audit systems to ensure and maintain PCI DSS compliance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Develop and maintain security documentation, including policies and other project deliverables&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Assisting in the information security awareness, training, and educational activities for all company personnel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Technical / Professional Expertise:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s or Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in the relevant technical field and/or specialised security certification&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Information Security relevant certifications (e.g. CCNA Security, Security+, CISSP)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience working with multiple operating systems, with good level knowledge of Linux, UNIX and Windows.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Strong background in host, network and application security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Advanced knowledge of TCP/IP networking, and network services such as DNS, SMTP, DHCP, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Experience working with firewalls and intrusion detection systems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Expertise with a scripting language to develop own tools as required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Extensive knowledge of internet security issues and the threat landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Excellent written and oral communication skills.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;middot;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;Knowledge in project management, data mining and statistics would be considered an asset&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidate contact Clare&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1417</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:31:18 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1417</guid></item><item><title>Information Security Specialist</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our client, a leading International Advisory Firm, is seeking specialist professionals experienced in Information Security to work within their practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will hold tertiary qualifications in IT or Business, with ambitions to hold a Chief Information Security Officer role and with the ability to deliver those relevant skills to leading organisations within Business and Government sectors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Such clients require assistance within the areas of information and business risks, independent assessments of internal controls, IT governance and cyber security.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assignments generally cover areas including but not limited to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;vulnerability assessments&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;information security audits&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;business continuity planning&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;penetration testing&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;investigations and technology forensics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be qualified as Certified Information System Security Professionals (CISSP), Certified Information System Auditors (CISA), Certified Ethical Hackers (CEH), or be planning to qualify for such certification or similar. A strong enthusiasm for Information Security and IT, and continuous development of related skills is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;rsquo; relevant, practical work experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Solid knowledge of international security standards and legislation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent presentation and report writing skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Creative and successful approach to problem solving, balancing measures to mitigate risks with the respective costs&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;High standard of ethical behaviour and professionalism&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to build and develop strong relationships&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should this role be of interest and you would like to be considered, please contact Clare&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1416</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:30:52 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1416</guid></item><item><title>DB2</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A large banking client is looking to recruit a DB2 to join their growing&amp;nbsp;team.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Creating database, configure db for archival logging, configure db parameters&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Database upgrade/migration (applying fix pack and Version upgrade)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;DB2 Database Security Model (Authentication, Authority)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;DB monitoring (Database Snapshot and event monitor)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Database backup/restore&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Review and Execute DDL, review DB2 diaglogs, notification logs&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Resolve locks and deadlocks&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Analyse and recommend performance enhancements in database design, SQL queries and DB setup&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintain and enhance database availability, manage large number of connections/users&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Project and task reporting&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Communication with management, key-users, team members and suppliers&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Expected skills and experience:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;4+ years of experience with DB2 DBA (Linux, Unix and Windows)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A solid knowledge of DB2 Database architecture (Process, memory and storage architecture) and DB2 Database fundamentals (Threads/process, Instance, table spaces, Containers, SMS, DMS, buffer pools)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Worked with DB2 V9 or higher&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Hands on with management/monitoring tools available for DB2&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good in root cause analysis of any outage from DB2 logs&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sound knowledge on Database character sets (UTF8 and Non-UTF8 Database)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Hands on exposure on Data movement tools (db2move, export, import etc.) and on Linux, Unix Platform and comfortable in Linux/Unix basic commands&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Clare&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1307</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:30:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1307</guid></item><item><title>CRM Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our client, an established Gaming company, is seeking to recruit a CRM Developer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The successful candidate will be responsible for building all CRM templates along with the execution and delivery, both automated and&amp;nbsp;real-time, of all related CRM activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With experience in delivering successful training the CRM Developer will become the tool expert within the department, continuously&amp;nbsp;ensuring that knowledge cascades to the team and all required tool resources are used to their full capability.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Creating impeccable landing pages and email templates with the latest technologies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Play an active part in the various states of campaign design and execution&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Stay up to date with all department tools, and implement the coaching, training and development of the Content/CRM team&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure ongoing improvements in the operational process, so that efficiencies increase along with department outplut quality&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Support complex campaigns, providing insights and guidance that drive proper campaign execution&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Demonstrate innovative approaches and provide constant input to the team to ensure that campaigns run effectively and using the&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;latest technology&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Become the established and key point of contact relating to all relevant technical areas&lt;br /&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years&amp;rsquo; experience in a similar CRM or email development role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in CSS3 / HTML / HTML5 / Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to build attractive and responsive landing pages&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills with fluency in English, both written and oral&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working knowledge of CMS tools (such as Optimove, WordPress) various CRM, and email marketing&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent attention to detail and strives for quality and consistency&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience with MYSQL and PHP, along with working knowledge of Photoshop would be considered a plus&lt;br /&gt;
	&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should this role be of interest and you would like to be considered, please contact Clare&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1418</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:30:37 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1418</guid></item><item><title>Frontend Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;This Frontend Developer position is with a large Software House who service the Gaming sector.&lt;br /&gt;
You will report&amp;nbsp;to the CTO and will&amp;nbsp;work together with the existing development team to develop and maintain the systems including our live client sites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Functions&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 2&amp;nbsp;years working experience in Development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure the right development of a work package&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Optimize application for maximum speed and scalability&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assure that all user input is validated before submitting to back-end&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills/Competencies Required&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;PHP, HTML, Javascript&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent English, both written and oral&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Initiative&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Self going&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Team Player with good social skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Positive attitude&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Easy to adapt and flexible&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidates to contact Clare on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1436</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:30:30 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1436</guid></item><item><title>.Net Back-End Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Too many Backend Developer roles to choose from?&lt;br /&gt;
Looking for a company who provides cutting edge technology?&lt;br /&gt;
Attractive remuneration package whilst working in a dynamic, fun environment&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apply Now!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Joining this dynamic team, you will be involved in all aspects of software development from making sure that the architecture and design is as good as we can make it.&lt;br /&gt;
To writing code and unit tests and manage our SQL and NoSQL data models. You will work both with designing and implementing new features as well as analyzing the system and improve architecture and technical excellence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
- Development experience&lt;br /&gt;
- Able to work in a large team&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Skills:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;C#, .Net&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Visual Studio&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;WCF&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Unit test and mocking frameworks&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;MS SQL&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;NoSQL databases&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;NServiceBus&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;AppDynamics&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;TeamCity&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Sonar with SQALE&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Octopus Deploy&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;TDD&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;bull;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Pair Programming&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidate contact Clare on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1283</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:30:25 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1283</guid></item><item><title>Software Developer Networking</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a software developer with a flair for networking?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Opportunity for both Junior and Senior Developers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Main Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible to design and Implement Software Provisioning and Support Tools to provide a view of the status of the network infrastructure;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Candidate will be designing, monitoring and executing projects that are Design, Monitor and execute projects envisioned to integrate third party systems with various network elements/systems.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Lead acceptance testing, modifications or necessary technical work configurations in relation to software releases.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Uphold the infrastructure utilised to host and deliver the services;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Work as a team with other sections within the technical Networks department as required.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be responsible to provide training to other members of staff in other departments;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Candidate might be required to provide support duties outside office hours&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal Candidate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in Spring Framework&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in J2EE, JPA, XML, Web-services (JAX-WS);&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience on DBMS including Oracle, Sybase and MySql;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge on object oriented programming and design patterns;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge BRMS and BPMS such as Drools and JBPM will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of HTML, CSS, Javascript &amp;amp; AJAX;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent troubleshooting and logical skills;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills both verbal and written together with personal and interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Organisational and multitasking skills &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Veronique on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1530</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 14:36:07 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1530</guid></item><item><title>IT System Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will provide IT support services to the internal&lt;br /&gt;
customer base, ensuring that work is successfully prioritized and completed in accordance with the&amp;nbsp;business expectations. This role involves working closely with the IT Operations team, being at the&amp;nbsp;forefront of resolving all IT related issues either by phone, email or internal ticketing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Forming part of IT support Team and provide IT support services to th internal customers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working closely with operations team and solving IT related issues via phone, email or internal ticketing&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The role will involve troubleshooting users issues using tools including remote administration of company hardware&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Conducting systems backups and data recovery&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist with emergency support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year experience in the similar role with hands on experience&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Windows Operating systems, including Active Directory and Group Policy maintenance&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Networking and TCP/IP&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;User Administration&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Basic knowledge of Linux server administration&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;VMware vCentre management&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Citrix XenApp&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;PABX and physical access control administration&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working on shift basic (08.00 AM &amp;ndash; 20.00 PM)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Flexible in providing occasional on-call out of hours support (additional remuneration package offered)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good verbal and written command of English language&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1529</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 14:10:33 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1529</guid></item><item><title>Software Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you a Java Developer?&lt;br /&gt;
Working with the latest technologies?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This roles call for highly motivated individuals who are willing to work in a demanding and challenging environment to develop automated solutions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Senior Software Developers and Software Developers would be involved in all stages of the software development life cycle, including requirements definition, design, development, testing and implementation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Selected candidates would be required to write complex test suites and help enforce standards. Senior Software Developers would, in addition, be expected to mentor their junior colleagues and contribute to activities of project management and co-ordination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal candidate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Recognised qualification in IT or a related subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Proficient in Java, have good knowledge of web services and related integration technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Familiar with JEE and related technologies such as JPA/Hibernate, JAX-WS, JMS and Spring (including Spring MVC), and with Web 2.0 technologies and techniques such as AJAX, Javascript frameworks such as JQuery and CSS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested candidates contact Veronique&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1528</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 14:09:04 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1528</guid></item><item><title>Accounts Assistant - Firm</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Candidates should be in the very early stages of ACCA with some experience in Accountancy&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Working with us:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Career development and training - we invest in our people&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Great rewards&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Friendly, sociable, corporate culture&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Growth and expansion of the firm - join us on this journey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The Job will involve the following responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Managing of a client portfolio of companies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Supporting clients on a day to day basis;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparing financial records of the company up to Trial balance stage;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaising with auditors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Part time basis is also considered&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1527</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 11:21:12 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1527</guid></item><item><title>Payroll / Accounts Assistant - Firm</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Working with us:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Career development and training - we invest in our people&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Great rewards&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Friendly, sociable, corporate culture&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Growth and expansion of the firm - join us on this journey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle and prioritize multiple tasks and meet all deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience is considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;O&amp;rsquo;level standard of education and good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the preparation and processing of Payroll&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Review and ensure accuracy of approved timesheets&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Track and deduct payroll deductions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Administration of the electronic timekeeping system&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure valid data transfers to/from payroll service&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure that employee changes are entered correctly and made on a timely basis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Part time basis is also being considered.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1525</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 11:20:37 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1525</guid></item><item><title>Treasury Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Due to company growth a new career opportunity has arisen within the Treasury department of this large Financial Services Investment Company for a Treasury Manager&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The role&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Company operates under a Category 3 licence and seeks a high calibre individual to assist with the running of its Treasury Operation.&amp;nbsp;The selected individual will form part of the company&amp;rsquo;s house view committee and will&amp;nbsp;deal primarily in&amp;nbsp;fixed income securities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;You should:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Possess a Finance related University degree or hold a financial services qualification.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Have a minimum of 3 years experience working in a treasury department that manages fixed income based portfolios.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be able to analyse market information and developments and assess the likely effects of such&amp;nbsp;developments on portfolio positions.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Have experience with Bloomberg workstations&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Have excellent communication skills and be able to work in a dynamic environment.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Plus Points&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Have experience operating&amp;nbsp;as a market maker.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of FX or other&amp;nbsp;instruments.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of advanced Excel / Bloomberg techniques&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salary being offered will depend on experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1524</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 10:01:25 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1524</guid></item><item><title>Compliance Officer &amp; MLRO</title><description>&lt;p&gt;One of the leading providers in financial services is looking for a compliance officer and MLRO. &amp;nbsp;The ideal candidate would be familiar with investment and fund services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Operating within the legal and compliance framework ensuring compliance with all regulatory requirements&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Acting as the Compliance and MLRO&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the local Risk Management framework&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring and reporting on compliance and AML&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Contact with the MFSA and other authorities&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Providing Compliance and AML training to the employees&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;AML and KYC procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal candidate:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preferably prior experience as Compliance Officer and MLRO&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Highly organised and focused&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Professional and committed to deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Stefania at finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1523</link><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 16:02:13 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1523</guid></item><item><title>Marketing Assistant - Financial Services</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A financial services organisation is seeking a Marketing assistant to join their local setup and assist with the execution of marketing plans and conducting research on companies within the sector which the organisation operates in. No previous work experience is required.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Further responsibilities include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintaining the internal client database updated;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of online campaigns and assist with online advertising;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Quarterly newsletter;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal candidate should be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;In possession of a tertiary level of education in Marketing or Communications;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proficient in written and spoken English;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Able to work under pressure and adhere to tight deadlines;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;In possession of an EU citizenship due to work permit restrictions in Malta;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in financial services will be considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested applicants are to e-mail Simon on tech@castilleresources.com for more details.&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1519</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 14:48:26 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1519</guid></item><item><title>HR Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;To be responsible for and oversee the Company&amp;rsquo;s Human Resources requirements reporting directly to the General Manager.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities and tasks:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Planning, directing and coordinating all activities in the HR department working closely with other Company departments as a HR business partner&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Developing immediate and long term HR objectives, strategies, policies and programs in the areas of manpower planning, recruitment, training and development, compensation, benefits, personnel policy and record administration, and employee and labour relations with department managers.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To interpret and advise on employment law, oversee the legislation, analysis, maintenance and communication of records required by government legislation.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Planning and sometimes delivering training &amp;ndash; including inductions for new staff, generating and implementing human resources development programs to ensure that all employees increase their skills and contributions to the company.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Co-ordinating with the Financial Controller all payroll procedures and execution, with the assistance of the Payroll Executive.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Min 3&amp;nbsp;years&amp;#39; working experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A relevant HR&amp;nbsp;qualification&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluent English both written and spoken.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1518</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 12:28:48 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1518</guid></item><item><title>Business Development - Retail</title><description>&lt;p&gt;An international retail company has recently set up office in Malta and are seeking to recruit a Business Developer to join their operations department in Malta. This position will be mostly focused on generating new leads within international distributors and retailers and maintaining existing ones.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal candidate needs to have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in B2B within international distribution;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Fluency in French and English - both oral and written;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication and presentation skills;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;EU citizenship given the position will be based in Malta;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Given the nature of the business, chosen applicant will be required to travel from time to time, depending on business needs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more details, call or e-mail Simon on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1516</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 08:50:41 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1516</guid></item><item><title>Insurance Operations Specialist</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Operations Manger, a leading international insurance company representing top brands worldwide is seeking to employ an Insurance Operations Specialist.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities will be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Deputise in Operations Managers Absence&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Pilot and implement new programmes&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Contribute to optimisation of the productivity of the platform of claims management of the companies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure claim management is compliant with regulations, internal process and policies.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure the quality of service over the claims management&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be ACII qualified&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Similar experience within insurance, preferably multi line&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The ability to travel.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information and detailed job description please contact Nikki on nfarrugia@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1426</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 15:08:37 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1426</guid></item><item><title>QA Automation Tester</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The primary responsibility of the Quality Assurance Team Executive would be to act as a customer representative in QA Activities of new technology products and services.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Duties:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Creating, managing and adhering to test plans and task assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reviewing work progress and making regular recommendations for team, process and solution improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Extracting and reporting status updates and KPIs to the QA Team Lead and Project Managers.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Taking a pro-active and dynamic approach towards problem solving and root cause analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Developing relationships customers and other bodies to ensure pro-active achievement.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To contribute to the delivery of new products / services by leading or assisting in the transition phase of a project as necessary&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To assume an active role in solution design, from a quality perspective&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To gather and manage all the necessary documentation related to quality assurance such as test results and quality criteria documents&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To vet and review design documentation submitted by product architect&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;
	The ideal candidate will have:&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A degree or an equivalent certification in Computer Science or a related field;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years&amp;rsquo; experience in a software testing or a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Exposure to modern testing methodologies and testing automation tools (including scripting).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent troubleshooting skills to analyse root cause complex issues;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in building test plans and related tools such as MS Project;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of performance and scalability test approaches;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in software development, Oracle, and PL/SQL;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent time management, organization and prioritization skills;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to read, analyse, and interpret technical reports.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of test tools such as JIRA, SOAPUI, JMeter, Putty etc. will be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in system administration or administration of test tools will be considered an asset;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;ISTQB certification will be considered an asset.&lt;br /&gt;
	&lt;br /&gt;
	Interested candidates contact Clare on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1511</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 14:05:11 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1511</guid></item><item><title>Junior Accountant - Private Firm</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;font face="Arial, Helvetica, sans-serif"&gt;We are seeking to grow our finance team and require the services of a junior accountant.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our client portfolio includes a mixture of companies operating in the local business as well as companies operating internationally including companies providing Investment Services, Shipping and Yacht operators, Holding companies and Remote Gaming Operators.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Candidates should be either fully qualified or partially qualified having completed all the F modules with 2 &amp;ndash; 3 &amp;nbsp;years&amp;rsquo; work experience.&amp;nbsp; Job will involve the following responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Managing of a client portfolio of companies mainly involved in international business activities;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Supporting clients on a day to day basis;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparing financial records of the company up to Trial balance stage;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaising with auditors.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1497</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 13:46:48 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1497</guid></item><item><title>Financial Forecasting Modeller</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Directly reporting to the Head of Planning and Transformation, the chosen candidate will form part of the Bank&amp;rsquo;s capital Planning Team and will work closely with the Risk, Treasury and Finance teams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In this role the candidate will execute implementation of models, stress tests, processes and governance for ICAAP, SREP, Recovery Plan, Budget, Forecasts and Business Plans. The selected candidate will be responsible for reporting findings and formulating recommendations to senior management teams and governance committees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Duties and responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Managing financial models and using robust quantitative analyses to assess the adequacy of Bank&amp;rsquo;s position&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaising with departments across the Bank to develop the Bank&amp;rsquo;s business plan, forecasts and budget projections&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Implementing process improvements on existing core team processes&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Applying superior analytical skills to drive key analytics for Senior Management&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Developing subject matter expertise in current and evolving regulations (e.g. LCR, NSFR, BASEL, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaising with teams across the company including Credit Risk Management, Treasury Management to project metrics under specific scenarios&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Coordinating the development, maintenance and enhancement of econometric expertise and stress testing methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Developing best practice modelling techniques, ensuring comprehensive documentation and maintaining best of class model monitoring and outcome analysis&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Contributing to the efforts of the model build process through the various approval committees throughout the Bank such as Asset Liability committee, Board, etc.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required knowledge, skills and experience:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Maths, Statistics, Physics, Engineering or Finance&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Microsoft Excel&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in programming would be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Finance, Banking or Financial Modelling experience would be considered an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position apply online or send your CV for the attention of Mark&amp;nbsp;to finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1513</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 12:36:33 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1513</guid></item><item><title>System Specialist - Cloud</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Are you System Administrator with passion for learning cloud systems? He have fantastic&amp;nbsp;opportunity for you with company which can give you great exposure to new technologies and allow you to work in multinational environment. &amp;nbsp;The company offers competitive&amp;nbsp;remuneration package with end of the year bonus based of performance and flexi working hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;2 years of experience in similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Microsoft IIS&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong knowledge of Windows Server technologies, including virtualisation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Microsoft SQL Server&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to install, configure, monitor and tweak networks and data center equipment (such as UPSs, load balancers)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong understanding of IT security&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A passion for virtualisation and private/public cloud services&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Considered as an asset:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Understanding of HTML, CSS, Microsoft .NET, C#, PHP or scripting&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Understanding of agile software development methodologies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in managing cloud hosting environments such as Microsoft Azure&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SQL configuration, data retrieval and manipulation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on &lt;a href="mailto:tech@castilleresources.com"&gt;tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1400</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:33:48 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1400</guid></item><item><title>Junior NOC Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;We have a perfect opportunity for Junior Candidates which would like to develop their skills in networking and form part of NOC team. Selected candidate will be reporting to NOC &amp;amp; technical helpdesk team lead and assist with day-to-day tasks, including documentation, training, procedural development and reporting. This position is shift-based and require replacement of NOC Technicians in order to ensure smooth 24x7 monitoring of all platforms. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ideally in possession if an ICT/Engineering/Electronics/Telecommunications related qualification&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in an ICT/Telecoms/Networking/Business related field.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;MCAST Advanced Diploma in IT (Computer Systems and Networks or End User Support).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;NCC Diploma in Computing (MQF Level 5).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 1 year experience working in a similar role or in a technical support function.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good computer skills, especially in the use of MS Excel, Word and Visio.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1411</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:33:02 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1411</guid></item><item><title>Junior BI Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;The ideal opportunity&amp;nbsp;for developers who wish to switch their career to BI or for new graduates who wish to join established BI team and make BI as their career.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Form part of existing BI team which is responsible for the design, development and implementation of BI solution&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Computer Science or Statistics&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to multitask and take initiative with an inclination towards statistics and data manipulation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SQL and Windows Server&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of .NET with ability to develop in VB.net or C#.net is considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1304</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:32:53 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1304</guid></item><item><title>BI Developer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Write relational and multidimensional queries, whilst creating and deploying reports.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible for aggregating large sets of data from heterogeneous sources into a data warehouse that is used extensively across the organization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in computer science or related degree&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Al least 2 years of experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong SQL, Microsoft SQL Server Reporting knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Analysis and Integration Services&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Basic experience of SQL server&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of at least one data visualization tool&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1165</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:32:48 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1165</guid></item><item><title>Core Networks Engineer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Well established company is seeking to employ Engineers in various sectors of its Core Networks Department. The chosen Candidate will be given an exciting opportunity to develop their career in a challenging, specialized and constantly changing environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Researching, recommending technical solutions and implementing standards&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reporting generation and data analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring and analyzing technical reports.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Troubleshooting&amp;nbsp;of problems and providing timely corrective action.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Delivering training.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A Degree in a telecommunications related field or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Two years&amp;rsquo; experience working in a telecommunications (or related) environment.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;CCNA/CCNP.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in IP networking.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Possess a valid driving license.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Considered as an asset:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Linux/Unix including Perl/BASH scripting, SS7/SIP, MySQL, network security and TV technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Windows and Unix Operating Systems.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be conversant with TCP/IP technologies.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on &lt;a href="mailto:tech@castilleresources.com"&gt;tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1161</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:32:43 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1161</guid></item><item><title>System Specialist Engineer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our Client is looking to recruit a degree level candidate to join their engineering department. The chosen candidate will be reporting to Core Networks Operations Manager and will be learning telecoms signaling, company products and services. The Client is providing six months training where the candidate can get familiar with the applications, company portfolio and assist in operational and maintenance duties. The duties will also include monitoring and control, execution of installation, configuration of equipment, trouble shooting and maintenance. The career progression will involve providing advice on all aspects related to the Voice Network including how to maximize the use of the assets, how to minimize costs and how to improve operational procedures and methods as well as design, project management and implementation of technical solutions related to voice network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;An Engineering/IT Degree (Bachelor or Master)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Very good all-round Internet related technical skills.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Very good problem diagnosis and solving skills;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good team work and coordination skills.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Leadership, negotiation and communication skills.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Considered as an asset:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;System Administration skills on Linux.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Database Administration skills.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Networking skills, i.e. CCNA&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Programming skills, especially in scripting languages like Perl, Python, Ruby, JAVA.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Any experience in Telecom&amp;rsquo;s.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A valid driving license&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1410</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:32:35 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1410</guid></item><item><title>Technical Operations Engineer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;If you are skilled and motivated individual looking to join production engineer group we have great opportunity for you in the online gaming company. As technical operations engineer you will be required to demonstrate excellent system management, diagnostic and support skills in all of infrastructure. The ideal candidate must be conversant in networking, server and storage technologies and be in possession of well understanding of n-tier architectures. The main duties will include: technical escalation point for the 24x7 NOC team, including on-call basis, maintaining, upgrading,&amp;nbsp;optimizing&amp;nbsp;and ensuring maximum uptime of live, pre-production and dev environments and overseeing the preparation of environments for the testing software releases, participate in the planning, scheduling and execution of said releases.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Knowledge and experience in any of the below areas would be beneficial:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A proven track record in IT engineering&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Linux server administration experience (RedHat)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Container technologies (Docker)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Configuration management and automation tools (Puppet, Ansible)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Source control systems (GIT)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Database administration experience (RDBMS, NoSQL)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Messaging technologies (ActiveMQ)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Web Servers Experience (Apache, Nginx)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Application containers (Jboss)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Core Services - NTP, proxy, mail, DNS&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to document technical concepts/procedures&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Relevant understanding of IT security&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Public/Private Cloud experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Scripting languages&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Object-oriented languages&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Big Data technologies (Splunk)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1461</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:32:31 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1461</guid></item><item><title>Systems Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Well established company developing intelligent online gaming platforms is looking for System Administrator to join their growing team. The company gives the Employees space to thrive build and contribute across a number of products.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Windows Server 2008 R2, 2012 and 2012 R2 &amp;ndash; maintenance, installation and configuration of the server&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of CISCO, Barracuda&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;VoIP installation and maintenance (3CX) with DDI&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Exchange&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;MySQL and MySQL Enterprise Setup with Replication, Failover Clustering, Administration, Monitoring and Security&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience as a user of CRM systems will be considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring of Enterprise Infrastructure with Nagios, Nagvis, PNP for Nagios and New Relic&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Server Room Design and Implementation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;UPS and Generators Setup and Monitoring (APC)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Linux Server knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;VOIP Systems (3CX)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintenance of CCTV and Access Control Installation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;SAN installation and configuration, ISCSI Storage, HP StoreVirtual, IBM StorWize&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Backup systems (Veeam Backup and Altaro)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintenance, troubleshooting and set up of hardware&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Active Directory Design, Setup and Maintenance with Failover&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Setup and Configurations of Windows Server 2008 R2 - 2012 R2 including HyperV Core&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;VMware ESXi and vSphere Design, Setup and Configuration&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Usage of Ticketing Systems&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of Web Development including CSS, FTP and programmes such as WordPress or Drupal would considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in the roll-out of new software systems including evaluation as well as implementation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree or good competency in relevant area&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A minimum of 3 years&amp;rsquo; experience in a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of flow-charts and similar Software Engineering frameworks&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Prior experience in the iGaming industry is considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1047</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 11:32:24 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1047</guid></item><item><title>Accountant - Financial Services</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Description and Responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reporting to the Finance Director, in this role, you will be responsible for the accounting and tax compliance of a portfolio of client companies.This is a new role and offers good prospects for&amp;nbsp;career progression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your duties will include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Updating of financial records&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of Management Accounts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of VAT Returns&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of Tax Returns&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaising with the auditors for the audit of Financial Statements.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Minimum Qualification requirements&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will be ACCA qualified or in the final stages of ACCA with minimum of 3 years accounting experience in a similar environment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will have excellent organization and communication skills, be pro-active, be willing to contribute ideas to improve the systems and procedures, be able to work under pressure and adhere to deadlines.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested kindly apply online or else contact Andre by email on finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1506</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 14:32:04 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1506</guid></item><item><title>IT Administrator</title><description>&lt;p&gt;If you are 1&lt;sup&gt;st&lt;/sup&gt; and 2&lt;sup&gt;nd&lt;/sup&gt; line support IT Administrator we have exciting opportunity for you with very well established company in Malta. Main duties will include carrying out operational activities, resolving incidents, assisting with installations, providing support of MS Windows Server, Oracle database and Linux servers. Successful candidate will be required to visit customers on site and perform investigations and incident resolution and maintenance of IT equipment and peripherals and adhere to warranty requirements. The candidate will be required to demonstrate a flexible approach to location and working hours.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Key Requirements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Administration, installing and configuration of Windows/Linux Systems&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of SQL language&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Understanding of LAN/WAN configuration and TCP/IP protocol&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in troubleshooting&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication in English&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Clean driving licence&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1504</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 12:25:14 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1504</guid></item><item><title>Payroll Administrator - Retail</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Payroll Administrator&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are a well-established group primarily operating within the retail industry and we currently in the process of seeking to employ a Payroll Administrator&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Required Qualifications:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Confidentiality is of utmost importance and must exercise extreme discretion&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to handle and prioritize multiple tasks and meet all deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience is considered as an asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;O&amp;rsquo;level standard of education and good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Description:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible for the preparation and processing of Payroll&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Review and ensure accuracy of approved timesheets&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Track and deduct payroll deductions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Coordinate between various departments to ensure proper flow and maintenance of employee data&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Administration of the electronic timekeeping system&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure valid data transfers to/from payroll service&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Establish/maintain employee records&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure that employee changes are entered correctly and made on a timely basis&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Review changes for proper authorization and compliance with local regulations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1472</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 11:56:45 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1472</guid></item><item><title>Billing System Enginner</title><description>&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintenance,&amp;nbsp;implementation operations and monitoring of hardware and OS&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Development, technical advice and implementation of new services in a timely manner as required by the Company.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Manage the databases adequately using the necessary tools as required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible to maintain and keep backups and use them for disaster recovery purposes as may be necessary, including procedure to update secondary machines and make them available as production in a disaster situation&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Manage communication with suppliers for any escalation of issues required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Keep up to date with the required technology in order to provide adequate technical advice as necessary (Operating Systems, Databases and hardware)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responsible to communicate, co-ordinate and implement routine updates/patches/new features with suppliers&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Propose new better ways of working for improving the system/existing processes as required&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ideal Candidate will have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;I.T. related professional degree or equivalent professional experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Billing Systems (considered an asset)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience using Linux and Windows operating systems&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of Unix shell scripting&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience working with SQL queries and development of PL/SQL applications&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Administration of Oracle Databases. Hands on experience in application servers (e.g. Apache Tomcat and Microsoft IIS, Servers) &amp;nbsp;(considered an asset)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Minimum basic knowledge of IP protocols&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ability to plan work accurately whilst maintaining a certain degree of flexibility in order to deliver on Market requirements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information contact Kamilla&amp;nbsp;on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1502</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:07:55 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1502</guid></item><item><title>Head of Accounts</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Seeking a Head of Accounts&amp;nbsp;to join one of Malta&amp;#39;s most prestigious Corporate Services Provider.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;The successful candidate must&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;come &amp;nbsp;with the right mindset to organising and running a commercially and technically sound department.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities will be to:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Plan and manage work streams&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Supervise the team ( circa 12 persons)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Oversea work and sign off accounts&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Manage training plans and program&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Head of accounts is expected to technically competent and up to date with IAS and IFRS &amp;nbsp;and have a good knowledge of Tax Accounting&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications required:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Must be a fully qualified Accountant&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Have the ability&amp;nbsp;to train junior staff,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Meet and maintain the high standards offered by said Client&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information, please contact Nikki on finance@castilleresources.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1246</link><category>Executive</category><pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 08:24:39 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1246</guid></item><item><title>Banking Advisory Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our client is a leading international firm with offices around the world. They are seeking to strengthen their Banking Advisory due to the growth for this line of service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is an exciting new opportunity and would be a great career move for the right person.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills and Experience Required:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;exceptional analytical and communication skills (oral and written) with a strong attention for detail&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;ability to gather, verify and analyse information, formulate views and develop and communicate well-rounded conclusions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;client focus, with ability to work quickly and establish effective working relationships&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;logical and methodical approach to problem solving&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;project management and organisational skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;ability to work in a fluid dynamic environment where change is the order of the day&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The selected candidate will be responsible for:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;effectively overseeing and executing engagements including interacting with clients at appropriate levels, preparing financial models, analyzing financial information, and preparation of deliverables including reports, presentations and discussions with the client&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;training and mentoring junior team members&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;actively continuing personal development and learning&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;understanding the capabilities of the firm and looking for opportunities to sell additional services to our clients.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Qualifications Required&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Candidates should have a professional qualification (Degree in Accountancy, Banking, Finance, or Economics, ACCA, ACA, CFA, FRM or equivalent) and have a minimum of five years&amp;#39; experience in a professional environment.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Candidates having banking regulatory and advisory experience will be given preference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why should you join this company ?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Opportunities for travel on international assignments from time to time&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Attractive salary remuneration&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Top class training and support&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Long term growth opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Working with leading local and international clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Job security and stability&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1449</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 22:45:52 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1449</guid></item><item><title>Senior Audit Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;Salary and benefits will range depending on the candidate&amp;#39;s experience. skills, qualifications and current earnings. This is an excellent opportunity for someone seeking to make the next step in their career.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;This role requires an individual with:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;A proven career within the audit practice, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;Having a minimum of&amp;nbsp;7 years audit experience,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;With a deep understanding of IFRS and having held an equivalent position within an audit firm.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;Candidates must be qualified accountants and are required to have broad audit experience on a variety of clients&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;Candidates are expected to have strong project management skills&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;span style="font-family:arial; font-size:13.1999998092651px"&gt;Must have previous experience in managing a varied portfolio of clients and will be reporting directly to an audit director.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/144</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 22:45:41 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/144</guid></item><item><title>Quality Assurance Executive</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Currently looking for&amp;nbsp;a&amp;nbsp;Quality Assurance Team Executive:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Responsibilities include:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Creating and&amp;nbsp;managing test plans together with&amp;nbsp;task assignments.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reviewing work progress and making regular recommendations for team, process and solution improvements.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Extracting and reporting status updates to the QA Team Lead&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Problem solving and root cause analysis.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring that products / services are quality tested, meet the agreed functional / non-functional specifications and to ensure that the delivered product is fit for purpose.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Contributing&amp;nbsp;to the delivery of new products / services&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Managing &amp;nbsp;&amp;ldquo;post-launch project review&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Regular adherence with QA Policies and Procedures&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The ideal candidate will have:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A degree or an equivalent certification in Computer Science or a related field;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;At least 2 years&amp;rsquo; experience in a software testing or a similar role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Exposure to modern testing methodologies and testing automation tools (including scripting).&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent troubleshooting skills to analyse root cause complex issues;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in building test plans and related tools such as MS Project;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of performance and scalability test approaches;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge in software development, Oracle, and PL/SQL;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of test tools such as JIRA and&amp;nbsp;SOAPUI&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should you be interested, get in touch for more information.Email Veronique on tech@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1480</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 13:49:11 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1480</guid></item><item><title>Accounting Manager - Insurance</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A leading insurance company is seeking to employ an Accounts Manager to join their team of professionals, servicing international clients. This role will give great exposure to the chosen candidate and will involve building and maintaining relationships with clients long term.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Why should you join this company?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Continuous exposure to clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;International client exposure&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Stable and growing company&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Professional working environment&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Long term growth opportunities&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Above market salary and remunerations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Main Responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Approve reconciliation of bank accounts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Check monthly posting of bank and investment transactions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitor cash requirements of the companies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Check the management and statutory accounts prepared by accounting associates.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist with/or prepare the CBM returns, Annual Regulatory returns and Quarterly Solvency returns&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring of client solvency and capital requirements&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Obtaining regulatory approval of changes to business plan&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Obtaining board approval for underwriting decisions&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure the production of management accounts, statutory accounts and information, budgets, cash flow statements and supplementary information as required.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assist with the adoption of appropriate accounting practices and ensure adherence thereto.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Manage cash requirements of the companies&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaise with and monitor investment managers in respect of invested funds&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintain contact with all client contacts, board directors and officers and advise them of developments&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Co-ordinate client and board meetings&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure timely production of board packs (minimum 7 days prior to meeting)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure timely production of minutes and review prior to distribution&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Action matters arising from client meetings&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure relevant company secretarial functions are performed in a timely manner and take on the Company Secretary role as necessary&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensure compliance with Corporate Governance&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintain ongoing relationships with clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Speak at least monthly with the client and visit client as required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Establish good relationship with key clients, regulatory and service providers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Qualifications and Experience&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Degree in Accounting /or ACCA &amp;amp; CPA&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;5-10 years insurance experience or financial services &amp;nbsp;industries&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of captive insurance industry considered a large asset&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent Client Service and interpersonal skills; comfortable dealing directly with clients&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Advanced presentation skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Compliance knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Can solve moderately complex issues through experience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1490</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 12:23:03 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1490</guid></item><item><title>Fund Accounting Manager</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Want to work in a successful funds company?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Willing to work among highly qualified and experienced multi-lingual professionals? We are currently looking for a fund accounting manager to join a formidable team.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Role and Responsibilities&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Daily management of the fund accounting and shareholder services teams &amp;amp; Prepare/Review and present financial statements.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation and review of NAV calculations and financial reporting &amp;amp; invoice processing.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Perform quality and compliance assurance checks.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Bank, inter-company, assets and investments reconciliations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Review, prepare and present monthly cash flow reports, KPI reports and other investment reporting as requested for monthly/quarterly meetings for the funds&amp;rsquo; investment strategy committees and board of directors.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Liaise with the shareholders services team in relation to subscriptions and redemptions and related charges and commissions.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Oversee and review the shareholder and compliance services team with preparation of dealing summaries, monthly statements, contract notes, share register updating and any client acceptance and due diligence procedures.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be the key person from the Fund Administrator to ensure and oversee the smooth completion of annual audits including finalization of all financial statements prior to review by the external auditors to ensure completeness and accuracy&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Develop strong knowledge of the client&amp;rsquo;s operations, underlying asset classes and hedging mechanisms.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Qualifications &amp;amp; Requirements&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;CPA, CA, ACA or ACCA qualified or part-qualified or equivalent.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong accounting background and accounts preparation experience.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;3 years&amp;rsquo; work experience in a fund accounting environment is essential; of which at least 1 year as senior fund accountant with experience in managing teams.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience of PFS Paxus integrated fund administration system is an advantage.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent MS Excel and strong MS Office required.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong analytical and organizational skills, ability to manage and track multiple tasks and deliverables simultaneously.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent teamwork, team-management, interpersonal, client relationship and communication (written and verbal) skills.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why join this company?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Luxurious &amp;amp; modern offices.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Very good exposure within funds.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;The candidate will be required to travel occasionally to other offices mainly Spain and UK.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good Salary Package.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If interested contact Andre on finance@castilleresources.com&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1484</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 14:38:42 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1484</guid></item><item><title>Client Accountant</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Our client is as&amp;nbsp;service provider offering a range of innovative and effective services that have widespread appeal to corporations and high net worth individuals. The role is an exciting opportunity that will offer positive challenges, ongoing training and the possibility of International travel from time to time as the work demands.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Main or Key Responsibilities:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Postings &amp;ndash; to complete bank and VAT postings and reconciliations.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Preparation of VAT returns.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Accounts &amp;ndash; to prepare statutory financial statements from source documentation and liaise with auditors for the completion of the audits.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Interim accounting assignments &amp;ndash; to prepare management accounts as above and other ad-hoc accounting reports as required.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;System development &amp;ndash; to appropriately report deficiencies; to contribute to strategies to resolve deficiencies identified.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Other responsibilities &amp;ndash; to assist in other technical and administrative areas within the Company as may reasonably be requested, having regard to level of work and existing work areas.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;Experience and qualifications:&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;At least 2 years&amp;rsquo; experience in an accounting environment and may hold a relevant accounting qualification.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Experience in fiduciary and trusts will be considered an asset.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Good working knowledge of Microsoft Word and Excel.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Personal Attributes:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;The ideal candidate must be a team player who can work on own initiative, with the&amp;nbsp;ability to work under pressure while adhering to tight deadlines. Must have a&amp;nbsp;pro-active and problem solving approach and be able to adapt&amp;nbsp;to change. Organizational and communication skills, both written and verbal and accuracy and attention to detail are of utmost importance&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1421</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 11:13:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1421</guid></item><item><title>Finance Officer - Banking</title><description>&lt;p&gt;One of Malta&amp;#39;s leading financial institutions is seeking to employ a Finance Officer&amp;nbsp;to join their growing team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Job responsibilities:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Uploading postings whilst ensuring that these are approved and reflected in the Bank&amp;rsquo;s general ledger;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reviewing suspense, intercompany and similar types of accounts to ensure that these are cleared precisely.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reviewing bank reconciliations to ensure accounting records are being appropriately managed;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Maintaining the banking and accounting system of the Group entities&amp;rsquo; general ledger, inter-system reconciliation and related tasks&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparing monthly management and variances reports&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparing VAT returns and assisting with withholding tax queries and returns;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Opening new general ledger accounts as required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting in the testing of new products or any other amendments required to the systems;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting with any regulatory reporting requirements&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Assisting with the annual / interim audits /reviews&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Performing other related duties as required, which may include payroll accounting and completion of tax returns&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Documenting the Finance department&amp;rsquo;s policies and procedures&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Other duties as may be determined from time to time by the Chief Financial Officer&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Required knowledge, skills and experience:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Partly qualified/studying to obtain ACCA qualification or similar&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Advanced level in Accounting&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good knowledge of accounting specifically IFRS &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proficiency in Microsoft applications (in particular MS&amp;nbsp;Excel)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Attention to detail&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in this position, kindly apply online.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1167</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 16:36:57 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1167</guid></item><item><title>Fund Accountant Senior</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Want to work with the leading recognized fund administrators in Malta? Apply within as this knowledgeable&amp;nbsp;team of accountants and professionals is seeking to take on board a Senior Fund Accountant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Job Responsibilities:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To ensure well timed and proper NAV calculation on a weekly or monthly basis&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Handling of security and cash activity for portfolios&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Reconciliation of the portfolio from broker to in-house structure.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Responding to client queries in a timely manner.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring proper compliance with regulatory needs and other requirements of the funds specifications&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Detailed revision of NAV calculations for Hedge Funds&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Preparation of financial statements as required&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Supervision and training of Fund Accounting staff&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Skills required:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;2-3&amp;nbsp;years&amp;rsquo; experience in a similar role.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Be able to meet agreed deadlines&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Experience in private equity is necessary.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;An accountancy qualification would be an asset.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Excellent interpersonal and written communications skills&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Strong PC skills including Word, Excel&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/975</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 10:18:01 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/975</guid></item><item><title>Accounts Clerk - International Firm</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;We are a global consultancy firm specializing in investment programs. We are currently looking to employ an accounts clerk to join our offices in Malta.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Job Duties include:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Must be able to work on own initiative with limited supervision&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Compile and Analyze financial information&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Prepare general ledger accounts&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Produce monthly reports as instructed&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Preparation of revenue, expenses, invoices and other accounts docs&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Process payments&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;To assist in the development and maintenance of financial databases, computer software systems and manual filing systems&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Assisting the accounts team&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;To provide support and to assist in the establishment of new business in any foreign country&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Credentials and Employment experience:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Excellent verbal and written communication of Maltese and English&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;Accounting background at Diploma level&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;At least 5 year experience in a similar role&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;&lt;font face="Verdana, Geneva, sans-serif"&gt;&lt;font size="2"&gt;IT literate and experience in Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Database Management and other software applications&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1476</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 16:14:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1476</guid></item><item><title>Account Manager - Insurance</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Our Client&amp;nbsp;operating within the Insurance sector, is seeking to recruit an Account Manager to support the growth strategy in new products and services diversification.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Responsibilities will be:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To manage existing accounts in Spain and Portugal,&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;To follow implementation and foresee any bottleneck so as to anticipate action plan and to help these accounts grow.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This will involve working with insurance teams at global and local level, and travelling frequently (at least once a month) to Spain and Portugal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ideal candidate will have:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;+4 years&amp;#39; experience in an Account Management role&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good understanding of affinity and B to B to C insurance&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Good writing and speaking knowledge of &lt;b&gt;Portuguese, Spanish and English&lt;/b&gt; is essential&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Well organized &amp;amp; excellent communicator&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Sales skills &amp;ndash; result oriented character&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more information please contact Nikki on finance@castilleresources.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1371</link><category>Executive</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 15:16:00 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1371</guid></item><item><title>Head of Syndicated Loan Closer</title><description>&lt;p&gt;A leading bank is seeking a Head of Syndicated Loan Closer. This person&amp;nbsp;will be leading a team responsible for closing off syndicate loan trades. The team is mainly responsible for managing the flow of trade information, preparing and setting-up trade bookings and settlements, maintaining detailed and accurate trade records as well as monitoring the distribution of trade knowledge throughout the required areas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Some duties and responsibilities&lt;/b&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Ensuring expedite settlement of unsettled trades through handling of syndicate loans documentation (including but not limited to: Trade Confirmation, Assignments, Novations &amp;amp; Transfer Certificates, Pricing letter / Funding Memos)&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Monitoring settlement of loan trade and following up on any delayed settlements whilst ensuring that loan trade settlements are reflected accurately and timely in the Bank&amp;rsquo;s current loan system and following up on any updates/ corrections required.&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Recording of any inaccuracies/ delayed updates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The ideal candidate will have:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of LMA Standard documentation and awareness of LSTA&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;A certification in Credit and Loan Administration and LMA&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Proficient in Microsoft Excel&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Previous experience in similar loan closure role&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For &amp;nbsp;more details please contact Nikki on finance@castilleresources.com&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1369</link><category>Executive</category><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 15:15:46 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1369</guid></item><item><title>Castille Internship Program &#x2013; Tech</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Castille is looking for aspiring young interns from different educational systems with a genuine interest in &lt;b&gt;Software Development &amp;amp; Technology&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;I&lt;b&gt;nternships &lt;/b&gt;on a short or long term placement. The purpose of the Castille Intern Program is to provide students with an opportunity to enhance and apply what they learn in their academic setting by working in an organization which offers the student a structured real life work experience. Duration of the program is flexible and will be agreed upon by all parties before the internship begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this work experience students would:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Gain valuable work experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Build contacts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Apply classroom knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a glimpse of future opportunities for professional growth &amp;amp; development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a realistic preview of what it is like to work in a professional service organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interested candidates are invited to apply online on&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.castilleresources.com/en/login"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;and send an email on &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:intern@castilleresources.com"&gt;&lt;b&gt;intern@castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;.&lt;/u&gt; We will contact candidates when we find the ideal internship for them.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/782</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 14:48:15 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/782</guid></item><item><title>Castille Internship Program - Marketing</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a job to gain experience?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Castille is looking for aspiring young interns from different educational systems with a genuine interest in&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;Marketing&lt;/b&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;b&gt;Internships&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;on a short or long term placement. The purpose of the Castille Intern Program is to provide students with an opportunity to enhance and apply what they learn in their academic setting by working in an organization which offers the student a structured real life work experience. Duration of the program is flexible and will be agreed upon by all parties before the internship begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this work experience students would:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Gain valuable work experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Build contacts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Apply classroom knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a glimpse of future opportunities for professional growth &amp;amp; development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a realistic preview of what it is like to work in a professional service organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interested candidates are invited to apply online on&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.castilleresources.com/en/login"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;and send an email on&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:intern@castilleresources.com"&gt;&lt;b&gt;intern@castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;.&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;We will contact candidates when we find the ideal internship for them.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1001</link><category>Technology</category><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 11:44:55 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1001</guid></item><item><title>Castille Internship Program &#x2013; Accountancy &amp; Finance</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Castille is looking for aspiring young interns from different educational systems with a genuine interest in &lt;b&gt;Accountancy &amp;amp; Finance Internships&lt;/b&gt; on a short or long placement. The purpose of the Castille Intern Program is to provide students with an opportunity to enhance and apply what they learn in their academic setting by working in an organization. It is more than a job; it is a program which offers the student a structured real life work experience. Duration of the program would be flexible and will be agreed upon by all parties before the internship begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;During this work experience students would:&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Gain valuable work experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Build contacts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Apply classroom knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a glimpse of future opportunities for professional growth &amp;amp; development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a realistic preview of what it is like to work in a professional service organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One may also receive offers for full time employment once the program is complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interested candidates are invited to apply online on &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.castilleresources.com/en/login"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;and send an email on &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:intern@castilleresources.com"&gt;&lt;b&gt;intern@castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;. We will contact candidates when we find the ideal internship for them.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/784</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2016 11:44:49 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/784</guid></item><item><title>Castille Internship Program - Statistics</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Castille is looking for aspiring young interns from different educational systems with a genuine interest in &lt;b&gt;Mathematics/Statistics Internships &lt;/b&gt;a short or long term placement. The purpose of the Castille Intern Program is to provide students with an opportunity to enhance and apply what they learn in their academic setting by working in an organization which offers the student a structured real life work experience. Duration of the program is flexible and will be agreed upon by all parties before the internship begins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this work experience students would:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Gain valuable work experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Build contacts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Apply classroom knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a glimpse of future opportunities for professional growth &amp;amp; development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a realistic preview of what it is like to work in a professional service organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interested candidates are invited to apply online on&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.castilleresources.com/en/login"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;and send an email on&amp;nbsp;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:intern@castilleresources.com"&gt;&lt;b&gt;intern@castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;.&lt;/u&gt;&amp;nbsp;We will contact candidates when we find the ideal internship for them.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1002</link><category>Finance</category><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2016 15:36:29 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/1002</guid></item><item><title>Castille Internship Program &#x2013; Legal</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Looking for a job to gain experience?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Castille is looking for aspiring young interns from different educational systems with a genuine interest in &lt;b&gt;Legal Internships&lt;/b&gt; on a short or long placement. The purpose of the Castille Intern Program is to provide students with an opportunity to enhance and apply what they learn in their academic setting by working in an organization. It is more than a job; it is a program which offers the student a structured real life work experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During this work experience students would :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Gain valuable work experience&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Build contacts&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Apply classroom knowledge&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a glimpse of future opportunities for professional growth &amp;amp; development&lt;/li&gt;
	&lt;li&gt;Get a realistic preview of what it is like to work in a professional service organisation&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One may also receive offers for full time employment once the program is complete.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Interested candidates are invited to apply online on &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.castilleresources.com/en/login"&gt;&lt;b&gt;www.castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;nbsp;and send an email on &lt;/b&gt;&lt;a href="mailto:intern@castilleresources.com"&gt;&lt;b&gt;intern@castilleresources.com&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;u&gt;.&lt;/u&gt; We will contact candidates when we find the ideal internship for them.&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description><link>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/783</link><category>Legal</category><pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2016 16:11:49 GMT</pubDate><guid>https://www.castilleresources.com//en/job-detail/783</guid></item></channel>
<nodes>97</nodes></root>
