<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type='text/xsl'  href='../xslt/list.xsl'?>
<root xmlns:jobsinmalta="http://jobsinmalta.com/jobsinmalta-schema" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" jobsinmalta:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://jobsinmalta.com/jobsinmalta.xsd" encoding="utf-8">
<channel>
    <title>Konnekt</title>
    <description>Konnekt Opportunity Feed</description>
    <link>https://www.konnekt.com/</link>
          <item>
        <title>Administration Clerk (Part-Time)</title>
        <description>Our client, an established company within the Maritime industry are currently seeking to recruit an Administration Clerk on a part-time basis to join their team of professionals.

Administration Clerk (Part-Time)
MT 5207/16

In this role you will primarily be called to update and upload product specifications on the company website. This will involve, photographs of products, compiling their description and specifications and inputting all data on the company&#x2019;s database. In addition,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14786/administration-clerk-part-time</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 16:24:35 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client is an established organisation within the Maritime industry. There are presently seeking to recruit a Junior Engineer to join their energetic and dynamic team of professionals.

Junior Engineer
MT 8971/16

As Junior Engineer, working closely with the General Director, you will assist as necessary in the general and daily running of operations. You will directly participate with various engineering projects, which will involve regularly analysing internal processes and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14789/junior-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 16:23:02 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Administration Assistant (Part-Time)</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-known company within the Maritime sector. Presently they are seeking to employ an Administration Assistant on a part-time basis to joint their professional and dynamic team.

Administration Assistant (Part-Time)
MT 6859/16

As Administration Assistant, working closely with the ISO Manager you will be called to assist in daily administrative tasks. This will involve inputting data in the company&#x2019;s database, performing a number of filing processes, handling calls and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14787/administration-assistant-part-time</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 16:21:07 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Fraud Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is a start-up online casino starting their operations in Malta, but forming part of a highly successful and established land-based casino in Northern and Central Europe. They specialise in social casino and are looking for a Fraud Officer to join their team of professionals.

Fraud Officer
MT 5196/16

The successful candidate will be reporting directly to the General Manager and be primarily responsible for the Risk, Fraud and Payments function. You will be responsible for...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14766/fraud-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Gaming</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 14:36:17 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Public Affairs And Communications Manager</title>
        <description>Our Client,&#xA0;a&#xA0;local renowned well established Group of Companies, is seeking to recruit a &#xA0;Public Affairs &amp; Communications Manager&#xA0;to join their Team.

Public Affairs &amp; Communications Manager
MT 0435/16

You will develop the Public Affairs &amp; Communication systems for a group of four companies operating within the Beverage, Retail, Hospitality and Education industries. You will be reporting into the Chief Operations Officer and working in close collaboration with the General Managers, In...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14817/public-affairs-and-communications-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 14:09:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is&#xA0;group of companies operating across different vertical industries. Through focused efforts, they have built a strong presence and they are currently seeking to recruit a Senior Accountant&#xA0;to join their team.&#xA0;

Senior Accountant
MT 4984/16

As Finance Manager, you will be reporting directly to the CFO and will have a team of 6 Accounts Executives reporting to you. You will be responsible of leading the Accounts Department and ensuring that everything is running smoothly....</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14816/senior-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 12:26:00 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Client Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is an established accountancy firm operating within the financial services industry for a significant number of years. They are currently looking for a Client Accountant to join their team.

Client Accountant
MT 6765/16

As a Client Accountant you will be forming part of a team of client accountants and you will be reporting directly to the Partners of the firm. You shall be responsible for a portfolio of clients and shall ensure correct and up to date accounts are...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14784/client-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 10:40:26 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller - Part Time</title>
        <description>Our client is an expert in providing medical services to a variety of multinational companies and they are seeking to recruit a part time Financial Controller to join their team of professionals.

Financial Controller - Part Time
MT 5829/16

As Financial controller, you will be mainly focused on international projects and will be primarily responsible for the production of management accounts, generating internal reports,&#xA0;preparing the budgets and forecasts and VAT returns.&#xA0;You will...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14801/financial-controller-part-time</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2016 10:14:35 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Administrative Assistant</title>
        <description>Our client, a reputable institution within the Financial Services sector, is currently seeking to recruit a Marketing Assistant&#xA0;on a one year definite contract, which may be extended or made into an indefinite contract.

Administrative Assistant
MT 4263/16

As an Administrative Assistant&#xA0;you will be screening calls, managing calendar events and uploading events and articles onto the website.&#xA0;You will also assist in the administration of ad-hoc projects and coordinate the logistics of...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14731/administrative-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 21:17:02 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Civil &amp; Structural Draughtsperson</title>
        <description>Our client, an established architectural firm, are currently seeking the services of a Civil &amp; Structural Draughtsperson to join their team.

Civil &amp; Structural Draughtsperson
MT 4315/16

Reporting to the Chief Architect, you will be required to produce sketches and detailed scaled plans using AutoCAD. This will include liaising with building services, project managers, contractors and customers, and collecting all the information required. The job holder, will be responsible for...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14808/civil-structural-draughtsperson</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Creative &amp; Design</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 17:19:14 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Marketing Assistant</title>
        <description>Our client, a reputable institution within the Financial Services sector, is currently seeking to recruit a Marketing Assistant&#xA0;on a one year definite contract, which may be extended or made into an indefinite contract.

Marketing Assistant
MT 0001/16

As a Marketing Assistant you will be responsible for the day to day support of the marketing function. This will include executing the marketing plan, contributing to social and digital media campaigns, conducting research on companies...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14810/marketing-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:57:51 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>HR Coordinator</title>
        <description>Our client is a multinational company operating in Malta with increased activity in its manufacturing and trading operations. They are currently seeking to recruit the services of an HR Coordinator.&#xA0;

HR Coordinator
MT 6493/16

&#xA0;As an HR Coordinator you will form&#xA0;part of the HR Department and working closely with team members and managers. &#xA0;You will be responsible for&#xA0;assisting&#xA0;in employee performance reviews, delivering in-house induction training,&#xA0;supporting employee communication and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14813/hr-coordinator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:57:29 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Site Operations Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is a sizeable international company offering a wide range of technical products and services. They hold an extensive client base and throughout the years they have cultivated top notch quality standards in an effort to fortify their market leadership position. A vacancy for the role of Site Manager has arisen within their structure.

Site Operations Manager
MT &#xA0;5431/16

This role carries the responsibility for managing a team in the day to day running of the operations, in...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14811/site-operations-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 16:11:14 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Logistic Engineer </title>
        <description>Our client,&#xA0;a well established company operating in the field of energy, is looking to recruit a Logistic Engineer&#xA0;to work strictly with the Production &amp; Technology Department in order to ensure the flow of the operations.&#xA0;

Logistic Engineer&#xA0;
MT 3084/16

In the role of Logistic Engineer you will be in&#xA0;in charge of&#xA0;all aspects of the distribution with the ultimate goal of improving the efficiency&#xA0;of&#xA0;the system&#xA0;employed. You will be working in&#xA0;the entire supply chain including handling...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14807/logistic-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Supply Chain, Transport &amp; Warehousing</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 11:59:36 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller (Insurance)</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-established company operating within the financial services industry, primarily within Insurance. They are currently in the process of seeking to recruit a Financial Controller to manage their Finance team.

Financial Controller
MT 4960/16

In this role, you will be reporting to the CEO and will be managing the Finance team.&#xA0;will manage the compilation and presentation of management accounts, budget preparations, financial forecasts and ensuring compliance with all...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14546/financial-controller-insurance</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 10:49:41 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is a company that provides electrical and mechanical installation services&#xA0;to a broad range of clients. They are currently looking to recruit an Accountant to join their team.

Accountant
MT 8039/16

As an Accountant&#xA0;you shall be responsible for the setting up of the finance function and ensuring the correct development of the department on an ongoing basis. You shall be responsible for&#xA0;preparation of management accounts and the preparation and submission of the VAT returns....</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14772/accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 10:22:36 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Executive (French speaking)</title>
        <description>Our client, an internationally recognised brand, is currently in the process of opening their offices in Malta. They are looking to employ an Accounts Executive to join their offices in Malta.

MT 9301/16
Accounts Executive&#xA0;

In this role, you will be responsible for accounting duties for their Malta and even for their international offices. These responsibilities will include the posting of invoices, preparing reconciliations, constantly tracking expenses, the preparation and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14700/accounts-executive-french-speaking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2016 10:14:55 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Runner</title>
        <description>Our client is an established organisation operating within the maritime industry. They are currently seeking the service of a Runner to join their dynamic and energetic team of professionals.

Runner
MT 5287/16

Within this position you will be called to manage and evaluate the company&#x2019;s purchase requirements. The job holder will be responsible for liaising with internal stakeholders, sourcing technical equipment and other products required to conduct operational activities. The...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14785/runner</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Supply Chain, Transport &amp; Warehousing</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 17:16:00 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Project Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client is an industry leader providing various engineering related systems. They have built a solid reputation and workforce and are constantly on the lookout to fine tune their operations in order to reflect best industry standards. They are currently seeking to recruit &#xA0;a Project Engineer to join their team.

Project Engineer
MT 7175/16&#xA0;

As a Project Engineer you will be responsible for management of projects &#xA0;from pre tendering all throughout completion, with regards to...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14794/project-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 16:32:57 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Operations Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is an esteemed Industry leader offering a multitude of services. Through the years they have achieved significant results and have expanded their services to the foreign market. Currently they are seeking to further expand their team with the recruitment of Operations Manager.

Operations Manager
MT 0358/16 &#xA0; 

Reporting to the General Manager you will be engaged in the daily operations and general management of the company. You will be tasked with establishing and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14795/operations-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Construction</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 15:54:11 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client is&#xA0;one of the largest yachting group of companies in Malta. Founded in 1989, the company started out offering basic yachting services however following their initial success, the company has now grown to offer a wider range of services such as refit management, yacht brokerage, yacht charter, customs clearance, agency and bunkering. They are currently looking to recruit a Financial Controller to join their team.

Financial Controller

MT 0939/16

As a Financial Controller...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14773/financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 13:38:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client&#xA0;is a well-established importer and distributor operating within the FMCG industry, having an established portfolio of well-renowned brands.

Financial Controller
MT 0851/16

As a Financial Controller, you will be reporting to the General Manager. In this role, you will be responsible managing the accounting team,&#xA0;the preparation of management accounts, preparing monthly internal reports such as profitability reports for their main products and outlets, and liaising with...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14802/financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 12:19:12 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Group Marketing Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading group of companies operating within the automotive industry, with a solid reputation. They are currently seeking the services of a dynamic and committed Group Marketing Manager to join their team.

Group Marketing Manager
MT 2524/16

As Group Marketing Manager, reporting to the Managing Director you will develop and manage marketing and promotional activity for the company in order to ensure profitability in line with the company&#x2019;s overall strategy. &#xA0;The...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14798/group-marketing-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 11:26:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Clerk</title>
        <description>Our Client; an established company in mechanical and engineering services is seeking to recruit an accounts clerk to join their finance team.

Accounts Clerk
MT 4655/16

As an Accounts Clerk, you will perform basic accounting and book keeping duties such&#xA0;as&#xA0;general ledger postings,&#xA0;account reconciliations, issue payments, credit control and report up to Trial Balance stage. Reporting to the Finance Manager, in this Role you will have other duties as may be required in order to be able...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14799/accounts-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 10:32:13 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>DBA</title>
        <description>Our client is an organisation operating within the financial services industry and is renowned for their reputation of excellence and dedication to offer a quality service. Their success can be accredited to their commitment to employee development and product innovation. They are currently seeking to recruit a committed person for the post of a Database Administrator.&#xA0;

DBA
MT 0770/16

As a DBA you will be responsible for the design, installation, configuration, upgrade,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14796/dba</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 09:30:15 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Sales Manager</title>
        <description>Our client, an international provider of solutions for the packaging and processing industries, is presently seeking to recruit a Sales Manager&#xA0;to join their growing team.

Sales Manager

MT 5834/16

In this role you will be&#xA0;responsible for ensuring sales growth and&#xA0;company&#xA0;penetration within the market. You will be handling client relationships and provide high quality services as well as secure new business relationships and increase sales revenue. You will be in charge of organizing...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14703/sales-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Oct 2016 07:54:40 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Operations Manager (Warehouse &amp; Distribution)</title>
        <description>Our client, is a joint venture between two established importation and distribution companies holding a varied portfolio of products. They are currently seeking to recruit an Operations Manager to establish and grow this new business.

Operations Manager (Warehouse &amp; Distribution)&#xA0;
MT 5569/16

Reporting to the Board of Directors, you will be engaged to manage the day-to-day operations and general management of the company. You will be tasked with establishing and implementing company...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13130/operations-manager-warehouse-distribution</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 16:21:48 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Account Manager - Legal</title>
        <description>Our client is a Group that operates within the financial services sector. They&#xA0;are a well known as a &#xA0;retirement scheme administrator and as a Corporate Services provider. Due to growth, they are&#xA0;currently looking to recruit a Legal Account Manager&#xA0;to join their team of professionals.

Account Manager - Legal

MT 3571/16

As an Account Manager, you will report directly to the Director of Client Services and you will handle and process the legal and administrative matters related to the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14742/account-manager-legal</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Legal</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 14:45:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Customer Account Manager - Nano Market - German</title>
        <description>Our client is an international company providing&#xA0;unrivalled levels of business and IT support.&#xA0;Their success is derived from their dedication and focus to deliver a high quality service at all times. As a result of growth, they are currently seeking the services of a German Speaking Customer Service Representative.

Customer Account Manager - Nano Market - German
MT 5254/16

In this position you will be the a point of contact for Customer&#x2019;s Support, and Sales enquiries, taking ownership...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14793/customer-account-manager-nano-market-german</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Customer Service</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 14:32:43 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Technical Manager </title>
        <description>Our client who is an established organisation operating within the manufacturing industry is presently seeking to recruit a Technical Manager&#xA0;to join their team.

Technical Manager
MT&#xA0;7298/16

You will be responsible for the general tooling, jigging and processes in the Factory, ensuring that the tools are in such a state that all production runs flow smoothly with good quality. The inventory for equipment, tools and jigs thus falls under your responsibility. As the Technical Manager,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14791/technical-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 13:06:07 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Quality Assurace (QA) - Temporary</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-established organisation operating within a high value manufacturing industry. They are currently seeking a&#xA0;Quality Assurance person to join their team on a Temporary basis.

Quality Assurace (QA) - Temporary
MT 9421/16

Reporting to the Quality Assurance Coordinator, you will be responsible for assisting the company in the maintenance, upkeep and development of the various pillars of the quality management system by participating in the continuous improvement...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14792/quality-assurace-qa-temporary</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Science &amp; Research</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 12:56:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Medical Writer</title>
        <description>Our client, a multinational company operating in Malta with increased activity in its manufacturing and trading operations, is currently seeking to recruit a Medical Writer.

Medical Writer&#xA0;
MT 5139/16
&#xA0;

Reporting to the Senior Manager, as a Medical Writer, you will be responsible for drafting and writing the clinical section of medical reports. All documents developed will be of an excellent scientific standard requiring you to analyse and compile data within set timelines....</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14757/medical-writer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Science &amp; Research</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 11:33:11 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>R&amp;D Laboratory Technician</title>
        <description>Our client, a multinational company operating in Malta with increased activity in its manufacturing and trading operations, is currently seeking to recruit a Laboratory Technician.

R&amp;D &#xA0;Laboratory Technician
MT 4466/16

The chosen candidate will be reporting to the Global Containers &amp; Disposable Lab Supervisor, and will be responsible for carrying out routine laboratory work in compliance to the regulatory bodies in charge. The duties would consist of&#xA0;&#xA0;running tests&#xA0;related to product...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14715/r-d-laboratory-technician</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Science &amp; Research</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 11:32:55 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Finance Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is an international company experienced in global sourcing, offering a vast range of installation materials and sanitary ware. They are seeking to recruit a Finance Officer to join their team of professionals.

Finance Officer
MT 5800/16

As Finance Officer, working alongside the Finance Manager you will be responsible for daily accounting duties. Your responsibilities will include the posting and issuing of invoices, bank reconciliations, the preparation of payments and also...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14790/finance-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 09:00:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Quality Assurance (QA)</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-established organisation operating within a high value manufacturing industry. They are currently seeking a&#xA0;Quality Assurance person to join their growing team.

Quality Assurance
MT 5185/16

Reporting to the Quality Assurance Coordinator, you will be responsible for assisting the company in the maintenance, upkeep and development of the various pillars of the quality management system by participating in the continuous improvement process while ensuring compliance...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14781/quality-assurance-qa</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Other</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2016 08:30:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Client Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is a reputable organisation operating within the financial services industry and forming part of an international network. They are currently seeking a Client Accountant to join their finance team.

Client Accountant
MT 0231/16

As a Client Accountant you shall be responsible for a portfolio of clients in order to provide accountancy services. You shall be responsible for ensuring accounting records have been&#xA0;accurately inputted into the system and ensure accurate accounts...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14783/client-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 19:43:18 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Operations Executive</title>
        <description>Our client, an organisation offering a wide range of products and services in the sector of entertainment and telecommunications is&#xA0;currently seeking to recruit an Operations Executive.&#xA0;

Operations Executive
MT 6069/16

As an Operations Executive, reporting to the Call Centre Manager,&#xA0;you will be responsible for&#xA0;monitoring of service levels throughout the day, you will also monitor&#xA0;Staffing levels, absence and overtime requirements. Your duties will include reviewing the&#xA0;contact centre...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14780/operations-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Customer Service</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 17:22:52 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Service Delivery Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is an established technology services provider operating with an international client base. They are currently looking towards strengthening their team through the recruitment of a&#xA0;Service Delivery Manager.

Service Delivery Manager
MT 7018/16

Reporting to the CEO, and working with the other Service Delivery Managers, in Malta and Globally. As the&#xA0;Service Delivery Manager&#xA0;you will be responsible for leading, coaching and developing a team of Assignment Managers that will...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14779/service-delivery-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 15:22:03 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>General Office Clerk</title>
        <description>Our Client is an established player in the maritime and hospitality industry. As part of their ongoing growth they are currently seeking to recruit a Junior Office Clerk to join their team.

Junior Office Clerk
MT 1691/16 

You will be supporting the management team by&#xA0;performing General Administration and Secretarial duties. You will also be assisting the Marketing Department and the Business Development team&#xA0;in their day to day duties. As a Junior Office Clerk, you will do filing&#xA0;and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14698/general-office-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 14:51:39 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Insurance Clerk</title>
        <description>Our client is a prominent company operating within the automotive industry. They are currently looking for an Insurance Clerk to join their team.

Insurance Clerk
MT 2763/16

As Insurance Clerk you will be in charge of clerical duties primarily in relation to insurance sales, underwriting duties, claims processing and renewals of policies and vehicle road licences. You will liaise with customers and other third parties, collecting payments and dealing with incoming and outgoing calls....</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14777/insurance-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Insurance</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 12:15:58 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client is an established company within the petroleum industry. Due to growth, they are seeking to recruit a Financial Controller to join their team of professionals.

Financial Controller
MT 5595/16

As the Financial Controller, you will be responsible for the Company&#x2019;s Group Accounts and perform general accounting functions which will include financial planning and month- end accounting procedures and reconciliations. Other responsibilities would include preparing monthly...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14775/financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:37:02 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Corporate Governance Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading and prestigious business law firm servicing a substantial local and international client base. They are currently in the process of seeking to employ a Corporate Governance Executive&#xA0;to join their firm.

Corporate Governance Executive
MT 9997/16

As a Corporate Governance Executive,&#xA0;you will be assisting&#xA0;the Insurance department or Corporate Governance department&#xA0;accordingly. Your responsibilities will include corporate governance, assisting in the drafting of...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14776/corporate-governance-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Legal</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 11:15:01 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Corporate/ Financial Services Lawyer</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading and prestigious business law firm servicing a substantial local and international client base. They are looking to recruit lawyers to their Corporate and Financial Services teams.

Corporate/Financial services&#xA0;Lawyer
MT 5551/16

In this role, you will form part of a professional team operating in corporate, commercial and financial services practice. You will address client needs and manage daily requests appropriately. As part of this role you will draft and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14774/corporate-financial-services-lawyer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Legal</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 10:38:40 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Client Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-establish firm within the Corporate Services Industry, offering specialised services to an International client base. They are seeking to recruit a Client Accountant to join their team of professionals.

Client Accountant
MT 5510/16

The successful candidate will be part of the Finance Department and reporting to the Accounts&#xA0;Manager. You will be responsible for a portfolio of clients and will be in charge of&#xA0;preparing financial statements up to management...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14771/client-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 08:52:19 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Client Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is a fast growing international business which offers financial and business services to onshore and offshore clients. They are currently looking to recruit a&#xA0;Client Accountant&#xA0;to join their team of professionals.

Client Accountant
MT 9826/16

The successful candidate&#xA0;will be responsible for a portfolio of clients and&#xA0;duties will include over-seeing and reviewing of all book-keeping; reviewing of VAT returns; the preparation of Tax returns and the&#xA0;preparation&#xA0;of the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14770/client-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Finance</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2016 08:13:28 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Social Media Content Producer</title>
        <description>Our client is one of the largest organisations on the Maltese Islands and is seeking to recruit a Social Media Content Producer to join their team. &#xA0;

Social Media Content Producer
MT 7450/16

You will be producing content in line with the brand&amp;#39;s communication strategies and content production initiatives for multiple channels. &#xA0;This, you will be doing from planning to development and may include but not limited to; writing and proof reading, creating visual content for web, social...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14748/social-media-content-producer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 08:01:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Digital Strategist</title>
        <description>Our client is one of the largest organisations&#xA0;on the Maltese Islands and is seeking to recruit a Digital Strategist to join their team. &#xA0;

Digital Strategist&#xA0;
MT 3589/16

You will be reporting into the Digital Director and your main aim is to be the key implementer of the organisation&amp;#39;s digital strategy. &#xA0;You will explore, utilise and advise upon the full array of digital tools including websites, mobile, social media online portals and other digital platforms. &#xA0;As the Digital...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14746/digital-strategist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Oct 2016 07:58:12 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Medical Information Specialist</title>
        <description>Our client, a multinational company operating in Malta with increased activity in its manufacturing and trading operations, is currently seeking to recruit a Medical Information Specialist.

Medical Information Specialist
MT 7686/16
&#xA0;

As a Medical Information Specialist you will be responsible for inspecting products with the scope of providing both the potential benefits and risks that the products entail. This position calls for you to develop and examine documents such as annual...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14762/medical-information-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Science &amp; Research</category>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2016 23:15:48 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Compliance Assistant </title>
        <description>Our client is an established company providing financial services to both local and international clients. They are currently seeking to recruit a Compliance Assistant to join their Audit and Assurance Department.

Compliance Assistant
&#xA0;MT 1704/16

As a Compliance Assistant your responsibilities will entail assisting in Anti-Money Laundering (AML) and Regulatory Compliance audits by carrying out research on AML and regulatory issues impacting mainly the investment services arena and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14761/compliance-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Finance</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 16:50:08 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Head of Operations</title>
        <description>Our client is an established player in the maritime and hospitality industry. As part of their ongoing investment and growth they are currently seeking to recruit Head of Operations to join their dynamic team.

Head of Operations
MT 1027/16 &#xA0;

Reporting to the General Manager, you will be engaged in handling the day to day operations and general management of the company. You will be tasked with establishing and implementing company strategy, directives and operational policies, in...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14697/head-of-operations</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Hospitality &amp; Leisure</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 16:18:05 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Administrative Assistant</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading law firm in Malta. They are looking to recruit an Administration Assistant to join their growing team.

Administration Assistant
MT 9510/16

In this role you will be screening calls, managing calendar events and supporting the corporate department in administration work.&#xA0;You will also assist in the administration of ad-hoc projects and coordinate travel bookings.&#xA0;Furthermore, you will be assisting in preparing reports and updating records and databases with...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14760/administrative-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 16:08:00 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Head of Compliance - MLRO</title>
        <description>Our client is an established&#xA0;electronic money institution. They are currently seeking to recruit a Head of Compliance and MLRO to join their Compliance Department.&#xA0;

Head of Compliance - MLRO
MT 2687/16

In this Role, you will be reporting to the CEO and will be acting as the financial institution&#x2018;s Money Laundering Reporting Officer, heading the financial institution&#x2019;s Compliance function. As an MLRO you will be responsible for the the drafting of the relevant institution&#x2019;s Compliance...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14744/head-of-compliance-mlro</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Finance</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 11:38:25 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Receptionist / Administrator</title>
        <description>Our client is a company offering corporate, advisory and trustee services, are looking for a&#xA0;Receptionist / Administrator to implement their team.

Receptionist / Administrator
MT 3531/16

As Receptionist/Administrator&#xA0;you will be responsible for managing the reception area,&#xA0;answering telephone calls in a courteous and friendly manner, obtaining the caller&#x2019;s name&#xA0;and diverting calls as necessary.&#xA0;Your responsibilities will also include coordinating office activities, compiling and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14759/receptionist-administrator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 10:48:05 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Restaurant Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is an established and reputable company operating within the hospitality industry. They are seeking to recruit a Restaurant Manager to join their team of professionals.

Restaurant Manager
MT 8896/16

As Restaurant Manager, you will be in charge of managing all aspects of the F&amp;B operations within the Restaurant. You will be responsible to control budgets, analyse current operations, manage staff, determine pricing, promote the company&#x2019;s products and participate actively in...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14739/restaurant-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Hospitality &amp; Leisure</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2016 09:44:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Digital Marketing Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is a well&#xA0;established and one of the leading real estate companies on the Island. They are looking to a Digital Marketing Executive to join their team.

Digital Marketing Executive
MT 8699/16

Reporting to the Marketing Manager, you&#xA0;will be called to oversee the digital marketing strategy and manage marketing projects. You will be responsible for using creative and innovative strategies to enhance and develop the company&#x2019;s online presence and engagement. Within this position...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14754/digital-marketing-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 16:30:23 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Electrical Technician</title>
        <description>Our client is an international manufacturing company acting as a supplier to leading clients in Europe and Worldwide. Over these past years, the company has invested significantly in technology and human resources in order to drive business and change. They are now looking towards recruiting an Electrical Technician&#xA0;to assist in the running of the business.

Electrical Technician
MT 8201/16

You will be engaged in fault finding on plant, production and general plant services. You will...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14756/electrical-technician</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Manufacturing</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 15:33:26 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Finance Associate</title>
        <description>Our client is an online lead generation company, and is seeking to recruit a Finance Associate to join their team of professionals.

Finance Associate&#xA0;
MT 6975/16

The successful candidate will be working as part of a team and be responsible for general daily accounting duties. You will be in charge of the monitoring of invoices and credit card expenditure, producing monthly sales data reports and analysing data, and liaising with payment providers with regards to day to day...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14755/finance-associate</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 15:00:17 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>BAU Developer - Big Data</title>
        <description>Our client is a prominent company operating within the iGaming industry. They are currently looking to recruit a BAU Developer to join their dynamic team on full time basis.

BAU Developer
MT 0449/16

Working within the Data Development team, you will provide 2nd line support for issues arising on real-time ingestion applications and be responsible to ensure that client issues are resolved within a timely and quality efficient manner to ensure the continuity of data processes and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14714/bau-developer-big-data</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 14:51:35 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>IT Administrator</title>
        <description>Our client is a well known international company&#xA0;operating&#xA0;within the manufacturing industry. They are currently looking to recruit an IT Administrator&#xA0;o join their team.&#xA0;

IT Administrator
MT 6076/16

As an IT Administrator you will be providing corrective 1st and 2nd line support for customer&amp;#39;s&#xA0;systems&#xA0;and preventive maintenance for the company&amp;#39;s systems and products. You will carry out operational activities, resolving incidents, assisting with installations, updates,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14749/it-administrator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 11:57:38 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Customer Support Officer Japanese Speaking</title>
        <description>Our client is an IT company providing specialized payment solutions to clients deriving from different vertical industries. They are currently looking for an Account Manager to maintain good business relationships with existing key clients.

Customer Support Officer Japanese Speaking
MT 2262/16

The successful candidate will be required to provide support and assistance&#xA0;along with implementing proactive measures to ensure customer satisfaction.&#xA0;You will need to ensure that clients&#x2019;...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14750/customer-support-officer-japanese-speaking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Customer Service</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 11:48:10 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Food &amp; Beverage Operations Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is an established and reputable company operating within the hospitality industry. They are seeking to recruit a Food &amp; Beverage Operations Manager to join their team of professionals.

Food &amp; Beverage Operations Manager
MT 7025/16

As Food &amp; Beverage Manager, you will be in charge of managing all aspects of the F&amp;B operations within the Hotel. You will be responsible to control budgets, analyse current operations, promote the company&#x2019;s products and participate actively in...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14734/food-beverage-operations-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Hospitality &amp; Leisure</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 11:47:12 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Compliance Officer</title>
        <description>Our client, a dynamic&#xA0;electronic payment solutions company, is currently in the process of seeking to employ a Compliance Officer to join their team.

Compliance Officer
MT 4198/16

In this role, you will form part of a team and will be reporting to the Head of Compliance. Your responsibilities will include conducting KYC, KYB, and PEP checks, AML checks, assisting in investigations,&#xA0;and reporting any suspicious activity to authorities. You will also be responsible for internal and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14745/compliance-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Other</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 10:16:51 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Pension Scheme Administrator</title>
        <description>Our client operates within the financial services and they&#xA0;are a well known retirement scheme administrator. Due to growth, they are&#xA0;currently looking to recruit a Junior Pensions Scheme&#xA0;Administrator to join their team of professionals.

Junior Pension Scheme Administrator

MT 8731/16

In this role you will assist with the day-to-day administration duties such as collating supporting documentation for application forms and for compliance processes. You will need to accurately upload...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14741/junior-pension-scheme-administrator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Other</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 08:58:22 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Corporate Administrator</title>
        <description>Our client provide corporate management services to help maximise efficiency and productivity. They&#xA0;serve&#xA0;more than 100 multinational companies that act in fields including real estate, construction, banking, oil and gas, telecommunications and private equity. Due to growth, they are currently looking to recruit a Corporate Administrator to join their team.

Corporate Administrator

MT 7431/16

As a Corporate Administrator you will handle and process administrative matters relating to...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14740/corporate-administrator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Corporate Services</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2016 08:50:27 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Accounts Clerk</title>
        <description>Our client is one of the leading law firms in Malta specializing within the financial services. They are currently seeking to recruit a Junior Accounts Clerk to join their team of professionals.

Junior Accounts Clerk
MT 5897/16

As a Junior Accounts Clerk you shall be working closely with the Director and be responsible a variety of accounting duties, up to the compilation and extraction of trial balance. You shall ensure proper inputting of all transactions and invoices and maintain...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14650/junior-accounts-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 16:56:53 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Financial Services Lawyer</title>
        <description>Our client is a boutique law firm with a strong international client base operating primarily within investment services. They are currently looking to recruit a Junior Financial Services Lawyer to join their team.

Junior Financial Services Lawyer
MT 3064/16

As a Junior Financial Services Lawyer you shall be working within the legal advisory and&#xA0;structuring team of the firm and you shall be dealing with company incorporations, licensing of investment services providers and assisting...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14649/junior-financial-services-lawyer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Legal</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 16:48:46 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accountant (Insurance)</title>
        <description>Our client is a captive reinsurer operating locally and forming part of a larger group. They are currently seeking to recruit an Accountant to join the team.

Accountant
MT 9812/16

As an Accountant you shall be responsible for ensuring and maintaining proper accounting records and the preparation of the company&amp;#39;s monthly management accounts and&#xA0;statutory financial statements. You shall produce reports on a monthly and quarterly basis and handle all regulatory reporting, both to the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14738/accountant-insurance</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 16:18:28 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>IT Business Partner</title>
        <description>Our client is a well known international company&#xA0;operating&#xA0;within the manufacturing industry. They are currently looking to recruit an IT Business Partner to join their team.&#xA0;

IT Business Partner
MT 6503/16

Reporting to the Lead IT Business Partner, and working in the Service Delivery team, &#xA0;you will primarily be responsible to provide end user clients with support and maintenance. Responding to client, issues, installing, diagnosing, repairing, maintaining and upgrading PC software...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14737/it-business-partner</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 15:48:31 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Corporate Services Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is a reputable organisation operating within the Financial Services industry. They are seeking to recruit a Senior Corporate Services&#xA0;Executive to join their team.

Senior Corporate Services Executive
MT 7164/16

As a&#xA0;Senior Corporate Services&#xA0;Executive you shall be working within the corporate services department and you&#xA0;shall be responsible for handling a portfolio of international clients with local and international entities set up. You shall be a point of contact for...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14736/senior-corporate-services-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Corporate Services</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 14:50:57 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Documentation Clerk</title>
        <description>Our client is an establish Forwarding &amp; Logistics company, offering a number of transportation services. &#xA0;They are currently seeking to recruit a Documentation Clerk to join their on growing team.

Documentation Clerk
MT 4858/16

As a Documentation Clerk you will be assisting and supporting Shipping Line Managers by preparing necessary documentation for imported and exported goods. Within this post you will be responsible for inputting and issuing respective documentation such as...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14720/documentation-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 13:45:44 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Project Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is a very well established and prestigious&#xA0;commercial organisation operating also&#xA0;in the construction industry. They are now looking to implement their team hiring a Project Manager.

Project Manager
MT 9374/16

In the role of Project Manager you will take care of new building construction&#xA0;as well as restoration projects. You will be responsible to plan construction projects and oversee their progress in a timely and cost-effective manner liaising with design professionals,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14657/project-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Construction</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 12:08:49 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading organisation operating within the education &amp; tourism industry. They are&#xA0;currently seeking to recruit a&#xA0;Financial Controller.

Financial Controller
MT 7306/16

Reporting to the General manager&#xA0;you will be&#xA0;responsible for the day to day financial management of the company. As the head of department, you will&#xA0;lead the finance&#xA0;team and ensure&#xA0;that the company is in compliance with accounting principles and in line with&#xA0;legal fiscal requirements and established...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14668/financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 17:13:29 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Statistics &amp; Research Manager </title>
        <description>Our client, a national authority in Malta are currently looking to recruit a Statistics &amp; Research Manager to join their team of professionals.

Statistics &amp;&#xA0;Research Manager
MT 0296/16

As Statistics &amp; Research Manager, managing a team of statisticians, you will be called to provide technical assistance to other units within the authority. You will be overseeing various data collection,&#xA0;methodology and quality aspects of the process require to produce high quality analysis and data....</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14661/statistics-research-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Other</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 17:03:28 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Administrative Assistant</title>
        <description>Our client is a renewable energy solutions company specializing in domestic and commercial photovoltaic (PV) installations. They are currently seeking a Administrative Assistant &#xA0;to join their team.

Administrative Assistant
MT 3964/16

Working closely with the Managing Director Personal Assistant, you will be responsible for assisting with the day to day administrative duties required to ensure the smooth running of office . This will include handling telephone calls, walking in...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14729/administrative-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 15:26:39 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Finance and Administrator Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is a bank that is operating in Malta and would like to have a Finance &amp; Administration Officer join their team.

Finance &amp; Administration Officer
MT 3168/16

You will be in charge of drafting and executing advisory agreements and maintaining financial advisory project control registers. As the Finance &amp; Administration Officer, you will review monthly accounting,&#xA0;prepare the monthly management accounts and the&#xA0;annual financial statements. &#xA0;You will also&#xA0;be involved in audit...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14652/finance-and-administrator-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 13:46:49 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Group Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is a multinational company operating in more than 30 countries, offering a diversified product portfolio to corporate clients. They are now seeking to recruit a Senior Group&#xA0;Accountant to form part of a group wide function based in Malta.

Senior Group Accountant
MT 1713/16

As a Senior Group Accountant you shall form part of the&#xA0;Group&amp;#39;s Commercial Operations Team in Malta which is responsible for the Group&amp;#39;s commercial, financial and sales operations. You shall be...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14651/senior-group-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 12:35:23 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Marketing Executive</title>
        <description>Our client, a group of companies leading some of Malta&#x2019;s most reputable fashion shops, domestic design brands and outdoor publishing.

Marketing Executive
MT 0969/16

Reporting to the Manager Director you will be responsible to perform marketing research aimed at identifying new products and services.&#xA0;&#xA0;You will also be in charge of both internal and external communication including social media, press releases and updating websites.&#xA0;Duties will also include the management of the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14726/marketing-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Oct 2016 10:10:05 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Corporate Services Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is a prestigious law firm with a solid reputation, operating across a number of different areas within the financial services industry for a vast portfolio of local and international clients. They are currently seeking to recruit a Corporate Services Executive to join their team.

Corporate Services Executive
MT 9269/16

As a Corporate Services Executive you shall form part of a small team and report to the partner in charge of the unit. You shall be responsible for executing...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14724/corporate-services-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Corporate Services</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 16:54:54 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Clerk</title>
        <description>Our client provides an extensive range of professional security services for a various number of clients. Due to growth, they are seeking to recruit an Accounts Clerk to join their team of professionals.

Accounts Clerk
MT 0454/16

The successful candidate will be assisting the Financial Controller on basic day to day bookkeeping duties. These duties will include, the inputting and posting of invoices, bank reconciliations, maintaining accounting records, chasing debtors and assisting...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14723/accounts-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 16:45:36 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Clerk</title>
        <description>Our client operate within the Yachting industry and have been in operation since 1976. Currently they are looking to recruit an Accounts Clerk to join their team.

Accounts Clerk

MT 9004/16

As an Accounts Clerk, you will be reporting to the Financial Controller and you will be responsible for the accounting and&#xA0;bookkeeping&#xA0;duties such as posting of invoices, reconciliations,&#xA0;maintaining ledgers,&#xA0;creditors, debtors, inputting payments, maintaining stock, and even assisting in...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14722/accounts-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 16:23:13 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounting Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is an Insurance company that is part of a Group and they would like to add an Accounts Officer to their team.

Accounting Officer
MT 5135/16 

You will be reporting directly to the Chief Financial Controller (CFO).&#xA0; You will be conducting financial record keeping but not limited&#xA0;to that, income and expenditure, payroll and other financial transactions and posting to ledgers. In addition, you will be preparing the monthly management accounts and assisting in the regulatory...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14653/accounting-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 14:47:16 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Compliance Manager &amp; MLRO</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-known and established bank in Malta. They are currently in the process of seeking to recruit a Compliance Manager to join their Compliance department.&#xA0;

Compliance Manager &amp; MLRO
MT 7058/16

In this role, you will be reporting to the Head of Compliance and you will also act as MLRO. You will assist the Head of Compliance in the preparation and implementation of policies,&#xA0;procedures, systems, and controls&#xA0;related to financial crime, such as AML, CTF, ABC, and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14617/compliance-manager-mlro</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Banking</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 12:07:58 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Import/ Export Manager - Chinese (mandarin)</title>
        <description>Our client, an internationally recognised brand, represented in 46 countries on 5 continents&#xA0;are currently in the process of opening their offices in Malta. They are looking to employ an&#xA0;Import/ Export Manager - Chinese (mandarin)&#xA0;to join their team here in Malta.

Import/ Export Manager - Chinese (mandarin)
MT 1640/16

As the&#xA0;Import/ Export Manager you will be responsible for the daily&#xA0;global operations and&#xA0;logistics by air and ocean freight. You will also be responsible for customs...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14707/import-export-manager-chinese-mandarin</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Supply Chain, Transport &amp; Warehousing</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 11:22:35 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Compliance Officer - Banking</title>
        <description>Our client is a company within the banking industry who is currently looking for the services of an Compliance Officer to join their dynamic team.

Compliance Officer

MT 6396/16

The successful candidate within this role will be you will be responsible for meeting with potential customers of the bank, liaising with clients and ensuring their satisfaction. You will be responsible for creating and updating policies and procedures to ensure compliance with current and new legislation,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14719/compliance-officer-banking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Banking</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 11:20:46 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Office Clerk</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading organisation offering corporate and advisory services to a portfolio of international clientele. They are currently seeking to recruit an Office Clerk to join their dynamic team.

Office Clerk
MT 3172/16

Working closely with the Office Manager, you will be responsible for assisting with the day to day administrative duties required to ensure the smooth running of office. As an Office Clerk you will be responsible for handling telephone calls, opening, sorting...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14717/office-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2016 11:02:39 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>First Line Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client is an international company providing&#xA0;unrivalled levels of business and IT support.&#xA0;Their success is derived from their dedication and focus to deliver a high quality service at all times. As a result of growth, they are currently seeking the services of a Software Support Engineer to join their multicultural team.

First Line Engineer
MT&#xA0;&#xA0;7787/16

Within this role, you will be responsible to resolve and manage technical support for customers on software issues, gather,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14716/first-line-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 17:55:39 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Front End Developer</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading provider of affiliate marketing software who powers some of the industry&amp;#39;s most successful and high volume affiliate programs by providing a single centralised complete solution. It is currently seeking to recruit a Front End Developer on a full-time basis.

Front End Developer
MT 2595/16

Reporting to the R&amp;D Manager, you will act as a software architect from a front-end perspective and work closely with the product management team to ensure that business...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12574/front-end-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2016 15:24:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Data Quality Process Analyst</title>
        <description>Our client is a prominent company operating within the iGaming industry. They are currently looking to recruit a Data Quality Process Analyst&#xA0;to&#xA0;join their dynamic team on full time basis.

Data Quality Process Analyst (Intermediate level)
MT 4200/16

As a Data Quality Process Analyst you will support the development and maintenance of data quality framework such as data quality standards and processes. You will be responsible to:

Ensure that all data r&#xA0;received from multiple data...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14711/data-quality-process-analyst</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 12:33:55 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Sales and Design Consultant</title>
        <description>Our client is a renowned, fast growing organisation and one of the leaders within the retail furniture sector. Their success is attributed to a team of professionals who have a strong customer focus and true dedication to exceed their client&amp;#39;s needs. They are currently seeking the recruitment of Sales and Design Consultant to join their dynamic team.

Sales and Design Consultant
MT 4169/16

Working within a team you will be responsible for selling furniture solutions and advising on...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14710/sales-and-design-consultant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 11:49:30 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Data Warehouse Developer -  Data Quality &amp; Troubleshooting (Junior/Intermediate level)</title>
        <description>Our client is a prominent company operating within the iGaming industry. They are currently looking to recruit a Data Warehouse Developer focusing on Quality &amp; Troubleshooting&#xA0;to&#xA0;join their dynamic team on full time basis.

Data Warehouse Developer - &#xA0;Data Quality &amp; Troubleshooting
MT 8652/16

Working close within the Data Quality and Troubleshooting team, you will be responsible to provide 2nd line support and to ensure that incidents are resolved within defined resolution timescales...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14705/data-warehouse-developer-data-quality-troubleshooting-junior-intermediate-level</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 10:20:36 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Data Warehouse Developer</title>
        <description>Our client is a prominent company operating within the iGaming industry. They are currently looking to recruit a Data Warehouse Developer&#xA0;to&#xA0;join their dynamic team on full time basis.

Data Warehouse Developer
MT 2619/16

Working in a team of Data Warehouse and BI specialists you will be responsible for the development of different solutions. While understanding the business needs you will be designing and developing the data warehouse platform and provide respective reports and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14704/data-warehouse-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 09:45:18 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Production Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-established customer-centred company operating within the manufacturing industry. They are currently seeking to recruit a Production Engineer to join their tight-knit team.

Production Engineer
MT 0657/16

As Production Engineer, you will work closely and provide assistance to the Operations Manager in coordinating the safe and efficient operation of the company&#x2019;s plant operations. You will be responsible for calculating the production rate, while ensuring that the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14624/production-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2016 07:46:07 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Supply Chain Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is an international company with strong presence in Malta. They are&#xA0;presently seeking to recruit a Purchasing Executive&#xA0;to join their dynamic team.

Supply Chain Officer
MT 3221/16

In this role you will be responsible for reviewing weekly stock levels and calculate new requirements. You will take care of the inbound transportation planning, communicate supplies forecasts with other departments, data inputting, evaluate the supply plan, and create purchase orders.

The...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14701/supply-chain-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Supply Chain, Transport &amp; Warehousing</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2016 15:56:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Accounts Clerk</title>
        <description>Our client is an established operator in the Hospitality industry.&#xA0;Due to growth, they are seeking to recruit a Junior Accounts Clerk to join their team of professionals.

Junior Accounts Clerk
MT 7641/16

As a Junior Accounts Clerk your responsibilities will include administering accounting records, posting of&#xA0;transactions and the&#xA0;preparation and checking of sales invoices.

This post calls for an individual who has an Advanced level of education in Accounting and a minimum of two...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14670/junior-accounts-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 17:46:03 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Software Developer (C#)</title>
        <description>Our client is an established financial investment company who is seeking to recruit a Junior Software Developer to join their team.

Junior Software Developer (C#)&#xA0;
MT&#xA0;3112/16

Reporting directly to the IT manager, your responsibilities will include re-writing all in-house software and will be mainly working on C# and MsSQL. Here, you will be mainly responsible to ensure that the company&#x2019;s system is tailored for business growth as well as for ensuring that code reflects industry&#x2019;s best...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14669/junior-software-developer-c</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 16:47:43 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Executive </title>
        <description>Our client is a well-established industry service provider looking to compliment their accounts team with an Accounts Officer.

MT 2811/16
Accounts Executive&#xA0;

In this role you will be reporting to the Finance Manager and you will be working within a small yet dynamic accounts team. You will be responsible for the inputting of the&#xA0;day-to-day accounting entries together with the&#xA0;maintenance of&#xA0;accounts up to trial balance. You will also be assisting in the preparation and upkeep of the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14666/accounts-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 12:15:39 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>C# Developer</title>
        <description>Our client, a fast growing software development company, is seeking an exceptional talented and ambitious C# Developer to joint its team.&#xA0;

C# Developer
MT 7690/16

Reporting directly to the director, you must be a great team player and able to develop clean and well-engineered code that conforms to high standards. You will be developing exceeding applications for a range of international clients coming from diverse industries and be expected to make a difference in day-to-day tasks. In...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14664/c-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 12:05:24 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client&amp;#39;s operations have been established for over a 100 years, and they have diversified operations within the retail and catering industry. They are currently seeking to recruit an Accountant to join their team of professionals.

Accountant
MT 9905/16

The successful candidate will be working in a team of 5 Accountants and reporting to the Group Financial Controller. You will be responsible for the preparation of management accounts and financial reporting.&#xA0;In addition you...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14640/accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Oct 2016 09:57:57 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Facility Manager</title>
        <description>Our client aims to become one of the leading homes for the elderly in Malta and would require the services of a Facilty Manager to join their team.

Facility Manager
MT 9033/16

You&#xA0;will be reporting into the Managing Director&#xA0; and will be running the operations of the home which tasks include the management of the home including rooms maintenance and upkeep, HR Management and any other related tasks&#xA0;like Health &amp; Safety.&#xA0;As the Facilities Manager you&#xA0;will also ensure budget keeping and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14644/facility-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 22:05:34 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Draughtsperson </title>
        <description>Our client specialises in designing and developing equipment for the business services industry and are seeking to recruit a Draughtsperson.&#xA0;

MT 7267/16
Draughtsperson&#xA0;

As a Draughtsperson your responsibilities will be to go on site in order to take specific measurements and develop&#xA0;rough sketches and specifications in order to design plans using computer-aided design and drafting software. You will have the ability to&#xA0;come up with solutions and present multiple designs for review,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14645/draughtsperson</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Creative &amp; Design</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 16:19:46 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Building Services Assistant Engineer </title>
        <description>Our client specialises in designing and developing equipment for the business services industry and are seeking to recruit a Building Services Assistant Engineer.&#xA0;

Building Services Assistant Engineer&#xA0;
MT 0952/16

As a Building Services Assistant Engineer you will form part of a dynamic team of experts and be responsible for M&amp;E&#xA0;works from organising tenders and BOQs&#xA0;to&#xA0;designing&#xA0;M&amp;E systems. Other duties would also consist of going on site in order to inspect the installations and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14647/building-services-assistant-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 16:17:55 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Planning and Decision Support Manager</title>
        <description>Our client an international organisation operating within the communications industry is presently seeking to recruit a Financial Planning and Decision Support Manager.&#xA0;

Financial Planning and Decision Support Manager
MT 2040/16

In this role, you&#xA0;will be responsible for the financial support of strategic initiatives and transforming strategic objectives into the planning and budget process, performing financial analysis and investment appraisals, and supporting the different...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14660/financial-planning-and-decision-support-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 15:41:24 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Java Developer</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading open source&#xA0;platform&#xA0;provider who is seeking to recruit a Java Developer to join their dynamic team.

Java Developer
MT&#xA0;6831/16

As a software developer you will be responsible for understanding requirements, design, development, testing, debugging, and consulting clients within a team.&#xA0;&#xA0;You will also be responsible for the documentation of policies and procedures, and also the development, monitoring, and maintenance of systems.

The ideal candidate must...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14659/java-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 15:40:47 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>HR Manager</title>
        <description>Our client, a leading growing organisation operating within the education and tourism industry is currently seeking to recruit an HR Manager.

HR Manager
MT 9559/16

Reporting to the General Manager, as an HR Manager you will be responsible for the HR function for the company. You will handle the recruitment and selection process, maintain and update policies and procedures and the employee handbook, training and monitor strategy for benefits and contractual obligations. Other duties...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14658/hr-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 15:15:17 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Business Development Executive (Financial Services)</title>
        <description>Our client, a growing&#xA0;international company operating in the asset management sector, mainly&#xA0;offering&#xA0;consulting and accounting services, is currently in the process of seeking to employ a Business Development Executive to join their Malta office.&#xA0;

Business Development Executive (Financial Services)
MT 2581/16

In this role, you will be responsible for the process from identifying a sale to closing the sale with new and existing clients, preparing&#xA0;sales proposals and working closely...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14656/business-development-executive-financial-services</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 11:31:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Office Administrator/Receptionist</title>
        <description>Our client a successful translation and proofreading services provider is currently seeking&#xA0;to recruit an Office Administrator/Receptionist to join their dynamic team.

Office Administrator/Receptionist
MT 6382/16

As an Office Administrator/Receptionist, primarily you will be responsible for offering administrative support to the team, within an&#xA0;office structure. You will be handling all front office operations, such as answering the phones, taking care of correspondence, filing,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14655/office-administrator-receptionist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 10:00:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Systems Administrator</title>
        <description>Our client, an established company providing financial services to both local and international clients, is currently seeking to recruit a Systems Administrator to join their team of professionals

Systems Administrator
MT&#xA0;1560/16

As a Systems Administrator you will be responsible for offering remote support to various branch operations. Your duties will include designing the infrastructure, installing, configuring, maintaining and monitoring the servers, networks and network security...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14654/systems-administrator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 16:27:11 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Fraud Analyst</title>
        <description>Our client is a payment gateway provider and they&#xA0;are seeking to recruit a Fraud Analyst to join their team of professionals.

Fraud Analyst
MT 5037/16

The successful candidate will be reporting to the Fraud Manager and working as part of a team. You will be responsible for identifying high risk transactions within their business portfolio. You will need to&#xA0;monitor&#xA0;customer transactions in order to identify fraudulent activity, initiate fraud investigation cases, document and maintain...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14444/fraud-analyst</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2016 06:57:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Software Engineer (Java) </title>
        <description>Our client is an established and highly successful organisation within their technical industry. They are currently looking to expand their technical team by recruiting a Software Engineer.

Software Engineer (Java)&#xA0;
MT 2060/16

Reporting to the Network Service Assurance Manager, you will be responsible for the design and implementation of software support tools utilised to monitor and maintain the network infrastructure. Additionally, you will conduct acceptance testing, modifications...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14642/software-engineer-java</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 10:36:44 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Trusts Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading and prestigious business law firm servicing a substantial local and international client base. They are looking to recruit a Junior Trusts Officer&#xA0;to join their growing team.

Junior Trusts Officer
MT 8166/16
&#xA0;

As a Junior Trusts Officer you will be responsible for the administration of trusts. You will assist with the drafting of deeds, resolutions and other documents and collate other documentation such as client due diligence. You will also communicate...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14629/junior-trusts-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Finance</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2016 08:52:43 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Job Coach</title>
        <description>Our client&#xA0;whose initiative is to encourage companies to create greater employment opportunities for vulnerable groups in Malta &amp; Gozo are seeking to employ a Job Coach

MT 7368/16
Job Coach

The Job Coach will provide support and coaching to youths or adults with a disability when there is the opportunity for them to be employed. This will serve as further assistance to individuals to facilitate the transition and integration into the work environment. Within this position you will...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14631/job-coach</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Education &amp; Training</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 15:16:04 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Finance Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is a new Healthcare organization with an international footprint. They&#xA0;will be refurbishing, constructing and&#xA0;managing three major hospitals around&#xA0;Malta. Currently they are looking to recruit a Finance Manager&#xA0;to join their team.

Finance Manager

MT 4662/16

As a Finance Manager you will report to the Financial Controller and will be involved in the oversight of the financial position and obligations of the company. You will be responsible for&#xA0;presenting and reporting...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14630/finance-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 14:09:46 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Customer Service Assistant Manager</title>
        <description>Our client,&#xA0;a leading international gaming company with offices in Malta, is&#xA0;currently seeking to employ a Customer Service Assistant Manager.

Customer Service Assistant Manager
MT 8673/16

As Customer Service Assistant Manager you will be responsible for managing a team of Customer Service Team leaders and running the day-to-day Customer Service Operations. Within this position you must commit to observing, supporting effective decisions with the aim of improving Customer Service&#x2019;s...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14469/customer-service-assistant-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Customer Service</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 12:26:44 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Customer Service Team Leader (Shift Basis)</title>
        <description>Our client,&#xA0;a leading international gaming company with offices in Malta, is&#xA0;currently seeking to employ a Customer Service Team Leader&#xA0;to join their Malta operation due to growth.

Customer Service Team Leader (Shift Basis)
MT 0750/16

As a Customer Service Team Leader you will be responsible for managing a team of Customer Service Operators and the day to day running of the Customer Service Operation. You will be responsible for managing and improving the performance of team members,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14342/customer-service-team-leader-shift-basis</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Customer Service</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 12:25:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>HR Executive</title>
        <description>Our Client is&#xA0;a&#xA0;local renowned well established Group of Companies, is seeking to recruit an&#xA0;HR Executive to join their&#xA0;Team.

HR Executive
MT 8514/16

You will be acting as a point of reference and advisor to employees on day to day HR issues. In this role, you will also need to identify training and development needs, participate and lead the employee recruitment process and actively&#xA0;lead the implementation of business changes and initiatives that&#xA0;have an impact on employees ensuring...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14611/hr-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 08:47:03 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Foreman</title>
        <description>Our client is a very well established and prestigious&#xA0;commercial organisation operating also&#xA0;in the construction industry. They are now looking to implement their team hiring a Foreman.

Foreman
MT 8469/16

As a Foreman you will be responsible for organising and supervising day-to-day operations. Reporting to the Senior Projects&#x2019; Manager you will be responsible to motivate and control the personnel; you will make sure that&#xA0;the equipment and the materials are being used in the most...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14189/foreman</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Construction</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Sep 2016 16:54:49 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Brand Sales Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is an established and one of the leaders in the local media sector and is currently looking for a Brand Sales Executive to join their continuously growing team.

Brand Sales Executive
MT0340/16

Reporting to the Head of Sales as a Brand Sales Executive you will be managing and targeting current and sourcing new potential clients. You will work in an office environment, whilst maintaining different brands and portfolios varying from digital products and magazines.

The...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14619/brand-sales-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 16:41:27 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Assistant to the Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client, an established organisation operating within the aviation industry, is currently seeking to recruit an Assistant Financial Controller to join their team of professionals.

Assistant to the Financial Controller
MT 3513/16

The successful candidate will be part of the Finance Department, and will be responsible for monitoring stock taking procedures, preparing monthly management accounts and quarterly reports, preparing budgets and cash flow projections and&#xA0;assisting in the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14610/assistant-to-the-financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 16:30:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Group Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading group of companies&#xA0;operating within the automotive industry, with a solid reputation. They are currently seeking to employ a Group Financial Controller to join them.

Group Financial Controller
MT 0508/16

As Group Financial Controller you shall report directly to the Managing Director and you shall be responsible for managing a team of around 10 people. Your primary focus shall be leading and managing financial reporting and control, by improving processes and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14614/group-financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 15:39:39 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Network Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client is an established provider that offers IT Enterprise Solutions and Services. They are currently looking to recruit a Network&#xA0;Engineer to expand their dynamic team.

Network&#xA0;Engineer
MT 1685/16

Working closely with a team of Network&#xA0;Engineers, you will participate in designing of networks and security systems, implementing and maintaining network performance, monitoring and identifying bottlenecks, and to offer solutions to enhance services. You will also be responsible for...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14613/network-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 12:54:58 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Office Assistant</title>
        <description>Our client a&#xA0;firm whom offers a wide range of professional services,&#xA0;Including Audit, Accountancy and Tax are seeking to recruit a Personal Assistant.

Office Assistant
MT 0513/16

Reporting to the owner of the firm, as a &#xA0;Personal&#xA0;Assistant your responsibilities will be for,&#xA0;&#xA0;updating and maintaining client electronic database, filing of client documents and the upkeep of client KYC documentation. You will also be required to deliver VAT and Tax&#xA0;documents to the MFSA, along with other...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14612/office-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 11:32:19 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Mechanical/Electrical Engineering Technician</title>
        <description>Mechanical/Electrical Engineering Technician
MT 9258/16

We are currently in the process of meeting Mechanical and Electrical Engineering Technicians to work in different industries in Malta.

If you possess an Advanced Diploma or Higher National Diploma in Mechanical and/or Electrical Engineering (MQF Level 5) we are interested in meeting and assist you.&#xA0;As an Electrical Engineering Technician preferably you will be in possession of a Wireman License A and B.

As a Mechanical and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14586/mechanical-electrical-engineering-technician</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Manufacturing</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2016 10:08:25 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client, a&#xA0;well established name in the hospitality industry is currently seeking to recruit a Financial Controller.

Financial Controller
MT 1973/16

Reporting to the Chief Executive Officer, you will be responsible for the accounting and procurement departments. manage personnel and HR relations, monitor the IT Department and maintain an effective internal control system overall. As a Financial Controller you will compile&#xA0;monthly and timely Management Accounts including analysis...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14609/financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2016 12:15:48 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Manager - Parts Department (Gozo)</title>
        <description>Our client is one of the leading car dealers/importers in Gozo and is seeking the services of a Junior Manager to assist in the running of the business.

Junior Manager - Parts Department (Gozo)
MT 7453/16

You will be visiting auto mechanics to offer a range of automotive spare parts that the company imports and seek ways of creating a good relationship with them in the name of the company.&#xA0;&#xA0;You will be the point of contact for any&#xA0;requests/sales&#xA0;arising&#xA0;from these mechanics. &#xA0;As the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14606/junior-manager-parts-department-gozo</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 14:49:31 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior .NET Developer</title>
        <description>Our client, one of the leading financial services company&#xA0;in Malta, is seeking to recruit a talented individual to join their team of professionals as a Junior .NET Developer.

Junior .NET Developer
MT&#xA0;2992/16

This role calls for a graduate who will be reporting to the Software Development Manager, where you will assist in tasks along the entire SDLC, and will be responsible to suggest improvements and maintain the company&#x2019;s solutions. You will be responsible to build and maintain...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14601/junior-net-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2016 11:27:10 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Sales Assistant</title>
        <description>Our client is an established International company representing leading fashion branded accessories&#xA0;in Malta focused on offering high quality products and services. They are currently seeking a Sales Assistant to work in one of their outlets.

Sales Assistant&#xA0;
MT 3944/16

As &#xA0;Sales Assistant you will be responsible for the efficient day-to-day running of the outlet whilst providing excellent customer service and keeping abreast with new product launches and products available.Your...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14588/sales-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 17:14:26 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Quantity Surveyor </title>
        <description>Our client,&#xA0;a leading player operating&#xA0;within the construction industry and specialized in Civil Engineering,&#xA0;is presently looking for a Quantity Surveyor to join the team.

Quantity Surveyor 
MT 7691/16

As a Quantity Surveyor you will be&#xA0;reporting directly to the Commercial Manager and&#xA0;working closely with the Project Management and Tendering Units where you will be handling estimates and quotes while adhering with quantity surveying processes. You will also be required to prepare...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14592/quantity-surveyor</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2016 08:36:22 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Channel Management Senior Executive</title>
        <description>Our client, an international organisation with a strong local presence within the telecommunications industry, is currently seeking to recruit a Channel Management Senior Executive to join their dynamic team.

Channel Management Senior Executive
MT 2788/16

As a Channel Management Senior Executive, you will be &#xA0;involved at a strategic level to identify best practices and drive the Sales function forward. &#xA0;In your role you will liaise closely with management as well as team members,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14577/channel-management-senior-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 17:08:24 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Accounts Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is a group of companies and operates within four core sectors, which include, Hospitality, Development, Healthcare and Tourism. Due to growth, they are seeking to recruit a Senior&#xA0;Accounts Executive&#xA0;to join their Finance Team.

Senior Accounts Executive
MT 1495/16

Reporting to the Finance Controller, in this Role you will perform accounting duties such&#xA0;as&#xA0;ledger postings,&#xA0;bank &amp; account reconciliations,&#xA0;credit control and report up to Trial Balance stage. This role will also...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14591/senior-accounts-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 16:20:23 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Delivery Person</title>
        <description>Our client, a key player in the wholesale and retail sector, are currently seeking to recruit a Delivery Person to join their on growing team.

Delivery Person
MT 2965/16

Within this position you will be primarily responsible for the loading/unloading and distribution of goods to the company&amp;#39;s clients spread across Malta and Gozo. Other duties will also include promoting&#xA0;and briefly introducing&#xA0;new products and services on offer to customers, collecting payment upon delivery,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14583/delivery-person</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Supply Chain, Transport &amp; Warehousing</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2016 09:08:18 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Client Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client was established in 1991 and offers a wide range of accountancy services. Due to company growth they are currently looking to employ the a accountant to join their team of professionals.

Accountant

MT 9955/16

In this role, you will be responsible for the accounting of a portfolio of clients, ongoing day to day client support, the preparation of Financial statements, management accounts and VAT compliance.

You will need be in possession of a recognized accountancy...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14585/client-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 13:16:01 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Fraud Team Leader (Gaming)</title>
        <description>Our client is a well established gaming company providing a diverse product range. They are currently seeking to recruit a Fraud Team Leader to join their team.

Fraud Team Leader (Gaming)
MT 8495/16

As Fraud Team Leader you shall be reporting to the Fraud Manager and you shall be supervising a team of Fraud Analysts, including the shift leaders. You shall lead, develop and motivate team members to ensure the overall business objectives are achieved. You shall be responsible for...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14584/fraud-team-leader-gaming</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Gaming</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 13:11:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Software Developer (PHP/Python)</title>
        <description>Our client, a Maltese start-up company working within the consumer insurance market, is currently seeking to grow their product base and resources. They are currently seeking a&#xA0;Senior Software Developer.

Senior Software Developer
MT 2896/16

As a software developer you will be working on the internal company&#x2019;s product. You will be responsible to write thoughtful code and make sound architectural decisions. You will work on an interdisciplinary team to translate company goals into...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14580/senior-software-developer-php-python</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 10:07:04 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Talent Acquisition Specialist</title>
        <description>Our client,&#xA0;a leading international gaming company with offices in Malta, is&#xA0;currently seeking to employ a Talent Acquisition Specialist to join their dynamic team.

Talent Acquisition Specialist
MT 0790/16

As a Talent Acquisition Specialist you will be working closely with Hiring Managers and HR Business Partners. You will be responsible for sourcing candidates and providing a tailored candidate shortlist for specific recruitment assignments, building relationships with candidates and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14568/talent-acquisition-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Sep 2016 09:37:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Auto Electrician</title>
        <description>Our client is a company operating within the transport industry. They are seeking the services of an Auto Electrician&#xA0;to join their team.

Auto Electrician

MT 6386/16

As an Auto Electrician you will be responsible for providing electrical services on vehicles, which include preventive maintenance, inspection of electrical equipment, identification of hazards and fault finding. You will also be called carrying out repairs and performing defect modification and repairs of electrical...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12689/auto-electrician</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Other</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 11:00:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Customer Service Agent - Danish or English Speaking</title>
        <description>Our client, a leading Internet Betting company is currently seeking to employ Danish or English speaking Customer Service Agents to join their Malta-based operation.

Customer Service Agent - Danish or English Speaking
MT 3793/16

In this role you will be responsible for assisting and liaising with&#xA0;customers via telephone, live chat, e-mail and social media. You will be required to listen attentively to gather all relevant information in order to assess and determine possible causes and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14567/customer-service-agent-danish-or-english-speaking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Customer Service</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 16:45:14 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>HR Officer</title>
        <description>Our client, a well-established organisation operating within the insurance industry, is currently seeking the services of an HR Assistant to join their dynamic team.

HR Assistant
MT 1486/16

In this role you will be working closely with the HR Manager, to carrying out a range of HR activities on a daily basis. This will include time and attendance, recruitment, selection and induction, training, and staff welfare. You will be working closely with all levels of the organisation both on...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14564/hr-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 16:36:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Information Security Specialist</title>
        <description>A company that offers advisory services on improving business performance and managing risks, are seeking to recruit experienced professionals that aspire to perform the work of a Information Security Specialist.

Information Security Specialist
MT 7303/16

Forming part of the Advisory team, you will be responsible for managing cyber security risks for leaders within the business and government sector. You will be liable to assist clients with internal controls, risk assurance and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14562/information-security-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 08:50:58 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Credit Executive (Banking)</title>
        <description>Izola Bank, a licensed credit institution, has been operating in Malta since 1994. The Bank&#x2019;s operations are international in nature, making extensive use of advanced ICT systems.

Credit Executive (Banking)
MT 2908/16

In this role, you will be involved in all aspects of the credit process. Duties include the review and analysis of credit applications, preparation of annual credit reviews and monitoring of credit limits and the preparation of credit related reports for internal and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14507/credit-executive-banking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Banking</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 15:29:44 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Business Implementation Consultant</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-established company with a solid local and international customer base, specialised in the provision of Business Applications and Integration Solutions (ERP, Financial Management and Enterprise Asset Management solutions).&#xA0;

Business Implementation Consultant
MT 0498/16

They are currently seeking to recruit an Implementation Consultant, which entails carrying out requirements analysis, systems design, application build and user training, as well as occasional...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14554/business-implementation-consultant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 13:04:15 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Logistics Planner</title>
        <description>Our client who is an established organisation operating within the manufacturing industry is presently seeking to recruit a Logistics Planner to join their team.

Logistics Planner
MT 5548/16

You will be dealing with all orders of the company and communicating&#xA0;with the mother company abroad on a regular basis ensuring that all orders are handled as per client request. You will&#xA0;schedule and plan inbound raw materials in line with stock requirements, outbound production schedules and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14552/logistics-planner</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Supply Chain, Transport &amp; Warehousing</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2016 11:41:19 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Systems Engineer </title>
        <description>Our client is an established and highly successful organisation within their technical industry. They are currently looking to expand their technical team by recruiting a Junior Systems&#xA0;Engineer.

Junior Systems&#xA0;Engineer&#xA0;
MT 7017/16

Reporting to the Manager Core Networks Operations, you will be responsible to maintain the current circuit switch voice services on both the Mobile and Fixed networks. You will also be liable to monitor and control the execution of installations,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14544/junior-systems-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 12:50:47 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Product Owner/Scrum Master (Gaming)</title>
        <description>Our client is an established and successful worldwide bookmaker within the gaming industry, specialising in a particular market. They are currently a team of 55 people, and are looking to grow their technical team by hiring a Front-End Developer to work on the web application and mobile optimized websites.

Product Owner/Scrum Master
MT 4720/16

Working alongside Software Developers and UX/UI Designers, you will be responsible for gathering, organising and prioritising business...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14543/product-owner-scrum-master-gaming</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2016 07:50:20 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Marketing Specialists (Telecoms)</title>
        <description>Our client, GO, are a market leader in the telecommunications industry in Malta. They are currently looking for Marketing Specialists to join their team, in order to&#xA0;fully contribute in the Marketing Segment Team, ensuring&#xA0;that GO achieves its business objectives.

Marketing Specialists&#xA0;(Telecoms)
MT 6101/16

Within this position you will actively define and develop customer propositions and / or product strategies enabling GO to win in the market and achieve its revenue and market...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14540/marketing-specialists-telecoms</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Sep 2016 14:54:44 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Software Developer (C#/Java)</title>
        <description>Our client, a&#xA0;research oriented innovator with a unique product line up is current seeking to recruit a Software Developer to strengthen its R&amp;D team

Software Developer&#xA0;
MT 4041/16

Working within a multidisciplinary team you will be responsible to take part in the entire development life cycle from understanding requirements, design, development, testing, debugging and releasing. Additionally, you will be responsible to write technical documentation and procedures of work. As a...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14487/software-developer-c-java</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 19:51:05 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Shift Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is one of the leading companies in the FMCG sector. &#xA0;The company is now seeking the services of a&#xA0;Shift Manager&#xA0;to join their team in one of their outlets.

Shift Manager
MT 7732/16

You&#xA0;will report into the Restaurant Manager/Assistant Restaurant Manager and will manage effectively the opening, closing and running of shifts whilst maintaining Franchise Operating Standards. As a&#xA0;shift manager, you will have various operational&#xA0;tasks and responsibilities. You&#xA0;will effectively...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14537/shift-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Hospitality &amp; Leisure</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 17:01:18 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Risk Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is a reputable licensed banking organisation&#xA0;operating with the financial services industry. They are currently seeking to recruit a Risk Manager to join their management team.

Risk Manager
MT 9252/16

As Risk Manager you will be responsible for the smooth functioning of the Risk Management Unit and you will actively contribute towards the development, implementation and updating of risk and econometric models, risk metrics, risk management tools as well as taking the lead...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13229/risk-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Banking</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2016 09:14:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Hospitality Operations Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is an established player operating in the hospitality industry. They are currently seeking an Operations Manager to join their dynamic team.

Hospitality Operations Manager
MT 7933/16

As an Operations Manager you will be responsible for the daily running of the operations related to Food and Beverage,Housekeeping&#xA0;and&#xA0;Front Office. You will be in charge of employee relations, training and development, performance management and succession planning. You will be called to...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14528/hospitality-operations-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 16:22:18 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Field Technician </title>
        <description>Our client is a key player in the automation industry. They are currently seeking to recruit two Field Technicians to join their team.

Field Technician
MT 9002/16

As a Field Technician, you will be responsible for conducting preventive and reactive maintenance work on a large SCADA based building system. Additionally, you will mainly be monitoring&#xA0;safety and security equipment&#xA0;whilst&#xA0;ensuring that regulations are respected. You will also need to ensure maximum customer satisfaction as...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14527/field-technician</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Skilled Work</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2016 12:20:23 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Operations Assistant</title>
        <description>Our client is an establish Forwarding &amp; Logistics company, offering a number of transportation services. &#xA0;They are currently looking to recruit a Operations Assistant to focus and work particularly on the company&amp;#39;s RORO.

MT 9349/16
Operations Assistant

As an Operations Assistant you will be working within a team and be responsible for the cargo operations are planned and executed with the highest efficiency. This will include, discharge and loading, on board coordination and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14521/operations-assistant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Other</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 16:53:13 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accountant - Part Time</title>
        <description>Our client is a Swiss company that provides Legal, Fiduciary and Investment Fund Services. They set up&#xA0;new operations&#xA0;in Malta and are seeking the recruit&#xA0;a&#xA0;Part Time Accountant to join their team of professionals.

Accountant - Part Time
MT 4807/16

The successful candidate will be reporting directly to the Country Manager and will essentially be running the accounts department in Malta and liaising with the accounts team in Switzerland.&#xA0;You&#xA0;will be responsible for the&#xA0;internal...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12718/accountant-part-time</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Sep 2016 09:07:24 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Finance Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is a well established, well known organisation&#xA0;that markets some of the most popular and fashionable&#xA0;retail brands. Due to growth, they are currently looking to recruit a Finance Manager&#xA0;to join their team of professionals.

Finance Manager
MT 9411/16

Reporting directly to the Head of Finance, you will be responsible for the preparation of management accounts and financial reporting.&#xA0;In addition you will also be responsible for the budgeting process, checking of the monthly...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14513/finance-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 11:46:38 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Assistant Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client hails from&#xA0;the hospitality industry having&#xA0;a number of&#xA0;leading hotels in Malta, is currently looking to employ an Assistant Financial Controller to join their Finance team.

Assistant Financial Controller
MT 2819/16

In this&#xA0;role you will also&#xA0;assist&#xA0;the Financial Controller in analyzing financial information, in preparing financial statements, financial management reports, financial audits and budgets, whilst also analyzing and advising on business operations including...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14506/assistant-financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2016 11:06:48 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Cloud Systems Specialist</title>
        <description>Our client an award winning technology company specialising in delivering web and marketing solutions are&#xA0;seeking a Cloud Systems Specialist to work closely with the in-house developers while reporting to the CTO.

Cloud Systems Specialist
MT 6977/16

The Cloud Specialist will be responsible for the provisioning, setup, documentation and configuration of the hardware and software solutions that are virtualised and hosted on cloud platforms. You will be doing 24/7 monitoring of the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14508/cloud-systems-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 15:20:47 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Development Manager (MS Dynamics CRM)</title>
        <description>Our client is a start-up consultancy and development company specialising in MS Dynamics ERP and looking to build a 5 person MS Dynamics CRM team in their local offices to work on large-scale international projects. For this reason they are looking for a Development Manager / Team Lead specialised in MS Dynamics CRM to build and manage a team of 5 developers and act as the technical point of reference for the company.

Development Manager (MS Dynamics CRM)

MT 2148/16

Reporting...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14314/development-manager-ms-dynamics-crm</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 11:47:18 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>PHP Developer</title>
        <description>Our client is a company that designs bespoke software tools for local and international clients. They are currently seeking to recruit a Junior&#xA0;Developer to join their growing team.&#xA0;

Developer (PHP/C#)&#xA0;
MT 4453/16

Working within a tight knit team, you will be primarily responsible to develop and test solutions according to clients&#x2019; expectations and requirements. In addition, you will be responsible to provide technical guidance and interact along the stages of the SDLC whilst you will...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12747/php-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2016 11:38:19 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Purchasing &amp; Stores Manager</title>
        <description>Our Client,&#xA0;a&#xA0;local renowned well established Group of Companies, is seeking to recruit a Purchasing &amp; Stores Manager&#xA0;to join their Team.

Purchasing &amp; Stores Manager
MT 9530/16

You will be coordinating all company purchases of raw materials, spare parts, marketing material, stationary, uniforms and Health &amp; Safety supplies. As the Purchasing &amp; Stores Manager you will also coordinate all shipping requirements of all the purchase and exports within the company whilst being responsible...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14496/purchasing-stores-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Supply Chain, Transport &amp; Warehousing</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 15:03:37 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Assistant to the Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client is a fast growing mobile network which optimises traffic flow for performance marketing purposes. Due to growth, they are seeking to recruit an Assistant Financial Controller to join their team.

Assistant to the Financial Controller
MT 8549/16

The successful candidate will be part of the Finance Team and working alongside the Financial Controller. You will be responsible for general daily accounting duties, such as, debtor and credit control, the posting of invoices, bank...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14493/assistant-to-the-financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Aug 2016 09:33:51 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Accountant (Italian speaking)</title>
        <description>Our client is a&#xA0;rapidly expanding&#xA0;multinational organisation operating within the retail industry both locally and at an international level. They are presently seeking to recruit a Junior Accountant&#xA0;to join their dynamic team.

Junior Accountant (Italian speaking)

MT 1384/16

Your main responsibilities will be keeping tight control of accounts and ensuring that the warehousing activities are duly inputted and kept up-to-date. Moreover you will be handling the processing of invoices,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14489/junior-accountant-italian-speaking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 13:54:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Full Stack Developer (Python &amp; JavaScript) - Remote work</title>
        <description>Our client is currently&#xA0;seeking to recruit an exceptional and ambitious&#xA0;Full Stack Developer&#xA0;who is expected to work remotely on full time basis.&#xA0;

Full Stack Developer (Python &amp; JavaScript) - Remote job
MT 3370/16

As a full stack developer you will be working on developing and improving features built primarily in JavaScript, AngularJS, Python and PostgreSQL. You will be creating production grade JavaScript and Python code and will have the opportunity to implement solutions designed...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12810/full-stack-developer-python-javascript-remote-work</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 10:52:55 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Internal Auditor</title>
        <description>Our client, a renowned organisation operating within the manufacturing industry, is currently seeking to recruit an Internal Auditor to join their Finance Team.

Internal Auditor
MT 4765/16

As an Internal Auditor you will lead and perform the full audit cycle including risk management and control management over operations&#x2019; effectiveness, financial reliability and compliance with all applicable directives and regulations. You will determine internal audit scope and develop annual...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14479/internal-auditor</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Aug 2016 10:08:22 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Test Automation Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading provider of affiliate marketing software who powers some of the industry&amp;#39;s most successful and high volume affiliate programs by providing a single centralized complete solution. They are currently seeking to recruit a Test Automation Enginner on a full-time basis.

Test Automation Engineer
MT&#xA0;1780/16

Reporting to the DevOps Manager, you will be responsible for designing, enhancing, building, testing and deploy test automation solutions and frameworks. This...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14483/test-automation-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2016 20:19:58 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Call Centre Agent</title>
        <description>Our client is a company operating within the financial services and specialising in investments. They are looking for a&#xA0;Call Centre Agent to join their team.

Call Centre Agent
MT 8117/16

You will be&#xA0;part of the Call Centre Team and will mainly be making outbound calls to customers to set&#xA0;appointments for the salespersons&#xA0;of the company. You&#xA0;will also be building your own database. Full training will be given to the ideal candidate.

You will have a&#xA0;secondary standard of education...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14362/call-centre-agent</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 11:57:17 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Front End Developer (PHP)</title>
        <description>Our client is a leader in the IT industry providing state of the art, specialized, software solutions. Their efforts are mainly on&#xA0;support and on developing high quality methodologies enabling them to attract an ever-increasing number of customers. They are currently seeking the services of a Mobile Application Developer to join their present software development team.

Mobile Application Developer
MT 8603/16

Reporting to the Head of Software Engineering, the chosen candidate will be...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14481/front-end-developer-php</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2016 09:45:19 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accountant - South of Malta</title>
        <description>Our client is a renowned operator within the power generation industry. They are currently looking to recruit an Accountant to join the Finance Department.

Accountant - South of Malta
MT 1514/16

As an Accountant your will be reporting to the Executive of Planning &amp; Finance and you shall be responsible for the preparation of the balance sheet, profit and loss statements, asset management and accounting and other ad hoc reports. You shall also be actively involved in internal controls...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14478/accountant-south-of-malta</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 14:51:28 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Web/&#xA0;Graphic Designer</title>
        <description>Our client is a young vibrant company that has grown exponentially throughout the past decade and has become a leader in its industry. Due to this continued growth, they are looking to recruit a talented designer to join their busy and hardworking team.

MT 4295/16
Web/&#xA0;Graphic Designer (Freelance)

The client is&#xA0;looking for a talented Web/ Graphic Designer to create amazing user experiences. &#xA0;Forming part of the Marketing team on a freelance basis, the successful candidate will be...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12171/web-graphic-designer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Creative &amp; Design</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2016 11:28:49 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Assistant Financial Controller (Gozo)</title>
        <description>Forming part of a group, our client is one of the leading retail operators. They are currently seeking an Assistant Financial Controller to lead the operations of their multiple retail outlets.

Assistant Financial Controller (Gozo)

MT 3614/16

Based in Gozo, you will be responsible for maintaining an accounting system ensuring accurate, efficient and cost effective management of the company&#x2019;s financial affairs. You will ensure that monthly management accounts are prepared within set...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14368/assistant-financial-controller-gozo</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2016 11:13:35 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accountant (Banking)</title>
        <description>Our client is one of the leading operators in the local banking sector, offering services to retail and corporate clients. They are&#xA0;currently seeking to strengthen operations and are looking to recruit an Accountant to join the internal accounting team.

Accountant (Banking)
MT 6708/16

As&#xA0;Accountant you will be reporting to higher management and shall be responsible for monthly management accounts, the preparation of end of year financial statements, assist in the upkeep of various...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14466/accountant-banking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 14:54:44 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Software Developer (C#)</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading provider of affiliate marketing software who powers some of the industry&amp;#39;s most successful and high volume affiliate programs by providing a single centralised complete solution. It is currently seeking to recruit a Software Developer (C#)&#xA0;on a full-time basis.

Software Developer (C#)
MT 2198/16

Reporting to the Development Manager, you will be responsible for the design, development,&#xA0;implementation and testing deployment of software solutions. You will be...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14461/software-developer-c</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Aug 2016 10:05:05 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Front Office Sales Person (Mechanical)</title>
        <description>Our client is a well-established importer and distributor of Industrial and Heavy vehicles spare parts and is looking for an Front Office Sales Person (Mechanical) to join their on growing team.

Front Office Sales Person (Mechanical)
MT 6291/16

As a Front Office Sales Person you will interface with an interesting array of clients who seek assistance on the company&#x2019;s services. Your responsibilities will include greeting walk in clients alike, attend to sales enquiries, prepare quotes...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14376/front-office-sales-person-mechanical</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Aug 2016 14:56:36 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Digital Marketing Executive</title>
        <description>KONNEKT is currently looking for a passionate, energetic and meticulous individual to join the marketing team as a Digital Marketing Executive.

&#xA0;

In this role you will be involved in maintaining the brand&#x2019;s multi-channel communication strategies and outreach initiatives by:


	
	Coordinate and implement marketing activities and projects from planning to delivery, which may include: writing and proofreading copies, liaising with designers and printers, organising photo shoots,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14442/digital-marketing-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 15:48:14 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Chief Financial Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is an established and well-renowned company within the&#xA0;FMCG industry. They&#xA0;are currently seeking a&#xA0;Chief Financial Officer to join their&#xA0;Group.&#xA0;

Chief Financial Officer
MT 7331/16

Reporting to and working closely with the CEO, the successful candidate&#xA0;&#xA0;will assume a strategic role in the overall management of the company and will be primarily accountable for the financial and business services of the group. This will include strategic and ongoing development of such...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14439/chief-financial-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 12:30:16 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Clerk</title>
        <description>Our Client; a&#xA0;local renowned well established Group of Companies, is seeking to recruit an&#xA0;Accounts Clerk&#xA0;to join their Finance Team.

Accounts Clerk
MT 9582/16

As an accounts clerk you will be working mainly on&#xA0;accounts receivable transactions; handling cash and bank transactions, post&#xA0;invoices and maintain&#xA0;proper accounting ledgers.&#xA0;&#xA0;This role will also involve other duties as may be required in order to be able to ensure the smooth running of the department.&#xA0;

The successful...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14393/accounts-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Aug 2016 15:06:32 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Executive</title>
        <description>Looking for an accounting job in Malta? Our client a leading organisation operating within the education &amp; tourism industry is currently seeking an Accounts Executive to join their Finance team.

Accounts Executive
MT 6489/16

Reporting to the Finance Manager, in this Role you will perform accounting duties such&#xA0;as&#xA0;general ledger postings, daily bank &amp; account reconciliations, issue payments, credit control and report up to Trial Balance stage. This role will also involve other duties...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14384/accounts-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2016 09:33:59 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>PA/ Administrator</title>
        <description>Our client, an established company providing financial services to both local and international clients is currently seeking to recruit a PA / Administrator&#xA0;to join their team of professionals.

PA/ Administrator
MT 9233/16

As a&#xA0;PA/ Administrator&#xA0;you will be required to devise and maintain office systems to address the needs of the unit, in conformity with the Firm&#x2019;s policies. You will&#xA0;keep databases updated, ensuring the necessary changes and amendments to data are regularly made...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14360/pa-administrator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 12:59:15 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Cost Controller</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading company that provides holistic building services solutions to an extensive customer base. They are looking to recruit a Cost Controller to join their team of professionals.&#xA0;

Cost Controller
MT 4476/16

The successful candidate will form part of the Finance Team and will mainly be responsible for monitoring and controlling the costs of continuing projects. You will also need to interpret contracts and collaborate with Project Managers in order to ensure material...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14361/cost-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 09:20:41 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Business Marketing Specialist</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading organisation that operates in the technology sector and has established a strong reputation in the local market. They are currently looking towards recruiting a Business Marketing Specialist to join their commercial team.

Business Marketing Specialist
MT 8987/16

As Business Marketing Specialist, you will be primarily responsible for identifying market needs and monitoring key competitors in order to drive product actions, promotions and campaigns. You will be...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14355/business-marketing-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2016 08:50:51 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>MEP Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client is an establish project management firm in the construction and buildings services industry with a portfolio of local and international clients. They are currently seeking to employ the services of an MEP Engineer to join their M&amp;E Department. &#xA0;

MEP Engineer - Building Services&#xA0;
MT 2638/16

The MEP Engineer will be forming part of a team of engineers, and will be responsible for the effective and economic delivery of integrated building services engineering solutions by...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14338/mep-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Construction</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2016 08:59:11 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Software Developer (.NET)</title>
        <description>Our client, a major financial services client on the Maltese market, employing more than 180 people is looking to recruit a Junior Software Developer to join their fast growing IT team.

Junior Software Developer (.NET)
MT 2911/16

Together with the team, you will be developing software by using the latest technologies to ensure that business requirements are met through your own individual effort. You will be participating in the gathering and analysis of the new system requirements...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14341/junior-software-developer-net</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Aug 2016 09:55:46 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Factory Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is a long established&#xA0;and one of the leading companies operating within the manufacturing industry,&#xA0;with a strong presence in different international. They are currently seeking the services of a dedicated individual for the post of Factory Manager to form part of their management team.

Factory Manager
MT 8754/16

Reporting to the Head of Manufacturing, you will be responsible for the general management and production of the manufacturing plant. You will be responsible for...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14335/factory-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Manufacturing</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 14:23:29 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Chief Financial Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is a fast-growing online provider of banking and investment services, serving an international client base. They are seeking to recruit a Chief Financial Officer.

Chief Financial Officer
MT 1575/16

As the Chief Financial officer (CFO) you will be responsible for establishing transparency on the Bank&amp;#39;s and its individual business&amp;#39; financial performance and propose measures for performance improvement. You will provide and analyse accurate and objective regulatory,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14321/chief-financial-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Aug 2016 09:34:17 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is a major player in the local advertising and media market. They are in the process of recruiting an&#xA0;Accounts Executive to join their Finance Team.

Accounts Executive
MT 0074/16

As an Accounts Executive you will be working alongside and reporting to the Accounting Supervisor&#xA0;and&#xA0;will be&#xA0;a key member of the Finance team. You will assume responsibilities for the day-to-day accounting activities within the department including the preparation of reconciliations, issuing of...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14302/accounts-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jul 2016 12:05:41 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Credit Controller</title>
        <description>Our client a leading organisation operating within the education &amp; tourism industry is currently seeking to recruit a Credit Controller to join their Finance team.

Credit Controller
MT 8778/16

In this role, you will be responsible for ensuring that customers pay on time, collecting payments according to the agreed terms, &#xA0;following up with debtors, maintaining records for overdue debts, and&#xA0;co-ordinating as well as updating the sales and accounts team. This role also requires...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14298/credit-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2016 12:44:24 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Software Engineer (JAVA)</title>
        <description>Our client, a leader in on-line merchant global billing services, is currently seeking to recruit a Software Engineer to join their team on full time basis.&#xA0;

Software Engineer (JAVA)

MT 2664/16

As a software Engineer you will be involved in the whole development life-cycle. You will be responsible to conduct the necessary research and to explore technology to address any given projects. You will also be involved in the analysis and design of the project and be&#xA0;expected to deliver...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12432/software-engineer-java</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 16:53:00 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Shipping Clerk</title>
        <description>Our Client is a leading Company within the FMCG arena forming part of a global group. They have an established portfolio of renowned brands and are currently seeking to recruit a Shipping Clerk.

Shipping Clerk
MT 0897/16

You will be responsible to co-ordinate shipments of materials and ensuring that all goods are delivered to the premises as planned. As the shipping clerk, you will continuously source improved shipping terms with focus on cost and transit time. You will also prepare...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14185/shipping-clerk</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 08:59:25 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Product Analyst</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading provider of affiliate marketing software who powers some of the industry&amp;#39;s most successful and high volume affiliate programs by providing a single centralised complete solution. It is currently seeking to recruit a Product Analyst&#xA0;on a full-time basis.

Product Analyst
MT 7455/16

Reporting to the Head of Product, you will be responsible for the full life cycle of the product, and adding new features by performing periodical market research and competitor...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13496/product-analyst</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2016 11:02:13 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Corporate Business Sales Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading publishing company operating within the local sector. By showing a strong commitment to quality and improvement through sound investment, the client has managed to achieve a leading position within its sector. The Company is currently seeking to recruit a Corporate Business&#xA0;Sales Executive.

Corporate Business Sales Executive
MT2351/16

As a&#xA0;Corporate Business&#xA0;Sales Executive&#xA0;you will be reporting directly to the Head of Sales and be responsible for handling...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/14165/corporate-business-sales-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 13:19:26 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Fund Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client&#xA0;is a specialist within the fund industry. Due to growth they are currently looking to recruit a Senior Fund Accountant to join their team of professionals.

Senior Fund Accountant

MT 8743/16

Reporting directly to the Team Supervisor/Manager you will be responsible for the NAV calculations on a daily, weekly, monthly or quarterly basis which include the trade capture based on Broker/Custodian statements and Investment Manager&amp;#39;s files, the reconciliation of cash...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13142/senior-fund-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Funds</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2016 13:17:37 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Front End Developer (Gaming) </title>
        <description>Our client is an established and successful worldwide bookmaker within the gaming industry, specialising in a particular market. They are currently a team of 55 people, and are looking to grow their technical team by hiring a Front-End Developer to work on the web application and mobile optimized websites.

Senior Front End Developer (Gaming)&#xA0;

MT 8739/16

Reporting to the Project Manager and working in a tight-knit team, you will be mainly responsible to enhance the desktop and mobile...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12774/senior-front-end-developer-gaming</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 16:35:39 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Recruitment Specialist - Finance &amp; Legal</title>
        <description>Building and fostering relationships is KONNEKT's guiding principle.&#xA0;Ours is not a sales-driven model of recruitment.&#xA0;We are passionate about matching the right people with the right firms, but not at the cost of the relationships with our clients. Konnekt&#x2019;s track record in serving the most demanding business and&#xA0;individuals means we enjoy the trust of both firms and candidates alike.Recruitment Specialist - Finance &amp; LegalMT 3120/15Forming part of a tight-knit team, your focus will be to...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/10940/recruitment-specialist-finance-legal</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2016 14:42:56 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Business Analyst</title>
        <description>Our client, an established IT and communications company offering high-end solutions to a variety of corporate clients, is currently recruiting a Business Analyst.

Business Analyst
MT 4674/16

As a Business Analyst you will work close to the Software Team who has extensive experience in designing and delivering highly effective Workflow and Business Process-Driven solutions with proven results. A customer centered approach is key to ensuring increased customer performance, efficiency...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13512/business-analyst</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2016 16:15:30 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Human Resources Manager</title>
        <description>Our client, an organisation renowned for providing innovative training and development products and solutions, are currently seeking to recruit an experienced Human Resources Manager to join their team of professionals.

Human Resources Manager
MT 6193/16

As HR Manager, reporting to the Managing Director, you will be responsible for participating in consultancy projects with a wide range of clients. This will include delivering a full range of HR management services, such...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12643/human-resources-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2016 14:29:43 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Client Accountant</title>
        <description>Our client is a highly reputable corporate services provider offering management, administrative and corporate services in various jurisdictions to corporate, institutional and private high net-worth and ultra-high net-worth clients. They are looking to recruit a Client Accountant to join their team in Malta.

Client Accountant
MT 3000/16

In this role you will manage a portfolio clients based in Malta as well as the Isle of Man and will handle day to day operational requirements and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12893/client-accountant</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 11:39:47 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Health Claims Handler</title>
        <description>Our client, one of the leading Insurance Agencies in Malta, is seeking to recruit a talented individual to join their team of professionals as a Health Claims Handler

Health Claims Handler
MT 1176/16

As a Health Claims Handler&#xA0;you will be assessing and settling claims directly with clients or service providers in line with the company&#x2019;s customer service standards.&#xA0;You will establish and maintain&#xA0;good relationships with all types of clients and intermediaries&#xA0;to ensure providing a...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13479/health-claims-handler</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Insurance</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2016 10:08:17 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Accountant (Marsascala)</title>
        <description>Our Client; &#xA0;is an established player in the services industry, with a strong presence in their sectors in the local market. They are currently looking to recruit&#xA0;a junior accountant to join their Finance team.

Junior Accountant (Marsascala)
MT 5233/16

As an Junior Accountant, you will perform basic accounting and book keeping duties such&#xA0;as&#xA0;general ledger postings, bank &amp; account reconciliations, issue payments, credit control and report up to Trial Balance stage. Reporting to the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13447/junior-accountant-marsascala</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2016 13:09:18 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Executive - Research &amp; Economic Affairs</title>
        <description>Our client is a legal organisation offering a range of services. They are currently looking to strengthen their team through the recruitment of a Research and Economic Affairs Executive.

Research and Economic Affairs Executive
MT 3732/16

In this challenging but rewarding role, the Research and Economic Affairs Executive&#xA0;will be responsible for planning and implementing research projects, and assess the results. Once data is collected/collated&#xA0;and reports generated and analysed, this...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13424/executive-research-economic-affairs</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Science &amp; Research</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 13:14:15 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Mechanical Engineering Technician</title>
        <description>Our client is a worldwide Oil and Petrochemical company enjoying a strong reputation through concentrated efforts and long term vision which settled them at the forefront of competition and&#xA0;are currently seeking to recruit a Mechanical Engineering Technician.

Mechanical Engineering Technician
MT 7100/16

Reporting to the Maintenance and Repairs Manager as a Mechanical Engineering Technician you will be responsible for maintaining all the maintenance of the mechanical infrastructure...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13422/mechanical-engineering-technician</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2016 10:25:50 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Trainee Store Manager</title>
        <description>Our Client is an international retail chain, currently launching a Training Program for Store Managers to join their ongoing operations.

Trainee Store Manager
MT 5171/16

As trainee store Manager, you will be employed in a 12 month training program, where you will be working in a multinational retail environment. During this employment you will be trained and supported to understand and learn the ropes behind managing a retail outlet. Within this position you will be involved in...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13412/trainee-store-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2016 08:26:17 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Customer Relationship Manager </title>
        <description>Our client is an established bank offering services to retail users and business clients. They are now looking to recruit&#xA0;a Customer Relationship Manager within its Corporate Banking Unit.

Customer Relationship Manager
MT 6340/16

As Customer Relationship Manager you&#xA0;will be responsible for building and maintaining&#xA0;a healthy portfolio of customers. You shall ensure a high and sustained level of service whilst developing and enhancing a strong relationship with them as well as with the...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13231/customer-relationship-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Banking</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 13:59:25 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Systems Engineer (Linux / Windows) </title>
        <description>Our client is a fast growing company providing specialised solutions to clients deriving from different vertical industries. They have been experiencing sustained demand growth and as a result they are seeking to recruit the services of a Systems Engineer to join their team.&#xA0;

Systems Engineer (Linux / Windows)&#xA0;

MT 9700/16

In this role, you will be responsible for the installation, configuration and maintenance of the various systems, software and other technical infrastructure that...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13204/systems-engineer-linux-windows</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 09:18:27 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Technical Sales Engineer</title>
        <description>Our client, an established IT and communications company offering high-end solutions to a variety of corporate clients, is currently recruiting a Technical Sales Engineer

Technical Sales Engineer
MT 3340/16

As a Technical Sales Engineer working in a team, you will be responsible to generate leads and close sales. You will deal and negotiate with international suppliers and maintain a good working relationship with new and existing clients. The preparation of technical quotes and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13201/technical-sales-engineer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jun 2016 17:47:23 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Project Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is an established project management firm in the construction and buildings services industry with a portfolio of local and international clients. They are currently seeking to employ the services of a Project Manager to join their team. &#xA0;

Project Manager
MT 8607/16

As a Project Manager you will be reporting to the Head of Project Management with your main responsibilities will be the planning and implementation of projects, facilitating the definition of project scope,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13171/project-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Construction</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jun 2016 21:32:36 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Technical Coordinator</title>
        <description>Our client is a worldwide Oil and Petrochemical company with a strong reputation through concentrated efforts and long term vision which settled them at the forefront of competition and&#xA0;are currently seeking to recruit a Technical Coordinator.

MT 0214/16
Technical Coordinator

As a Technical Coordinator you will be responsible for assisting and planning technical projects. You will be supervising and coordinating during different phases of the projects and making sure that work is...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13163/technical-coordinator</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Skilled Work</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 16:05:09 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Electrical Technicians</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading company providing security systems to a broad range of clients. They are currently seeking to recruit an Electrical Technician to join their team of operations.

Electrical&#xA0;Technicians
MT 1360/16

Key responsibilities will include:&#xA0;


	Attend to, diagnose, and repair faults that may arise on commercial security access control, CCTV/CCTV IP and fire alarm systems marketed by the Company to its clients.
	Perform client site evaluations to provide listings of...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12915/electrical-technicians</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Management</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 14:01:53 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Audit Manager</title>
        <description>Our client, an established company providing financial services to both local and international clients, is currently seeking to recruit an Audit Manager&#xA0;to join their team of professionals.

Audit Manager
MT 1034/16

In this role you will be responsible for managing&#xA0;a wide portfolio of clients across various industries. You will be able to deliver statutory documentation as per local legislation; prepare and certify financial statements to present to management and financial bodies;...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13164/audit-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 10:56:41 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accounts Executive</title>
        <description>Our client operates within the&#xA0;financial services industry offering a range of services to their local and foreign clients. They are currently looking to recruit an Accounts&#xA0;Executive to join their team of professionals.

Accounts&#xA0;Executive

MT 9871/16

Reporting to the&#xA0;Director, in this position you will be called to assume responsibility for preparation of accounting documentation for the group of companies up till&#xA0;management account level. You will also need to prepare the&#xA0;financial...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13157/accounts-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2016 13:22:33 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Mobile Specialist</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading telecoms organisation who has established a strong reputation in the local market. They are currently looking towards recruiting an experienced Mobile Specialist to join their team.

Mobile Specialist
MT 5676/16

Forming part of the Marketing Department, you will be called to conduct&#xA0;marketing analysis and drive&#xA0;product strategy within the Mobile Segment Team, contributing towards&#xA0;ensuring business objectives are achieved.&#xA0;You will be responsible for...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/13136/mobile-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 14:23:49 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Funds Specialist </title>
        <description>Our client, an established company providing financial services to both local and international clients, is currently seeking to recruit a&#xA0;Funds Specialist in to join their multi-disciplinary asset management team.

Funds&#xA0;Specialist
MT 7370/16

In this role you will form part of a multi-disciplinary asset management team. You will assist&#xA0;fund managers and other investment service providers negotiate the increasingly demanding regulatory landscape they face by offering holistic and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12515/funds-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Legal</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2016 09:22:49 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Senior Accountant (Gaming)</title>
        <description>Looking for an accounting job in Malta? Our client, an internationally established company within the betting industry, is currently in the process of setting up their office in Malta and is seeking to recruit a Senior Accountant to join their team.&#xA0;

Senior Accountant
MT 3661/16

As a Senior Accountant, you will be reporting to the Board of Directors. Your responsibilities will include handling&#xA0;financial&#xA0;reporting, the preparation of monthly, quarterly and annual&#xA0;financial...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12885/senior-accountant-gaming</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2016 10:46:14 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Financial Controller</title>
        <description>Our client, an established and well renowned organisation operating within the Real Estate industry, is currently seeking to recruit a&#xA0;Financial Controller to lead the&#xA0;Finance team.

Financial Controller
MT 1616/16

As Financial Controller&#xA0;you will champion&#xA0;the finance function&#xA0;and support the CEO, COO and the Directors in all financial matters. You will be a key player in the analysis of new projects, provide support and analysis to business managers for strategic and operational...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12895/financial-controller</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2016 18:48:07 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>MS Dynamics AX Consultant (Analysis &amp; Implementation)</title>
        <description>Our client is an international organisation specialising in business consultancy and IT solution implementation within the ERP, CRM and eCommerce market. They are currently looking to grow their team by recruiting an MS Dynamics AX Consultant.

MS Dynamics AX Consultant

MT 2291/16

Working alongside a team of project team leads and the Technical Architect, the AX Consultant will act as the product expert by representing the client internally. This will involve consultation and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12844/ms-dynamics-ax-consultant-analysis-implementation</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 09:10:33 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>MS Dynamics AX Developer</title>
        <description>Our client is an international organisation specialising in business consultancy and IT solution implementation within the ERP, CRM and eCommerce market. They are currently looking to grow their team by recruiting an MS Dynamics AX Developer.

MS Dynamics AX Developer (OOP)

MT 2190/16

Working within a development team on large scale solutions, the chosen candidate will be working on the MS Dynamics platform, and will be involved throughout the analysis, design, development,...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12843/ms-dynamics-ax-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 13 May 2016 16:57:14 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Product Support Specialist (IT)</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading provider of affiliate marketing software who powers some of the industry&amp;#39;s most successful and high volume affiliate programs by providing a single centralised complete solution. It is currently seeking to recruit a Product Support Specialist&#xA0;on a full-time basis.

Product Support Specialist
MT 5562/16

Reporting to the Product Support Coordinator,&#xA0;you will be providing first line support via Live Chat and Phone&#xA0;in a&#xA0;promptly and accurate manner.&#xA0;You will...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12761/product-support-specialist-it</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 13:57:11 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Technical Officer (NOC) - Shift Basis</title>
        <description>Our client, a leading provider of Data centre, cloud and managed services, is looking towards expanding its team through the recruitment of a Technical Officer.

Technical Officer (NOC) - Shift Basis
MT 0052/16

In this role, working on shift basis so as to cover the company&amp;#39;s 24x7 operations, you will be responsible for offering 1st level technical support to the company&amp;#39;s data centre&amp;#39;s clients, identifying and responding to faults, monitoring of network infrastructure and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12715/technical-officer-noc-shift-basis</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 16:31:58 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Deputy Services Manager</title>
        <description>Our client is an industry leader providing various engineering related systems. They have built a solid team and are constantly on the lookout to fine tune their operations in order to reflect best industry standards. They are currently looking for an Deputy Services Manager&#xA0;to join their team.

Deputy Services Manager

MT 0777/16

Reporting to the Head of Servicing Department, you will be responsible to support on management functions such as staffing, training and expanding business...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12685/deputy-services-manager</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Administrative &amp; Clerical</category>
                      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2016 11:21:29 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>QA Analyst (Manual &amp; Automation)</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading provider of affiliate marketing software who powers some of the industry&amp;#39;s most successful and high volume affiliate programs by providing a single centralised complete solution. It is currently seeking to recruit a QA Analyst&#xA0;on a full-time basis.

QA Analyst
MT 6668/16

Being part of the company&amp;#39;s QA Team you will be responsible to ensure that the Quality of Service level of&#xA0;the company&amp;#39;s platform is constantly maintained. You will be responsible to...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12614/qa-analyst-manual-automation</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Engineering</category>
                      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2016 13:59:45 +0200</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Information Security Officer</title>
        <description>Our client is seeking motivated individuals who are ready to join a multi-cultural team of IT professionals. As part of this team you will have the opportunity to work on projects for a global portfolio of clients.

Information Security Officer
MT 0696/16

Your role will be to assist the Manager to identify and implement information security policies, standards, guidelines, processes, procedures, and best practices in order to further strengthen the company&amp;#39;s security program to...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12454/information-security-officer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 08:24:58 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Brand Executive</title>
        <description>Our client is an established and well-renowned manufacturing company encompassing an array of international and local brands, currently seeking to recruit a Brand Executive to join their team of professionals.

Brand Executive
MT6900/16

As Brand Executive will be reporting to the Head of Marketing and Communications. You will engage in all the marketing activities related to a vast portfolio of brands including but not limited to, coordinating of digital and social media campaigns. You...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12382/brand-executive</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Marketing &amp; PR</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 08:58:32 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Technician</title>
        <description>Our client, an established and well&#xA0;renowned&#xA0;manufacturing company encompassing an array of international and local brands is currently seeking to recruit a Technician&#xA0;to join their team of professionals.

Technician
MT 5674/16

The jobholder will perform maintenance on any type of plant and machinery in line with established quality and efficiency standards. S/he will also perform overhaul tasks of electrical/electronic, mechanic and pneumatic nature according to required standards....</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/12166/technician</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Other</category>
                      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2016 11:27:13 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Junior Java Developer</title>
        <description>Our client is a leading telecoms organisation who has established a strong reputation in the local market. They are currently looking towards recruiting a junior developer or fresh graduate to join their Java development team.&#xA0;

Junior Java Developer

MT 1920/16

Reporting to the Head of Development and working in a technical development team,&#xA0;you will be involved throughout the whole development life cycle and will particularly contribute in requirements gathering, design and...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/9619/junior-java-developer</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Information Technology</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 17:01:01 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Sales Manager - Africa Region</title>
        <description>Our client is a very well established, innovative and fast-growing manufacturing company operating with the FMCG is currently seeking to recruit a Sales Manager &#x2013; Africa Region

Sales Manager &#x2013; Africa Region
MT 0647/16

As a Sales Manager you will be working closely with the Regional Manager and be responsible for the African region. You will be &#xA0;managing business development and client relations of the assigned geographical areas. This will also involve in analysing products, sales...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/11908/sales-manager-africa-region</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Sales &amp; Business Development</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 12:13:34 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Recruitment Specialist - IT and iGaming</title>
        <description>Building and fostering relationships is KONNEKT&amp;#39;s guiding principle. Ours is not a sales-driven model of recruitment. We are passionate about matching the right people with the right firms, but not at the cost of the relationships with our clients. KONNEKT&amp;#39;s track record in serving the most demanding business and individuals means we enjoy the trust of both firms and candidates alike.

Recruitment Specialist - IT and iGaming
MT 1784/16

Forming part of a small, yet highly...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/11136/recruitment-specialist-it-and-igaming</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 16:58:47 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Recruitment Specialist</title>
        <description>Building and fostering relationships is KONNEKT&amp;#39;s guiding principle.&#xA0;Ours is not a sales-driven model of recruitment.&#xA0;We are passionate about matching the right people with the right firms, but not at the cost of the relationships with our clients. Konnekt&#x2019;s track record in serving the most demanding business and&#xA0;individuals means we enjoy the trust of both firms and candidates alike.

Recruitment Specialist
MT 2476/16

Forming part of a tight-knit team, your focus will be to manage...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/10234/recruitment-specialist</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Human Resources</category>
                      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2015 16:58:34 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
          <item>
        <title>Accountant - Banking</title>
        <description>Our client operates in the banking industry and is currently looking for an Accountant to join their team of professionals.

Accountant - Banking
MT 5160/16

In this role you will perform general accounting and reporting duties including assisting with the preparation of management accounts. You will assist in all areas of finance as needed, including with regulatory reporting&#xA0;and producing company financial positions. This is an exciting role which would offer the right candidate an...</description>
                <link>https://www.konnekt.com/jobs/11135/accountant-banking</link>
        <enclosure url="https://www.konnekt.com/img/logo.png" type="image/jpeg"/>
                      <category>Accounting</category>
                      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2015 14:47:00 +0100</pubDate>
              </item>
      </channel>
<nodes>224</nodes></root>
